So I was listening to your videos, that's like why I was a little late.
And at one point you said that growing up, I think it was in Missouri, you said...
No, Montana.
My bad.
Well, would never want to mix up the two.
They're so discernible.
You said a Mennonite lumberjack was your only friend.
That is all true too.
Very unique statement, but she was my only friend, the Mennonite lumberjack.
So needless to say, I have a long history of getting women out of oppressive calls.
No.
And we need that.
And we genuinely need that.
I mean, what are you up to this week?
Let's just start there.
Oh my God.
This week, I can't talk about half of the things I'm doing, but this week mostly just with the kids and working and finishing out my semester because I'm back in school.
So I have to go defend my senior thesis, which...
Which is about what?
The end of rebirth and how the age of permanence with the internet, we've really foreclosed forgiveness and rebirth, which has always been like a prerequisite for humanity and moral agency.
And so just talking about how the internet and I call it like the age of permanence has foreclosed that with everything is all the time and you can bring up any transgression and how this is indistinguishable from any like secular articulation of hell.
Okay.
I'm obsessed with that.
And I imagine you have a lot of strong opinions on the subject because...
And in a much lesser way, I experienced a lot of that myself.
It's like if you've ever held one belief, you can't be redeemed and you're bad forever and you're tainted.
Is that kind of like what you're getting out of the thesis?
Yeah.
In the thesis.
And so right now what's interesting is I'm writing this in the thesis, but I'm also speed running how to change that.
So I'm like, okay, well, how do you do that?
How do you move past your transgressions when they're permanent?
And not only are they permanent, they can be circulated at any time, all the time.
Even if you've addressed it, then they're put back in circulation in perpetuity.
So I'm also speed running the best way to create a call to action and how we can fix that.
And what does that look like for you right now?
Right now, it's really just being very honest about my experiences and where I went wrong, what I did wrong being a very public mouthpiece and what were the motivations behind it.
Because so many people, I don't think years ago that I would have said I was deeply insecure, that I had so many issues with my self-esteem and how I was perceived and my standing in the world.
But that does play a big role for anybody who's involved in a cult or really involved in a political movement that it's structurally indistinguishable from a cult.
Would you call MAGA a cult?
Yes, I would.
Because what is a cult to you?
To me, it's the structure of it in which it's not just your beliefs, but leaving it blows up your entire life, right?
So it's the structure and the architect of the financials that are in it, that your entire life is this.
They tell you don't go to college or drop out of college and really just be a political influencer.
So your entire, not only identity, but your social circles, all of my friends were these MAGA influencers.
I was very sequestered.
And something that is really important is the way they sequester information.
Because as you remember, at the start of MAGA, it was fake news and don't trust the media, don't trust your professors, all of these institutions are lying to you, don't trust the experts.
I mean, what are we supposed to trust?
Twitter and social?
Like that is genuinely what they're saying.
Which is owned by, you know.
You can't trust the mainstream media.
You should trust Twitter and Donald Trump's truths over New York Times.
And that's not to say that these outlets don't get things wrong and that they're not run by humans who, you know, can succumb to bias or whatever it is, but they really, the information sequestering and keeping you from real information and it is really critical to keeping people in that environment and within that cult mentality.
That's such a fascinating point.
And even beyond people who aren't political influencers, and you've talked about this too, like telling people in MAGA not to take birth control.
It's like, don't get an education, get pregnant, like all of these things that makes it easier and easier.
So actually, if you saw my video on my crazy MAGA influencer ex-boyfriend, he like robs the cradle and I was like 19 years old at my first turning point conference, the Young Women's Leadership Conference.
And this grown ass man who was like over 10 years my senior, plucks me up from my mother's house after a month of dating, like moves me to Tampa and really like molds me into this perfect MAGA influencer costume.
Like here's what you should post, here's the signs you should post, here's what you should put on it.
Never crossed the base.
But another thing was the birth control.
He had told me because it was so volatile, our relationship, he's like, I think your birth control is making you crazy.
And yes, that's what started my rabbit hole down saying like birth control is bad because he's like, I think the birth control is making you- Messing with your hormones.
Well, he also told me that he thought the government was deploying sound weapons to ruin our relationship.
Like this man was like that shit fucking insane.
No, yeah, it's not your like drinking problem.
But it was the birth control.
He said the birth control.
Yes, the birth control.
The hormonal birth control I was on did make me like rather depressed.
So, you know, I was like, you know, women deserve informed consent about like what the side effects are because they really don't give us too much informed consent.
And I do agree with that.
And there needs to be more research about how to lessen those side effects and how to manage them as well.
So when I would talk about that from an informed consent standpoint, then the right wing influencers and MAGA would take it.
And then all of a sudden Charlie Kirk's on stage saying hormonal birth control is like black tar heroin.
That's what he said.
That is what he said.
And so I got in a very public spat with Charlie over this.
And I was like, what is this like white male crusader going on, a jihadist, I think, and then they got mad at you for that because they had meetings over this because I was like Charlie's on white male jihad, like telling like parents and husbands to take away women's birth control.
Like don't let your daughters be on birth control.
And mind you, it also I was on birth control well before I was ever sexually active because I have endometriosis and it is the only thing that helps me manage the symptoms because no one cares enough to invest in reproductive health care and find another solution.
I would be fine to not be on it if there was another way to manage it, but there isn't unless I get surgery.
Ashley St. Clair, it's so great to have you here.
We have, oh my God, we have so much to discuss.
I was listening to your get ready with me's and they're a riot by the way.
I agree with you on the new luminous silk being terrible.
It's awful.
What they did to them.
Why?
Can they stop changing things?
They did it because they needed to remove some ingredient that was like banned in the EU.
So now we all have to suffer.
Is it the talc or whatever?
I have no idea, but they fucking ruined it and I'm so upset.
What's like your new favorite foundation right now?
I think I have on the L'Oreal Pro Glow, the infallible.
It looks great.
It's fine.
So yesterday was Mother's Day and I did see Elon Musk posted a really, really sweet Mother's Day message.
He said, bitches, money, no taxes, party.
Wonderful.
That's really sweet.
Very, very classy.
I thought that that was really kind.
I love that.
I loved that.
I loved that as well.
I think that's what every mother really hopes to see from someone with whom she does have a child.
You should print that out on cards and just send them out.
And why hasn't Hallmark done that yet?
It feels like a really big missed opportunity, but one thing I wanted to ask you about, so I want to start with like the Mar-a-Lago of it all.
In one of your videos, you said that Mar-a-Lago, it's kind of like women treat it like it's this event.
Like there's like spray tan parties and all of these things.
And you mentioned that they have, they call her this, this is not your words or my words, a China lady who gets them fake handbags from China.
Is that true?
Yes, there is a China lady because they are all playing this, like keeping up with the Joneses and there's something like particularly sinister about the women among MAGA who enable this behavior so that they can class signal and all of this stuff.
But it really is, well, first of all, it's an aesthetic nightmare.
Like these women do all of this to look awful and like, no litter, dead ass.
And I'm like, then I'm like all of a sudden I'm butt ass naked and the girl's like, this is Laura Trump's spray tan girl.
And I'm like, and you're like, okay, like wear this, do this where it was like an all day affair.
It's like all these people do, it's all they think about.
Like it's all consuming for a party that's like, oh, we're so up the people.
Like you're not relatable at all.
They hate normal people.
They hate going to like the normal things.
These people would never take the subway in their lives.
Yeah.
Which I, I did myself for the first time alone to Brooklyn yesterday and I was really proud of myself.
I love the subway.
My son loves the subway.
The subway rocks.
It's amazing.
He's like, sleep, sleep.
Stand clear of the closing doors, please.
Doot doot.
He like knows it.
He loves it.
He'll be like, can we pretend we're on the train?
That's so cute.
I love that.
It was interesting.
Like you also said that essentially also when you go, it's like you're picking up your own tabs.
Like it's not even like people are necessarily paying for all your stuff.
Like Trump charges like a million dollars a year for a million dollars a year to be a member at Mar-a-Lago and they kept upping it as it got closer to the, the election cause they knew they could, but they're just paying for access.
It is such a weird vibe.
Like you go there and there's this patio area that Trump will like always eat out like with his family and these fucking orbiters will just like stare and like try to sit and eat next to him so that they can try to get a job in the admin.
Like Bill Pulte was orbiting around this man.
Like you would have thought Trump had his own like gravitational pull, like the way Pulte would just like orbit around him to try to get this job at HUD.
And like, this is what these people do.
This is how like all these jobs came about is by social climbing and really giving this man money.
You made such a good point too when in one of your videos you were talking about how yeah like he gives his donors jobs, which no matter where you are on the political spectrum, you should be able to look at that and be like, I don't want the highest bidder getting the job in the government.
Well, that was the big controversy when Kimberly Guilfoyle, who is the ex of Don Jr., Donald Trump Jr. When she got the appointment for ambassador to Greece, there was a big conundrum amongst people at the White House because they're like, well, what do we do?
Because we have like 20 donors and three congressmen who want this position.
That is what they said in text, like in permanence, in print to me.
And so this is absolutely how it operates.
That's insane.
You said something about House Inhabit also.
I hate that bitch.
That bitch is so crazy.
She's insane.
Tell me about why you hate her.
So she is just, she pretends to be an objective breaking news journalist, but she's really just a social climbing drunkard access journalist that in the words of the White House, was only brought there to launder the image of the Trump family.
And she sits here all day and night.
I have been nothing but cordial to this girl.
And then she is replying to posts calling me a cum dumpster, calling me a cum dumpster, saying and just basically saying yes.
Whoa, that's crazy.
So it wasn't just like, oh, a little like critique of me.
Sure.
That'd be fine.
Nasty.
This was nasty.
This was vile because Jess gets drunk and then she like fires off tweets.
So she replies to Emily Saves America as the one who called me a cum dumpster.
OK, really great company.
The irony, first of all, but I know at one point she had told her she was about to get sued for like this honey trap thing.
Emily Saves America.
Stop.
She tells the attorney and this guy, she's like, I don't even know how many people I've slept with, but like, I'll digress.
So then Jess replies to her, of all people, and it's like, oh, yeah, she's just mad that she didn't get the money she wanted, all this stuff.
You know, she overplayed her hand.
I was like, first of all, overplayed my hand.
I have cards on you, bitch.
Your husband was on an app for hookers and had a review on there.
OK, so let's talk about things, Jess.
I also know that you only have access to the White House because you were put there to launder the image of the Trumps.
So that's why I hate Jess.
Yeah.
When I saw her at a White House Correspondents Center event last year, she was like hammered out of her mind, like looked like she just rolled out of bed, just a hot mess, just like a frizzy mess, like being rude to the waitstaff.
They're like talking about how she was rude to waitstaff, which I think is the biggest red flag.
That is such an indicator of who a human being is, like how you treat people who are in service positions.
And yes, she's so rude to waitstaff, but also she had posted something like, oh, basically insinuating that I was envious of her.
I was like, bitch, I do not wish I was 30 years older, dressed like a lesbian and drunk off my ass at Mar-a-Lago with these white trash individuals.
Like, no, I don't envy you actually at all.
No.
OK, can I just say you're so funny and that's honestly really unusual for someone who was conservative for so long, because I just don't think conservatives are funny.
You know, I have so much PTSD from being in MAGA that I thought the words out of your mouth were going to be because you're a woman.
That's such a valid fear to have.
Like honest to God, that's such a valid fear.
But also that pisses me off that she said you just didn't get the money you wanted because you turned down an inconceivable amount of wealth.
Are you allowed to say the number?
People could look it up if they're not.
I have turned down a lot of money from a lot of various different sources.
And the money I've turned down from various sources is the GDP of a small nation.
OK.
I am probably the only bitch in the world who can turn down the amount of money I did and still be called a gold digger.
I'm like, what?
Women really can't win.
What do I have to do?
The same people calling me a gold digger would bend over and fold for a free appetizer at Mar-a-Lago.
And they have.
Yeah.
And they have and they will again.
So I want to talk to you a little bit about like leaving.
Like was there a specific moment where you're like, I've had enough?
Was there like a crux?
Sort of.
I always say that it was cumulative because I saw things over time and I didn't have the courage or the conditions to leave.
But what people always say, they say, she left because MAGA didn't like her.
And one thing that I think people know when they listen to me, I know MAGA very well.
I know social media very well.
I know the space very well.
I am not stupid.
I knew exactly their reaction, what that was going to be from the moment I announced my child.
I knew that when I took certain actions, I was going to be a persona non grata.
And I could have taken different actions in several regards, but I was ready to leave.
I'm the type of person who like once I leave a relationship, I'm already done.
Like I've done.
What's your sign?
Leo.
Oh, OK.
That makes perfect sense.
So, you know, when you're in a relationship, like if I leave a relationship, I've been done.
You're done though.
Yeah.
And so that's kind of how it was.
Like I was already done.
Like I did my like grieving enclosure while I was in it.
I really couldn't take it anymore, like on my conscience and my soul.
And then I'm a mother of two and I'm like, what am I?
What am I doing?
Like what is the legacy that I'm leaving for my kids?
What is the digital archive that I'm leaving for them to read, you know?
And so I wasn't proud of that and I wanted to change it.
Yeah.
I listened to your interview on A Bit Fruity podcast.
You talked and I want to address this specifically because I have a lot of trans listeners.
I'm pretty outspoken on trans rights.
You had harmful views on trans people that were reflective of, you know, I think you refer to it as trans panic in the conservative MAGA movement.
Do you feel like MAGA uses trans rights kind of as a way to distract from other things?
Because I've always felt like they use it as a way to distract from things getting more expensive and it like making it harder to live.
Like let's just blame this like random trans boogeyman.
Do you feel that way?
Yes.
They do use it as a distraction.
There's a few things going on.
One, it is a major distraction from real issues.
Two, they just enjoy being cruel.
Like they really enjoy being cruel to people who and punching down.
They really enjoy that.
And then lastly, they use it as a way to say like we care about women and children.
It is the one issue where they will say they care about women and children.
The only one.
The only one that they will ever say this while they keep sexual predators amongst the ranks.
For me, it was a place of ignorance and when you're in that, you don't think it's wrong because they're framing it as oh, you're protecting kids and this is wrong, this is evil.
And obviously in retrospect, it wasn't and I contributed to a lot of cruelty and harm within that community and I'm trying to do the most that I can.
I removed my name from the book that I wrote.
I cannot stop it from being published because of the agreements.
But I removed my name and I'm doing what I can in my local community as well and I'm less inclined to talk about that publicly because I don't want to put them in danger because there's so many eyeballs on me.
And so there are certain things that I want to do privately and keep privately and hopefully at some point I can speak about those publicly.
But I'm doing my best to make amends for the harm that I contributed to.
And then simultaneously, I was really uncomfortable with it behind the scenes and I know that's no excuse.
Like I should have also spoken up publicly, but I still have the messages with like libs of TikTok, hiya, where I was like, hiya, this is wrong, like you cannot dox these people.
And I wrote to her, I said, maybe the trans panic needs to stop and I still have those texts and it was just really difficult for me to navigate at the time and again, like that's not an excuse and I'm doing what I can now, but it was something that I had been uncomfortable with for a while.
It was something I've noticed about you that I really admire and I can't accept an apology on behalf of a community I'm not a part of, but you do strike me as being very genuine and sincere and like genuinely apologetic.
And I do think that when we know better, we do better.
Have you heard from people in the trans community?
Are people happy that you're speaking out?
Like have you had any meaningful conversations or exchanges?
Primarily the individuals that I've spoken to within the trans community are grateful and they're accepting.
And then there's a lot of people who say, I don't forgive you, but I appreciate the work you're doing and that's OK, too.
And there's still some people who are saying, fuck you, I don't forgive you at all.
And like you can fuck off into oblivion and that's OK, too.
Like all of those are valid responses.
And I'm not going to police or critique the way that communities that I contributed harm to are reacting to me.
Like that's not my place to critique.
Yeah, no, I think I think that's very, I think that's very fair.
So this is like a random question that I have with like MAGA influencers and stuff.
Are there influencers on the left who they're kind of like afraid of as being like very like effective or like like ones they want to take down?
Yeah, they are very scared of Hasan Piker.
Oh, they are?
That is like the one that they are scared of because Hasan has the ability to capture what I believe to be someone like the alt-right men as well.
Like he there is a crossover between the people who gravitate towards a Nick Fuentes or a Tucker Carlson that could find better solace in someone like Hasan.
They're terrified of Hasan Piker.
Terrified.
That's fascinating to me.
Oh, wow, that's interesting.
Yeah, I know there there is crossover.
And I mean, I've I've critiqued Hasan in the past and like his stands will come for me.
Like I'm I'm kind of of the mindset of I don't I really don't like a lot of things that he has to say, but I think he's a net good and I think he like deserves a platform.
I don't think he should be canceled.
I do think he says some things are like absolutely beyond the pale from time to time.
But that is so interesting.
Yeah, I mean, I don't I've always defended everyone's right to speak.
Even my biggest detractors.
I think we should be very wary whenever there is an establishment push to silence anyone.
I think that shows if the levers of capital are all fixated against one individual, you should probably pay attention to that.
I completely agree with that take.
Like I I've always been of the mindset of like, especially with all the shit going on with the FCC right now, like and I'm trying to like talk to conservatives and be like, listen, I think a lot of what you say on Fox News is stupid dog shit garbage.
And I hate it, but I still do defend your right to say it.
Yeah.
And listen to it and engage.
But also with people like Hassan or any streamer, they are live for so long and they are living the most honest articulation of like thought and commentary.
They're going to say stupid shit.
And that's OK.
And I guess that goes back to like my thesis, right?
It's like there has to be some forgiveness and grace to people being human and saying stupid shit, because look, if anyone pulled up our texts and group chats, you know, like I also get it.
We all say stupid things.
And I think it's really important to put that humanity and being human and being stupid back into the public sphere and owning it.
I think that is really important, especially like as we're building systems that aggregate humanity and we purposely leave so much of humanity out.
I think we have to put that back in and we have to have grace for people who are human and decide to speak all day, every day.
And yeah, there's going to be some things that are taken out of context that sound bad.
Like I have things that are in context.
That's awful.
Yeah, you know, famously so awful in context.
So I think there should just be grace in that regard.
I hear you.
And my hot take is that the people who are the loudest about trying to like point fingers and cancel people are just trying to distract from their own shit and the own harm that they've caused.
Oh, yes.
You know, yes, we see that with MAGA, the Party of Family Values.
Speaking of MAGA, so I was I was watching a video that you did about your ex-boyfriend DC Drano and a member who named himself.
By the way, I want to be very clear.
I called him Mr. Tampa.
He decided to make a statement afterwards and name himself.
So now we're naming.
So now we're naming names.
He couldn't resist.
And by the way, I lived in Tampa for a little bit.
Were you in South Tampa?
I don't remember where the drama.
No, I was in a place where the ceiling was falling down.
Oh, what the hell?
Wait, is he the one who is Binder Boy, the Epstein Binder?
Tell me that.
Oh, he was one of them.
Oh, he was the one.
He was a binder.
He was a binder boy.
Yes.
Oh, he's like real hideous.
Was he also the one who pissed?
Yeah.
No one cared when I was being a broke, ugly man.
OK, just when you're dating a rich, ugly, shallow.
So you can't date a rich, ugly one or a poor, ugly one.
What the fuck?
They all treat you like shit.
And that's the thing.
They're like, oh, like go for the ugly guy.
Go for the shy guy.
Go for the nerd.
No, because then you embolden them.
You can't do that.
And then they have too much nerve.
Yeah.
So talk to me about this relationship between him and a member of Congress.
So that's the only thing he decided to address head on in his statement was him and Ana Paulina Luna, because when we were dating, their relationship was just so weird.
It was just weird.
They were texting all the time.
She was making group chats saying like, oh, you should break up with her.
She's a brand liability.
I'm like, OK, fair.
But like that made me look like she's you're like, you did cook with that.
That's specifically the fact that any woman is like making a group chat to tell a man to like break up with her girlfriend.
That is like whatever.
So then I like almost die with a kidney infection that goes to my blood.
And I'm like, you know what?
Sayonara, I'm going to go visit my family in Colorado for a few days.
Like so then I leave.
I come back.
There's a cheap ass face mask in our shared bathroom, which was weird because I already moved into the guest room because I was over him.
OK, sure.
Then that's how it starts.
I was like, whose fucking face mask is this?
He goes, I thought it was yours.
I was like, it's not I would never use something that's fucking cheap.
Yeah, it was like one of those ones that falls apart.
No, it was like checkout aisle at Walmart.
The one that's like the self-checkout.
You're like, no, I can't.
You're like, I would literally never.
It was like it was on us.
But like nothing happened.
Nothing happened.
She was just here because she needed a place to stay because, you know, she's trying to run for Congress here because she was carpetbagging the district.
I think at that point she lived in Washington State.
Stop it.
She moves to South Florida and like stays over whatever they even if I stipulate that nothing happened, honestly, it would be better if they fucked because their relationship is so weird.
Like it's it's so strange.
And every one of his exes has an issue with it.
Like she will call him in the middle of the night talking about her visions, her dreams.
What do you mean visions?
She has vision.
OK, that's so Raven.
Yeah, literally.
Fucking what?
And her premonition.
She said that Rogan's ex-wife had a rotten spiritual smell.
Like, what does that mean?
And Rogan is D.C. Drano.
Yeah.
A rotten spiritual smell.
Like you're just a weird bitch.
And so she would go to his office.
Just a weird, weird relationship.
And then when I make this video talking about this, you know what she does?
She posts a video of Elon Musk with 15 sparkle emojis.
You weird bitch.
Like you.
I'm making a video about how obsessed you are with my ex.
So then you post the father of my child with 15 sparkle emojis.
You are one weird bitch.
Yeah, you're a weird ass bitch.
You're a weird ass bitch.
You have you have premonitions of spiritual rot.
You're a weird bitch.
So weird.
So like, above all else, you're just fucking weird.
So you posted a video recording of his Twitter feed.
And it's just all about her.
I mean, like post after post, it honestly looks like a paid like supporter.
That's OK.
But like anyone else that you know in your space that you post, like people know your friends.
They like don't publicize that they're friends or that he's the godfather of her child or that like they're invested in businesses together.
It's not her child, that his that his brother was hired on her congressional payroll to be security.
This man has a security expert.
No.
So that's what's weird.
Like you have all these posts and you're not up front about your.
It's just weird.
Yeah, it's like almost like if they're not hooking up like I wish you would.
Because now now it's just weird.
Yes.
Like that's just like a really strange environment.
But all of these people are weird.
Did you ever have any run ins with Caroline Lovett?
I did.
When she ran for that losing race in Congress, I did her video for that.
Now, at that time, she was dating like a guy her age, which, by the way, why do I get all the heat for dating an older guy?
That man, she's someone.
Did you see someone posted the photo she posted with her newborn baby?
They said you're closer in age to your baby than your husband.
Oh, I think about that for a minute.
Wait, is that OK?
Oh, yes.
Because she's like, what, 27?
And he's like 60.
Anything else about Emily Saves America?
Emily Saves America was involved in a honey trap.
Can you explain what that is for people unaware?
A trap is like where you have a young pretty would be a nice word for her because she's chopped as fuck.
I don't know.
She really is.
I saw her happening to her.
She used to be like kind of pretty.
I think she's just on the Internet.
I know.
I think the ugly like the rotten spiritual smell of her soul is coming out.
Hey, it's all about that rotten spiritual smell.
I'll ask Anna about that.
We also one really quick thing on her.
You said that she added Luna or something into her last name to sound more Latina, like she used to go by used to go by on a Polina.
And then she added Luna.
Remember, she was like a turning point influencer when she says she worked at a nonprofit.
The nonprofit in question was turning point, which like is it on paper a nonprofit?
She makes it like she was working for fucking Habitat for Humanity.
Right.
It's not St. Vincent de Paul.
Like we're talking about a thing that puts on like a massive, massive money making events.
Like, let's be so for real.
Wait, I'm sorry.
I totally detracted us.
OK, so Emily is.
Well, no, the bigger tea about Anna.
She also pretended to be Jewish like she was running around.
There are headlines saying, is she the next George Santos?
Because she was running around saying she's Jewish.
And then it turned out that her grandfather is a Nazi, like a literal literal Nazi.
Like these people are a mess, a mess, a mess, a mess.
No, I can't.
So Emily saves America.
I was at this company called Arsenal Media Group that was started by Benny Johnson and run by this fucking idiot in a 98 Dodge Caravan, Jason Cole.
And I'm fucking living for this conversation.
By the way, like fucking half the staff, which pissed me off because then everyone thought I was sleeping with him.
And I was like, I would never.
So then Jason has Emily.
Emily saves America sleep with a very prominent member of MAGA and tries to get her to record it for blackmail on him.
They're recording him facetiming.
And isn't that also illegal to like record like a sexual attack?
She's like, why is your name in like a potential lawsuit against me?
I was like, read 842 a.m. Yeah.
And then we're just going to open and close that one.
Yeah.
She's a hoe.
And she's like just dumb as a doorknob.
And she's been dating this guy forever who like won't marry her.
And she's sitting here like shitting on all these other people because she was hating on the one girl's engagement ring.
Right.
Yes.
But she can't get one.
Who's the girl who posted their stock?
OK, so someone said that that only happened, that ring gate only happened because when I fell down as the top conservative girl, that it left a power vacuum like when they took out Saddam Hussein.
They said it left a power vacuum when Saddam Hussein, your power.
Holy shit, Ashley, your power.
I think that's my header on Twitter.
I think you can find it.
That's not real.
Yeah, it's pretty funny.
But so, yeah, she's she's shitting on women's engagement rings and she was like, oh, it's so small or whatever.
Bigger than yours, bitch.
Yeah.
And I'm like, OK, wait.
So are you guys the party that like wants people to like get married or not?
Now they also have to be rich.
Like, like, well, everything she does is undisclosed ads to like all of it.
Everything she posts.
I think there's some link she was doing for climate something.
It's all paid and none of it.
That's why she was so mad at me for talking about how the the paid influence campaigns work, because she's on the take.
Talk a little bit about use her more because she's such a cheap hoe.
Like her rates are lower than the other people's.
Oh, that's embarrassing.
Yeah.
And I mean, this is such I'm I'm moved into these conversations all the time.
People think I'm paid for everything I say.
I'm like, I really don't think you guys understand the cash flow problem that we have on the left.
Like also, even if I were the things that I'm saying are like immigrants are people and trans people deserve rights.
Like even if I was paid to say that, what's the problem?
Talk to me a little bit about what that paid influencing looks like.
On the right.
So it's just everything.
They get paid for their tweets.
They get paid for messaging, for petitions, for and it's all coordinated.
A lot of the messaging is coordinated via group chats, via actual campaign calls with the administration, with the campaigns, with all of these figures that you see on Twitter.
They're all in lockstep.
You said something I thought was really interesting.
You said that the Trump administration will literally scour influencers on the right for any criticism of Trump and the administration.
And if they have criticized him at all, they're like barred from Mar-a-Lago, etc.
Oh, yeah, they'll get barred.
I have a girlfriend who she was supposed to go to an event at Mar-a-Lago in secret.
Katie Miller told her that Secret Service like scanned her social media and said that she couldn't go because she was questioning the assassination of Charlie Kirk.
This happened to me, too, because I was critical of Trump right before the primaries.
And then all of these influencers were attacking me, saying she's on the take from Ron DeSantis.
And I was like, one of them needs to pay me because I'm getting accused by both sides.
But no, they're they're paid for everything.
When they were all talking about how we all need the ballroom right after the assassination attempt, I'm putting that shit in quotes at the White House Correspondents Dinner.
Is that an example of like a paid messaging campaign?
With the ballroom rhetoric that happened, there's one of two options.
Either you're so fucking stupid that you all came to the same ignorant opinion.
Sure.
You all looked at that and said Trump needs his ballroom, which is a possibility.
No, it's not the statistical likelihood of everyone looking at that like independently and objectively and saying he needs a ballroom is not likely.
And the other option is that it's coordinated and they're getting paid for that shit.
Sometimes they're not paid.
Like sometimes they just want to be a part of the cool kids club so much that they will just say, oh, OK, the White House wants this out.
So there's also also this social like validation aspect of it, too.
So a lot of it is paid, but also they just want to be accepted by this social circle.
And I think about this a lot.
So before I did entertainment full time, I had a background in research and I did research on belonging, which sounds like.
But it's actually like a very real concrete concept that leads to better retention, better employee morale.
Like I would do it for clients.
And I think about this with MAGA a lot.
I think that for a lot of people and you, you talk about this a lot, too.
And people really should go watch Ashley's video.
She gets into like a lot of hilarious, like amazing detail talking about all this, but it's also very smart how it all kind of happens and works together, the machine.
But I think a lot of people mistake assimilation for belonging and MAGA.
It's like the red hats and the this and the that.
That's not actually true belonging because the tenants of belonging are absent, which is like respect, trust.
Right.
Like none of those things are present.
All that you have are these like symbols that don't actually amount to belonging.
Yeah.
And that's what makes it more indicative of a cult, too, because it's just a lot of symbolism and whatever.
And they also prey on very vulnerable people.
I was an incredibly broken individual.
Like I still am in a lot of ways.
I was a kid.
I was 18 getting involved with Turning Point chapters, Young Americans for Liberty.
Like I was out of my home and I still had so many issues and I had issues with alcohol use and drug use and all of this.
And they prey upon these people who just like so desperately want to belong and have some sort of social validation that it's it's so much easier for them to get away with this because broken individuals are less likely to speak out as well.
Absolutely.
And it's also so much more difficult to leave.
I mean, like you talked about it.
And again, it's like you're not defending any of your past decisions.
You're just providing context.
Like once you've built your entire social circle around a movement, if you leave that movement and you change your beliefs, you lose a massive part of your identity.
You lose most of your close friends, most of your professional opportunities.
Like that is difficult.
And it's dangerous.
Like these people don't just say, oh, OK, bye.
See you never.
They don't let you leave peacefully.
You've had people approach your family members at baseball games at, you know, in the grocery store or wherever.
Well, what do they say?
Like, are you do you know Ashley St. Clair?
So right now, what just came to fruition like this weekend was there's a team of private investigators that have been physically harassing my family and people connected with my family.
And that is very.
What do they say?
They they are just saying things that are like, oh, here's the photos we have of all you guys.
They're quite literally showing them the photos that they have.
And that is a cult.
I know a journalist personally who covered Scientology.
And then one day I get chills every time I think about it.
They sent her a photo of her mother, like through the blinds of her mother's house.
And that's it.
And that is intimidation tactics that they use in cults that we know to be terrifying, like Scientology.
Right.
And now MAGA is doing the same shit.
And I can assure you people love to say all both sides are the same.
Whatever.
If I were to just, you know, kind of exit liberal influencing or whatever, I would not have people harassing my family members like that simply would not happen.
No.
And that's the other thing.
It's like they want to paint me as some gold digging grifter, attention seeker.
Then then why is there so much energy being put into shutting down?
How are you taking care of yourself mentally?
I love Pilates.
I love reading.
I love my kids.
Just hanging out with my kids is really grounding, too.
And I have real life friends who are not involved in politics or media.
We love that.
And then they never even know what's going on, which is kind of great.
I love that they don't know what's going on.
Seriously.
I also just have good friends who even if they know what's going on, they don't bring it up and just doing normal things.
And being back in school has been really grounding, too, because I'm with a lot of my old professors who knew me for the way I thought when I was a kid, you know.
And so that's been really grounding and helpful.
Because you dropped out of college to like to do MAGA influencing.
Yeah, because I mean, like like we talked about DCJ.
Yeah, because they don't they don't want women.
They really don't want women to be educated.
Yeah.
And I have a really great family.
Like my mom is my rock.
Like I love her so much.
And so it's just.
You're going to suffer anyways, like pick a suffering that's worth it.
You know, it's not like my life would be all peachy if I didn't do this.
I would still have my other issues or there would be a new problem.
But I feel more comfortable now, which sounds crazy because I have more problems now than ever.
But I feel more like content and at peace because I think there's like a burden off of my conscience and my soul from like just talking about things honestly and being a real human being and not thinking about like curating it for for something and just being like, honestly, myself has been really helpful.
That's great.
And you're aligned.
And I get that, too.
I've been super honest about the fact that I grew up super conservative.
As we talked about, there's a whole machine, right?
It starts with the fellowship of Christian athletes sponsoring all of the after school events, which then feed you to the evangelical mega church, which then feeds you to turning point.
Right.
Like all of these things all work together.
And I've been super open about the fact that like I've had an abortion and there's just so much freedom in speaking truth to the things that you used to keep hidden and you used to keep a secret.
Just like you can't shame me for things that I'm fully owning.
Exactly.
You feel that way?
There's something inherently dirty about keeping a secret, even if it's not something that's wrong.
And so there there was a heavy burden on me for a while, like keeping these secrets like almost for a living.
But it's been good to just get them off my chest.
And I hope these other people do, too, because guess what?
There's a lot of people who should be honest about the abortions they had in the White House.
Like who?
I can't.
Can we believe?
Yeah.
Wow.
Right before she met her current husband and was at the White House, the thing they've all had.
I'm cheating on her husband.
She had a husband, cheated on him and got pregnant and got an abortion.
Party of family values.
Would you identify as a Democrat now?
I've been a registered independent for a while now.
I identify with a lot more progressive causes, I would say, than hard Democrat.
I just maybe I'm just like a more radical individual generally, but like I just don't agree with how moderate a lot of the Democrat policies are.
You said something I thought was brilliant, and I completely agree.
And I'm like, wait, yeah, you were like more Democrats would probably appeal to people on the right if they would run on things like overturning Citizens United, which like, to be fair, Democrats do want to overturn Citizens United, but they're not making it a focal part of their platform.
They're not making it a focal point.
They're also people need health care.
People need housing.
The war in Israel and what's going on on behalf of Israel is not popular.
The fact that they won't speak to this is absurd at this point.
And it's they're just shooting themselves in the foot.
Now, what I can be very clear about is I would never vote for a Republican again.
Absolutely not.
When we have these Republicans going up there who are supposed to be judges and taking appointments for these things, they will not state clearly that Trump cannot have a third term.
Go fuck yourself.
They can't stay clearly that he lost the election.
So so no, I will never, ever, ever vote for a Republican again.
That's what I can say.
There's a lot of work that has to be done in terms of orienting this country in onto the right path that I think should be more progressive than it is.
I think that's a fair take.
So there was a time last year, it was like the beginning of last year where literally out of nowhere, all of these conservative influencers at once started going at me so hard, like like it was like it was nothing.
And then there were all of these like random people making insane videos about me, my family, like screenshotting my LinkedIn and like trying to get me fired from my job.
The reason I'm bringing this up is because now that I look at it, I'm like, oh, that was totally like paid and orchestrated.
Like would the have you ever seen the right sometimes like that?
I really think you're discounting like how much the cruelty feeds off of it, like they really enjoy that when they see a good target that's going to get engagement.
They're like, oh, I'll post about this person, too.
Oh, let's see what else we can find.
Because you're a pretty girl who's saying things that they disagree with.
And so that's going to be fodder for MAGA and for the incel community and all of this stuff.
And they get off on that cruelty.
What do you see for your future?
Like what's next for Ashley?
I think, well, I'm going to I plan to go to law school and fight back.
You're going to be a great attorney, dude.
I want to go on the civil side and I want to regulate the shit out of AI.
Yes.
So we love that.
But I also turned down an AI sponsorship that would have paid my mortgage for the rest of the year, and it was really, really hard.
But I did it.
I don't think I didn't do it happily.
Yeah, but I did it good for you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I would advertise that more because courage is contagious.
And I think there needs to be a hard line in the sand about taking money from people who are so ontologically evil and disrupting like the anthropological and ontological conditions of humanity.
It's ontological, like the way in which we exist as humans and our interactions with the world and how we've existed spiritually.
So that is really concerning because I don't know that there's any going back.
And I think there's a desperate need for more people to go back to school for philosophy, because most of the philosophers that we read, they didn't have the ontological conditions that we do now with the Internet and technology.
And so it's a great point.
It's almost like like a Eurocentric philosopher who speaks about slavery.
You know, like they didn't have.
They didn't have a very necessary context that totally changes the rules.
Yes.
So like Hegel speaking on slavery, you're like, dude, you don't know.
Very Eurocentric.
Yeah, you don't know.
And so I think the same can be said about most thought that we have.
That's not here.
I think it's really important for more people to do long form thoughts about what it's like in this current technological stage of humanity.
That's so interesting.
Yeah, I really I really should talk about that more.
I don't think people understand like the number of things I turn down because they're ideologically misaligned with who I am.
That is really important.
And it's also important to tell because there's going to be young people who look up to you as a young pretty girl.
And you you've called me pretty twice.
I'm like, wait, yes, I'm like, come back any time.
You as well, Diva, obviously, or you wouldn't be here.
No, I'm kidding.
No, no, I was allowed on this podcast.
Sorry, it's prettier in here than a make America hot again party.
Can we actually talk about that for a second before I ask you when they had to cancel it because everyone was shocked because everyone was chopped as fuck.
And I know that for a fact, because an influencer who I'm friends with and you can believe this, Maria.
He responded to my video about her and he was like, I'm laughing my fucking ass off, like, get her.
I hate her.
Like, she's the worst.
But like what a little bitch is he like?
Say it publicly.
I know people do not.
I have no respect for that because they all talk shit about each other.
And I talk shit in public.
They all talk shit about each other behind their backs.
And they know how rotten MAGA is.
They know the shit I'm saying is true.
They know how awful the Mar-a-Lago scene is.
Like they know these things.
And there's people who want to leave.
There are people who are on your grandma's TV right now that are they want to leave.
OK.
And they're scared, especially the women.
But they're they feel stuck.
It does seem like there are more and more women, especially within the MAGA movement, who are pissed.
And none of none of the current conditions.
And this is why I'm particularly angry at the women of MAGA.
None of this would be allowed to occur if they stopped keeping the secrets for these men.
They know those women know.
Do you think there's like we're on the cusp of some of them kind of breaking out of that movement?
I hope so.
But they're scared.
They're scared.
Like people people always say to me, they're like, oh, well, why didn't you leave sooner?
But then simultaneously, they're like, these are evil people who kill people.
And simultaneously, they get mad at you for leaving.
Trust me, been there.
Like, I understand, again, to a lesser extent.
But like I was I was a Republican over 10 years ago before any MAGA existed, and I still get shit for it.
Well, I hope that any conservative women and actually a few have slid in my DMs when I've called out people on the right who've been like that guy's such a piece of shit.
Like, I'm really afraid of him.
But like, I'll give you information.
If any women on the right want to break out, you can always talk to me.
Like, I'll keep it confidential.
I'm I'm for the girls.
And I want I want to love that.
I want people to get out.
That's what I'm working on, too, like being a girl's girl.
Like, I feel so bad for the women that like I betray during my time.
I think about that, too.
Just like I was such a pick me.
And like that really disgusts me, like how much of a pick me I was.
And I just because we thought that aligning ourselves with like the patriarchy and stuff would like save us from all the harm that.
No, I didn't think that far ahead.
Oh, you did it harder than me.
But like, I was just like, I want to be like you, which also.
Yeah, I mean, especially if I just had such a need for validation, like you were probably smarter than me, but I was just like they like me.
I was a smart and an idiot at the same time, though, because I look at the things I used to say and I'm like, bitch, you really thought that?
But I did.
I just like didn't question it.
And I think that's part of it is like, don't question.
Yeah.
Even questioning the assassination of Charlie Kirk can get you banned from the White House.
I'm like, questioning is good.
We should want people to question really quick before I ask you someone you want to roast, someone you want to toast.
Are there any Democrat politicians that you like and or that you think could appeal to people on the right who kind of want to come over?
I like what Elizabeth Warren is doing.
Yeah, I think the way she's holding CEOs accountable is fantastic.
I think she's been doing great work there.
I think AOC and Bernie have been doing fantastic work with the data centers and AI.
I think that's a move in the right direction.
I do love our mayor in New York City.
I do love Zahran and the MAGAs who are saying that they don't.
They're lying.
OK.
They all like him.
They like him.
Even Trump's like in love with them.
Yeah.
You can't help but love him.
I mean, what's not to like?
Yeah, I think there's going to need to be just more not brand safe Democrat or progressive influencers.
I think that's why someone like Hassan is so effective.
Or like the women at IHIP.
I think they're amazing because they just are very blunt.
We need more honest and blunt people who will bring over MAGA and speak to just like real life experiences.
That's how they're used to being communicated to.
I think that's why my style has resonated with people on the right, too, is because they're kind of used to being talked to like that.
Yeah.
Have a little more gusto.
Sounding like such a little bitch.
Yes.
Just human.
Sure.
Just like more human.
Like the way that you would talk to anybody else.
I've heard a lot of people on the right say that they like AOC, actually, who's someone you would like to roast and someone you would like to toast.
We're skipping over Ashley's mean, but true, because she's already she's already kind of covered it.
She's covered the gamut, I would say.
Someone I want to roast and someone I want to toast.
Can we bleep it?
Why do you want to roast that person?
Because I think he's ontologically evil.
Genuinely.
Is he just like a fucking dweeb?
I think he's far less intelligent than people give him credit for.
Charismatic?
No.
Well, toast to Ron.
For what?
Because I thought his video that he did outside of that billionaire's empty house here in New York was great.
The people who just have these massive ass mansions and like don't actually stay in them.
I did see that.
I thought that was awesome.
I think we need to start making billionaires much more uncomfortable.
Yeah, I agree.
Because why do you have more money than God and more money than sense?
Yeah.
And people are starving.
Talked about this.
There's no there's no way to become an ethical billionaire.
There just isn't.
And I thought maybe there was.
Then I found out.
No.
I did an analysis of someone's wealth where I said, if you wanted to have as much wealth as this person, you would have to save one.
And we're just talking like straight cash.
Yeah, people like this.
Not all the stock market works.
No shit.
I'm just trying to put it in perspective for people.
You would have to save one million dollars every day since like 50 B.C. like in order to have like the amount of money that Peter Thiel has.
And he's not even the richest person in the world.
I think the progressives should do more visualizations of that.
Exactly how big the wealth gap is.
I think that's really important to articulating what's happening in this country because there's been more wealth displacement in the past few years than we've ever seen.
And we'll end on this note.
I ask every guest is what's something you love about yourself?
I love the mom I am.
And I love my ability to cook them meals that they love.
Like what?
What are their meals they're into?
So my older son loves when I make him this like Spanish rice.
And I stole the recipe from one of my girlfriends.
But he's obsessed with it.
OK, that's so cute.
Put on his mother's day thing.
He said my favorite thing is when his mommy's cooking.
That's so cute.
Because some of the kids are assholes.
So like my favorite thing is when my mommy finally gets off her phone or whatever.
And they're being honest.
He said he said mommy's most beautiful when she puts on her makeup.
And I was like, he said, listen, bitch, fix your face.
No, I think he was actually being so sweet.
No, it's adorable.
He knows that I like my makeup.
Yeah, he's asked me.
He's like, why do you put on your makeup?
I was like, I just like it.
It makes me feel pretty and fun.
And it's like my art.
Like when you color, this is my color.
Feminist king.
Yeah.
So but yeah, I love the mom I am.
I think that's my favorite part about myself, because it also helps you like deconstruct some other harmful things.
Like my son, we were at the grocery store and he heard people speaking Spanish and he goes, they're not speaking English.
I was like, no, they're speaking Spanish.
He goes, God just made them that way.
I was like, yeah, baby.
That's so cute.
And it was kind of like a full circle moment for me because I know several years ago I would have been like, why aren't they speaking English in my grocery store?
Like and so to have it come full circle and like see that my son is being raised with like kindness and understanding that I'm like, OK, like that's all worth it.
That'll be the legacy that you leave behind.
And your kids have a badass mom.
Like one day your kids are going to be like, yeah, my mom turned down a gargantuan sum of money because she loves me.
Really?
What's something you're working on about yourself?
There's a few things.
Really, the way I consume information is a big one.
But also just working on the thought patterns that I had, that I needed so much validation at that point in my life and working on making amends to the people that I harmed.
But really trying to adjust the thought patterns and getting to the root of, OK, why did I need why these demons who like me so much?
Like why was that the source of validation for me?
And so that's something that I've been working through.
Well, this has been such a great conversation.
I'm so happy that you were down to do it.
I've loved it.
Where can people find you and how can they support you?
I do not shout out my social medias, but why?
Because I don't want to be self-promoting right now.
Just at this point, if people find me, they find me.
What I would rather encourage people to do is read a book that I have liked over the past year's Evil Geniuses.
I think it's really great.
And talking about how we got to the current condition we did in the United States, particularly with money and politics.
I think that's a great book.
And Dark Money is another one.
Evil Geniuses.
OK.
And Dark Money is the other one.
I'll link them in the video.
Yeah.
Amazing.
I'd rather promote other people's thoughts in their full articulation.
I think people need to read books cover to cover again.
One last thing.
That's what's crazy about MAGA.
I learned so many of these people don't read the fucking books behind them, like in their news heads.
Like they do not read the books on their shelves.
They're just decoration.
I would go to their houses and ask them about these books on their shelves.
They could not tell me anything about them.
These people don't fucking read.
So read.
It's also crazy not to lie when lying is right there.
You could be like, oh, it's been a while since I've read that one.
I don't remember.
Yeah, but then it's every one.
Because I would ask them about like a bunch of them.
Yeah.
Are you an avid reader?
Since I was a kid, like I love reading.
And then I just kind of stopped doing it for a little bit when I was in MAGA.
And now I'm back to reading.
And now we're back to reading.
Yeah.
Read.
And like I always say, go to the club.
I'm seeing a lot of discourse about baby doll dresses feeding into pedophilia.
You guys get off the Internet, read a book, go to the club, hang out with people in real life.
People are being people are being really crazy.
We are all on the Internet too much.
Yes.
And let's consume information in a different way.
Well, thank you so much.
This was so much fun.
I love having you.
Yay.
And I'll see you next Tuesday.