Ashley St. Clair: Welcome to my home.
Luke: Thank you for having us.
Luke: I'm here with...
Ashley St. Clair: Ashley St.
Ashley St. Clair: Clair.
Luke: And what are we doing here?
Ashley St. Clair: We are exposing the systemic rot within MAGA and why Benny Johnson is indicative of all of it.
Luke: The online right-wing media ecosystem is fundamentally broken, corrupt, and dishonest.
Luke: Today, to explore this, I sat down with Ashley St.
Luke: Clair, who herself was a MAGA influencer for years, was in that right-wing media world, and is the mother of one of Elon Musk's kids, and witnessed things in that world.
Luke: That shook her to her core.
Luke: She's now exposing it all.
Luke: Benny Johnson is one of the largest influencers in the right-wing online media world, and Ashley worked for him at a company called Arsenal Media Group.
Luke: In this interview, we investigate him specifically.
Luke: Because he is, as Ashley put it, an embodiment of what is so broken about this cohort of influencers.
Luke: The financial impropriety, the workplace abuses, ignoring and covering up sexual harassment, public versus private life, hypocrisy.
Luke: And getting very, very rich by ripping people off and stoking outrage.
Luke: I try not to say this too often, but this is an interview you're going to want to watch until the bitter end.
Luke: She starts off by giving us insight into what it was like.
Luke: like working for Benny Johnson.
Luke: But by the end, we find out about foreign money flowing through MAGA media corruptly.
Luke: People being paid to say certain things they otherwise wouldn't say.
Luke: Campaign finance violations.
Luke: MAGA parties that get nasty.
Luke: And of course...
Luke: The age-old rumor with Benny gets a clear confirmation.
Luke: Is another obnoxiously anti-LGBTQ right-wing figure who desperately posts constantly about his super-duper, uber-traditional family hiding a secret about himself?
Luke: Ashley has the answer.
Luke: And we talk about it.
Luke: An important context as you prepare to learn about MAGA media and Benny Johnson as a symbol of it, Ashley stands by the fact that she wasn't planning on exposing everything about Benny in particular until he came after her child.
Luke: What do I mean?
Luke: Well, a few months ago, as Ashley's political shift had begun, someone commented on one of her posts reacting to her political shift, saying, you've previously engaged in blatant transphobia.
Luke: How do you feel about trans people in the wake of noticing how the far right truly is?
Luke: That was the comment at Ash St.
Luke: Clair, to which she responded, quote, I feel immense guilt for my role.
Luke: And even more guilt that things I have said in the past may have caused my son's sister more pain.
Luke: So her son with Elon Musk, and then Elon has a daughter who is trans.
Luke: I don't really know how to make amends, she continues, for many of these things, but I have been trying incredibly hard.
Luke: privately to learn and advocate for those within the trans community that I've hurt.
Luke: I also haven't said much on this because I have gone back and forth over whether my voice would be helpful on this issue since it will be framed as disingenuous or just turning because I'm scorned.
Luke: Even this reply will become right-wing hysteria, but yeah, I'm sorry.
Luke: Let me know how I can help.
Luke: That last part was quite the prediction because that rather uncontroversial post where she just expresses general compassion for trans people set right wing internet on fire, leading even to Elon Musk.
Luke: Elon Musk himself, after refusing to publicly confirm that Ashley's kid was his,
Luke: accusing her of planning to trans their child at one or two years old.
Luke: And then he said he was filing for full custody.
Luke: I'm going to get the kid.
Luke: Elon pushed a narrative to his 240 million ex-followers that Ashley St.
Luke: Clair was a threat to their child and she should have the kid taken away.
Luke: After, again, previously not even being willing to publicly confirm the validity of his paternity.
Luke: And like the controversy humper that he is, Benny Johnson thoughtlessly jumped onto the bandwagon and stoked the same narrative.
Speaker 3: It's sick.
Speaker 3: It's crazy.
Speaker 3: And it's wrong.
Speaker 3: Period.
Speaker 3: Just is.
Speaker 3: And so, yeah.
Speaker 3: The only thing that you can hope in this scenario is that the parent goes, the child goes to the sane parent that does.
Speaker 3: and believe in this type of gender fluidity.
Speaker 3: And butchery, I'm sure, is child mutilation.
Luke: So in response to that, Benny Johnson and Elon Musk sending swarms of their followers to harass and threaten Ashley St.
Luke: Clair, she said, enough is enough.
Luke: And that's when I flew across the country to find out the dirty deets of the right-wing media corrupt machine that she witnessed firsthand through the story of Benny Johnson.
Luke: Here it is.
Luke: This is Investigating Benny Johnson.
Luke: All this started with you posting a video responding to something Benny had talked about in relation to you and saying that you had known for a long time details about him and that you were ready to come forward with them.
Luke: Explain for the audience why you're speaking out against him now.
Ashley St. Clair: Why now is because Benny decided to tell everyone that I should lose my child, that I'm not a fit mother, and that my child should be taken away from me.
Ashley St. Clair: Benny, I've always had a disdain for, but that certainly accelerated it.
Luke: You worked for Benny Johnson.
Ashley St. Clair: I did, for a long time.
Luke: Explain your experience working for him.
Ashley St. Clair: Awful.
Ashley St. Clair: It was, I've never been treated that way in a work environment.
Ashley St. Clair: He was, and I found out very quickly that I wasn't alone in my experience with Benny Johnson and his erratic, abusive behavior many times as soon as I started.
Ashley St. Clair: working for Benny's company, it was right away a shitshow, abusive, being screamed at, yelled at, degraded.
Ashley St. Clair: There was one instance in which he was not happy about a script for a shoot,
Ashley St. Clair: and I don't, I didn't write the scripts, but I was the one that was most accessible to him, so he called me screaming, calling me profanities, calling me a bitch, calling me stupid,
Ashley St. Clair: and saying that this was literal cancer and that I owed an apology to him and his wife and his newborn daughter that this was such a mess.
Luke: What kind of conversations have you had with other employees of his about this behavior?
Ashley St. Clair: The same behavior.
Ashley St. Clair: It was, I feel like most of us at that company were kind of trauma bonded by one, the neurotic nature of the company as a whole, but also the abuse of Benny.
Ashley St. Clair: He was constantly doing this and
Ashley St. Clair: screaming at people and saying that it wasn't up to par.
Ashley St. Clair: Meanwhile, these employees are not being paid for the work that they're doing for Benny.
Luke: In our previous discussions, you laid out that there seems to be a pattern of him ripping off people.
Luke: Speak to that.
Ashley St. Clair: So Benny has built his entire brand
Ashley St. Clair: off of the backs of other people.
Ashley St. Clair: Nothing about Benny Johnson is independent.
Ashley St. Clair: Whether it was siphoning cash from Turning Point, a 501c3, their charity work is building Benny Johnson, or whether it was Arsenal Media Group, where he co-founded this company and had all of these employees,
Ashley St. Clair: many of which, most of which were not being paid properly on time, were in these abusive working conditions, and he used this and funneled this cash to build the independent journalist that is Benny Johnson.
Luke: The quote-unquote godfather of conservative media.
Ashley St. Clair: I really cannot emphasize enough how bad these conditions were that people would call out.
Ashley St. Clair: They would be suffering from anxiety, depression.
Ashley St. Clair: I have the text where I'm
Ashley St. Clair: texting my boyfriend at the time when I was working there saying, I can't do this.
Ashley St. Clair: I'm hyperventilating.
Ashley St. Clair: I'm having panic attacks.
Ashley St. Clair: I don't want to talk to Benny.
Ashley St. Clair: I have to get on a call with Benny again.
Ashley St. Clair: And this was prolific throughout the entire company.
Luke: You said previously, I just want to get this clearly.
Luke: You remember specifically in an angry phone call him calling you a bitch?
Ashley St. Clair: Yes.
Ashley St. Clair: What's also important about Arsenal is that while so many employees were not getting paid and they couldn't pay their medical bills, they couldn't feed their families, they were worried about paying rent,
Ashley St. Clair: Benny always made sure that the people working on his social media were paid.
Ashley St. Clair: Quite often there would be times that no one else at this company received their money, but Benny received his Facebook money and Benny had his staff paid.
Luke: To this day, are there former employees who are owed significant money?
Ashley St. Clair: Yes.
Luke: So Benny is making agreements to pay people.
Luke: This isn't like, oh, we wish you would pay me more.
Luke: He made agreements to pay people a certain amount.
Luke: Didn't, but made sure that his operation was funded.
Ashley St. Clair: Yes.
Ashley St. Clair: These people were given salaries, employment opportunities at the company that he co-founded and was running around as a tyrant through, and he did not care.
Ashley St. Clair: That anyone was not being paid.
Ashley St. Clair: Instead, he was buying houses, moving, drinking expensive whiskey.
Ashley St. Clair: having his team paid while everyone else was worried about how they were going to afford groceries.
Luke: Explain your experience with Madison Cawthorn and then how Benny and the Arsenal leadership responded.
Ashley St. Clair: So I met Madison Cawthorn through my work at Arsenal.
Ashley St. Clair: He was a client of ours and on one of the shoots I was put as the lead on the shoot and then I was told that I need to have a meeting with Madison afterwards about his campaign, his messaging.
Ashley St. Clair: And after the shoot I'm in the car with Madison.
Ashley St. Clair: I'm sitting to the far side, Madison gets in the middle and one of the people from his staff is on the other side.
Ashley St. Clair: And as soon as we get in the car, Madison like leans over and whispers in my ear and says, just so you know, I have no control over my obliques.
Ashley St. Clair: And every time the car turns, Madison's hand just so happens to land several times on my upper, upper thigh.
Ashley St. Clair: Like it was one wrong move and something was in me at this point.
Ashley St. Clair: And so I just brush it off and we go to this lunch that we're supposed to talk about his campaign.
Ashley St. Clair: And right away he starts talking about blowjobs.
Ashley St. Clair: And, you know, if I would give my boyfriend a blowjob if he was on death row and all of this crazy stuff.
Ashley St. Clair: And I did tell.
Ashley St. Clair: the leadership at the company and said I didn't want to be alone on these shoots with Madison anymore and that we shouldn't have any female staffers
Ashley St. Clair: alone on these shoots with Madison and they kept placing females alone on shoots with Madison and they also experienced sexual harassment from Madison and I told Benny directly years later I said this is who Madison is and
Ashley St. Clair: Benny was aware of it.
Ashley St. Clair: He had at one point we had scripted Madison to be in a locker room for a shoot and Benny explicitly said given his past we shouldn't put him in a locker room.
Ashley St. Clair: So very intentionally laundering the image of someone he knows is a sexual predator.
Luke: You told him explicitly in text?
Ashley St. Clair: Yes.
Luke: On the record?
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Luke: And to this day, does Vinny associate with Madison?
Ashley St. Clair: Yes.
Ashley St. Clair: I think it was a few weeks ago he did.
Luke: Explain for me one of the things we walked through is the potentially illegal, definitely immoral,
Luke: and definitely not transparent, funneling of money in between different entities associated with Benny, who was part of, but also much bigger operations.
Luke: Walk through that for the audience.
Ashley St. Clair: So there was a lot of different improprieties financially within this company that Benny had co-founded, one of which is as it relates to our for-profit entity, the 501c3 and a 501c4
Ashley St. Clair: from Turning Point, which was Turning Point PAC.
Ashley St. Clair: And when you were
Ashley St. Clair: with a PAC, you're not supposed to also be simultaneously working with the candidates, of which we were.
Ashley St. Clair: We were warned by legal that we had to firewall certain employees off.
Ashley St. Clair: They could not simultaneously work on the PAC side of things if they had worked with the candidates, but we definitely did.
Luke: And name the specific entities you're talking about.
Ashley St. Clair: Turning Point PAC and then the individual campaigns of these candidates that Turning Point PAC had us doing things for.
Luke: And so your company, Arsenal, was working simultaneously with the PAC and with the campaign directly, which your lawyers...
Ashley St. Clair: And Turning Point.
Luke: And Turning Point, your lawyers specifically warned against?
Ashley St. Clair: Yes.
Ashley St. Clair: The thing about Benny too is he, most people don't understand how much money that he's making from this fear mongering, from this promotion of violence, from his abusive behavior.
Ashley St. Clair: This man's making six figures a month on Facebook.
Ashley St. Clair: He is?
Ashley St. Clair: Yes, on Facebook, on YouTube.
Ashley St. Clair: The monetization flowing through these independent journalists is astronomical.
Luke: And do you remember having a conversation with him where he spoke to trying to sort of milk events that outward facing are all about supporting the cause, but behind the scenes was for the money?
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, they quite explicitly said that this is for the content.
Ashley St. Clair: Hey guys, we're missing opportunities to monetize Trump speeches.
Ashley St. Clair: They very much view everything within MAGA, these soundbites, these events, these speeches, and they promote them and they enable them because it makes them money.
Ashley St. Clair: If Trump has a good soundbite and they post it on their page, they're making this six figures a month on Facebook.
Ashley St. Clair: So they have no incentive structure to tone down the rhetoric or make this stop or have people be more...
Ashley St. Clair: More tactful, to be more civil.
Ashley St. Clair: It's all money for them.
Luke: It's going to be easy, I think, for supporters of Benny or people who are still sort of loyal to MAGA to brush off any of what you're saying as, oh, maybe a bitter former employee, maybe she's just a liberal trying to take down a MAGA guy.
Luke: What would you say to someone with that response?
Ashley St. Clair: If I was bitter, I would have said something a long time ago.
Ashley St. Clair: I would have said it as soon as I left that company.
Ashley St. Clair: And I also don't think it's wrong to be angry.
Ashley St. Clair: I'm really tired of women who are angry being called bitter or scorned when these men run around being angry at nothing all day.
Ashley St. Clair: And I'm angry with cause.
Ashley St. Clair: I am angry that this happened to me, that I had crimes happen to me within my workplace, that other employees, I had to listen to them talk about how they were abused in the workplace.
Ashley St. Clair: And then for this man to go and say, I should lose my child after everything.
Ashley St. Clair: Everything that me and these other employees went through and we said nothing, we were silent.
Ashley St. Clair: And now you say you hop on the train for a couple bucks to say someone that you know is a good mother should lose her child.
Luke: Why should a follower who likes his content, who agrees with his views, care?
Ashley St. Clair: Because you're being manipulated.
Ashley St. Clair: They do not care about you.
Ashley St. Clair: They do not care about the things coming out of their mouth.
Ashley St. Clair: It is all content for them.
Ashley St. Clair: It is designed to rile you up.
Ashley St. Clair: They love when there is something that is explosive or this fiery rhetoric because it makes them money.
Ashley St. Clair: They don't believe any of this.
Ashley St. Clair: While they are telling you that they're just...
Ashley St. Clair: down-to-earth patriots, they're hitting the four seasons and having an old-fashioned with McAllen that's worth more than their rent, you know?
Ashley St. Clair: And so at a time when people are struggling to have people like Benny begging for, you know, these memberships and these Q&As and, you know, give me money so you can support honest, independent journalism,
Ashley St. Clair: that is despicable to me.
Luke: And you say this not speculatively from the sidelines, but based on your experiences.
Ashley St. Clair: Yes.
Luke: That he doesn't believe much of what he says.
Ashley St. Clair: No.
Luke: You spent a lot of time, some of the audience won't know this, in the right-wing media space, yourself, as we're talking about working for these companies, going to these events, going to the post.
Luke: convention, parties, what would a random person just listening to this not know about the right-wing media ecosystem?
Ashley St. Clair: I mean, there's so much that they wouldn't know, but first and foremost, all of these events are just social party events for them.
Ashley St. Clair: There's nothing honest going on.
Ashley St. Clair: It's all networking to see who can get paid by who, and they need to get into these paid networks and these group chats, which they can climb up the ladder.
Ashley St. Clair: It's all a business to them.
Ashley St. Clair: Everyone's being paid, everyone's coordinated, and they're all involved in the most debaucherous behavior imaginable, which is fine.
Ashley St. Clair: However, this is a party that is promoting themselves as these moral grandstanders and that the left and the other people are the party of moral degeneracy when
Ashley St. Clair: I've seen more degenerate behavior from them than
Ashley St. Clair: you know, a random New York party scene.
Luke: I know exactly what you mean.
Luke: To each their own in a sense, but there is so clearly an effort from, Benny Johnson is one example, but a lot of these figures to
Luke: portray themselves as the epitome of morality and a very strict, specific set of guidelines and look, here's my perfect family and all this.
Luke: So then what do you mean by debauchery?
Ashley St. Clair: The sex, the drugs, the drinking, the money coming through from places that they need.
Ashley St. Clair: No, they shouldn't be getting money.
Ashley St. Clair: The paid opinions, all of this stuff is so prolific throughout MAGA and throughout this influencer ecosystem that they've created.
Ashley St. Clair: And it's very much like they're all wearing costumes because for someone like Benny, who's doing
Ashley St. Clair: a press conference with Pam Bondi saying his life is at risk and he's at so much risk, but is posting photos of his children and his family every other day,
Ashley St. Clair: that doesn't add up because you're not going to find photos of my children online because I am scared of what people will do.
Ashley St. Clair: That is not someone who's genuinely fearful for their family.
Luke: I wanted to ask you about that.
Luke: After a bunch of, it wasn't just Benny Johnson, obviously we're focusing on him here, but a bunch of different
Luke: famous figures and right-wing media personalities honed in after you expressed
Luke: the most uncontroversial sympathy for trans people on the idea that you were going to trans your one-year-old or something terrible was going on and then calling for your kid to be taken away from you.
Luke: Literally.
Luke: Just without any personal experience, publicly calling for that.
Luke: What was the reaction you saw?
Luke: What was the targeting of you after that?
Ashley St. Clair: It was horrific.
Ashley St. Clair: It was violent.
Ashley St. Clair: I had people saying they were going to come take my baby with a gun.
Ashley St. Clair: I had people posting images of me being burned at the stake and people running away with my child.
Ashley St. Clair: I had videos from people like Benny Johnson saying I should lose my child.
Ashley St. Clair: If you read those comments, it's like, save the baby, save her, she shouldn't have her child.
Ashley St. Clair: And they...
Ashley St. Clair: They put my family in a lot of danger.
Luke: And you know from experience that this wasn't because Benny, to use him as an example, was genuinely concerned for your kid.
Ashley St. Clair: No.
Luke: But because it would get some clicks and drive some outrage.
Ashley St. Clair: He has my phone number.
Ashley St. Clair: They all do.
Luke: So you mentioned the attempts in these networking events for people to find the money and let it flow to them.
Luke: One of the things that is just jarring is sometimes you'll see some news break and then like 8, 10, 12 different prominent right-wing accounts will post.
Luke: If not exactly word for word, almost word for word, the exact same posts.
Luke: What's going on behind the scenes that causes that?
Ashley St. Clair: Several things.
Ashley St. Clair: So there's a few different ways that this happens, one of which is the paid campaigns, and they are quite literally given a script or copy to post with their audience.
Ashley St. Clair: And because of the current FAC rules and regulations, they do not have to disclose that they are paid for these.
Ashley St. Clair: So you will never know that they're paid.
Ashley St. Clair: There's no obligation to disclose that they're paid for this stuff.
Ashley St. Clair: And then there's group chats with members of the Trump administration and the biggest right-wing influencers in which they quite literally coordinate the messaging for big news saying, hey, here's how we respond to X.
Ashley St. Clair: XYZ, here's the talking points, and they all go out in lockstep.
Ashley St. Clair: And one of these is actually that I was in was called Fight, Fight, Fight after the assassination attempt on Trump in Butler.
Ashley St. Clair: And it is people like James Blair, top mega influencers, the official Trump war room, all of these people are within these group chats and being told exactly what to say.
Ashley St. Clair: During the campaign, they also had campaign calls with influencers such as myself in which they said, hey, here's how we want to respond to things.
Ashley St. Clair: Here's the messaging that we're going to stay on.
Ashley St. Clair: Good work, soldiers.
Luke: Was there ever anyone expressing behind the scenes, ah, this feels a little bit weird?
Ashley St. Clair: Not really.
Luke: And then who's this, if there's paid campaigns, who is paying for those campaigns?
Ashley St. Clair: Everyone and anyone.
Ashley St. Clair: And what's astonishing is some of these funding methods are hidden through various different companies or consulting firms.
Ashley St. Clair: So you really don't know where a lot of the money is coming from.
Ashley St. Clair: And these also have paid trips to Israel, paid trips to Russia.
Ashley St. Clair: There's Qatari money flowing in and out.
Ashley St. Clair: So much Qatari money in Republican politics that...
Ashley St. Clair: Just you'll never find because it's laundered.
Luke: And how aware do you think the people accepting, I'm remembering right now the scandal about tenant media and Russian money ultimately being the source of
Luke: funding figures like Benny Johnson and others.
Luke: And the response from them, which I was willing to believe, was, well, we didn't know where the money was coming from.
Luke: We just knew somebody wanted to give it to us.
Luke: Is it mostly that, like, oh, I don't really want to know, or is there an awareness that it could be questionable sources?
Ashley St. Clair: Some of it, and then the other part is they're like over-pathologizing it to say, oh, well, there's not a problem with it.
Ashley St. Clair: But what was astonishing about the Tenet Media scandal with Benny, Benny Johnson and other top Republican figureheads receiving so much money from Russia.
Ashley St. Clair: Their response was, we were victims, like you said, we didn't know.
Ashley St. Clair: They also said that they were never given talking points, they never changed their material, and that to me is where everyone should go,
Ashley St. Clair: you didn't think it was weird that Russia liked your shit so much that you didn't have to change a thing?
Ashley St. Clair: Just keep doing what you're doing and Russia would like to pay you?
Ashley St. Clair: There was no introspection from Benny or anyone consuming his content.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, hey, why does Russia think what I'm doing is awesome?
Ashley St. Clair: Why does a foreign adversary of the United States like what I'm saying so much?
Ashley St. Clair: Nothing?
Luke: I will have angry mobs if I don't ask this next question as little as I want to.
Luke: Has Penny Johnson had sexual contact with men?
Ashley St. Clair: The amount of people who have confirmed to me personally
Ashley St. Clair: about his experiences with men is astonishing.
Ashley St. Clair: This is, at this point, it's an open secret.
Ashley St. Clair: And why haven't you sued Milo, Benny?
Luke: What a conversation.
Luke: And we actually delayed releasing this so we could have time to independently verify the claims that she made.
Luke: We went through screenshots on her phone, text messages, contacted other former employees.
Luke: And then on that last point, obviously, that's the least important part.
Luke: Are you gay or bi?
Luke: But I think the reason it becomes relevant with these figures in particular.
Luke: It's because people are just sick of the hatred these figures, like Benny Johnson, constantly stoke towards other people's identities and lifestyles when they themselves are so obviously not who they say they are.
Luke: I referenced more former employees of Benny's.
Luke: We contacted others beyond Ashley, and it really was disturbing to see how afraid they were of Benny going after them if they spoke up.
Luke: It's why I admire so much Ashley's willingness to just lay it all out there.
Luke: When not only Benny, but the richest man on the planet, Elon, has already demonstrated and is currently demonstrating a willingness to attack and go after legally, send followers to harass her.
Luke: It took courage to do what Ashley did there.
Luke: We talked to...
Luke: As an example, one former employee who described Benny as dangerous and psychotic, but wasn't willing to go on the record or do an interview himself.
Luke: out of fear of reprisal.
Luke: We need our media figures to be rational, good faith thinkers who care about the truth and aren't just chasing the next paycheck.
Luke: Too many today across the political spectrum, but especially in right-wing media, are just desperate for fame and money.
Luke: And much like Benny Johnson will screw over any amount of people, lie as much as necessary and sacrifice every principle for it.