Ashley St. Clair: It's not just me though, like all of his exes say the same thing.
Ashley St. Clair: We have like, we've unionized, we have a group chat.
Ashley St. Clair: I've never had so many exes in a group chat and I was in a harem.
Ashley St. Clair: So like, and they all have the same story, but I was out of town and then I come back and there's a face mask in our shared bathroom, which was weird because I had already moved to the guest room because he was annoying the shit out of me.
Ashley St. Clair: And I'm like, whose face mask is this?
Ashley St. Clair: And he's like, oh, I thought it was yours.
Ashley St. Clair: I would like, I would never use something that cheap who was here.
Ashley St. Clair: And he's like, it was Anna, but you know, she was just staying here because she's moving to the district to carpet bag because she was living, I think, in Washington at the time.
Hasan Piker: What the fuck?
Hasan Piker: Wait.
Ashley St. Clair: And like, she will call him in the middle of the night being like, oh, look at this guy.
Ashley St. Clair: Look at this star.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, f***ing weird.
Speaker 3: Dark woke.
Speaker 4: Dark woke.
Speaker 3: It's a really big deal.
Speaker 3: Anyway, Ash Sinclair, thank you so much for coming on.
Speaker 3: It seems strange when I start the conversation by saying, like, oh, this is Elon Musk's baby mama.
Speaker 4: Yeah.
Speaker 3: I know.
Speaker 3: You're more than that.
Speaker 3: You are also a right-wing reactionary conservative influencer.
Speaker 4: No, not anymore.
Speaker 3: You used to be.
Speaker 4: Only one of those things is still true.
Speaker 3: And then you went woke.
Speaker 3: Dark woke.
Speaker 3: You went dark woke.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Speaker 3: And you've been doing the tour.
Speaker 3: You've been doing the rounds.
Speaker 3: And I was like, and I've seen some of the...
Ashley St. Clair: I wish people would wait to reach out to me, though, because they're going to think I'm a plant.
Ashley St. Clair: Because they're all reaching out at the same time.
Speaker 3: Well, the reason why I reached out was because I've seen some of the things you've said about, like, your past...
Speaker 3: Opinions and the things that you believed and how you've changed.
Speaker 3: So I wanted to explore that with you.
Speaker 3: And then also I wanted to obviously ask you about the piping hot conservative tea.
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, I got it.
Ashley St. Clair: I got all of it.
Speaker 3: Because you've been, yeah, you were in this movement for a while.
Speaker 3: For those of you who don't know, I mean, you want to explain your background?
Speaker 3: And everything else?
Speaker 3: Because there probably are some people who are not aware.
Ashley St. Clair: So I got involved in right-wing politics around 18, 19 on my college campus.
Ashley St. Clair: I was involved in like a turning point chapter.
Ashley St. Clair: And it was very quickly that I was tweeting.
Ashley St. Clair: And all of a sudden, I'm driving Charlie Kirk to the airport.
Ashley St. Clair: And I'm a special guest at the Young Women's Leadership Conference.
Speaker 3: Okay, that's...
Speaker 3: Wait, let's start there, actually.
Speaker 3: Because this is fascinating for me.
Speaker 3: I've known Charlie Kirk, obviously, for many years.
Speaker 3: I debated him at Politicon twice.
Speaker 3: And I was fascinated with his journey because they basically plucked him.
Speaker 3: He wrote one, I think, like one high school paper.
Speaker 3: For his high school newspaper, he wrote an article about how a black woman, he speculated a black woman had taken his spot at West Point Academy.
Ashley St. Clair: What?
Ashley St. Clair: I didn't know this.
Speaker 3: Yeah, so.
Speaker 3: Oh, here, I'll give you some deep Charlie Kirk lore.
Speaker 3: We carry the flame here on the broadcast.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah, Charlie Kirk.
Speaker 3: Basically what happened is he wrote like some kind of reactionary article in his high school newspaper and then instantly it was on Breitbart and then after it was on Breitbart he was immediately on Fox News.
Ashley St. Clair: That's how it goes.
Speaker 3: Yeah and you had I guess a similar experience as well so let's start there.
Speaker 3: So you start tweeting and you're like I...
Speaker 3: Hate how woke society is.
Ashley St. Clair: I'm like, poor people be like, feel the burn.
Speaker 3: Okay.
Ashley St. Clair: Just stupid reactionary stuff.
Ashley St. Clair: And at first I didn't even have my photo on there.
Ashley St. Clair: And then I was like, wait a second, this will fly.
Ashley St. Clair: And so then I uploaded my photo.
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, so you were like, I'm just like, ain't on shit posting.
Speaker 3: Ah, okay.
Ashley St. Clair: And then once I uploaded the photo and started going live on Periscope, it was over.
Ashley St. Clair: Mike Cernovic and Jack Posobiec found me.
Ashley St. Clair: Okay.
Ashley St. Clair: It was over.
Speaker 3: So what, like, how, let's go even further beyond that, though.
Speaker 3: Let's start at the beginning.
Speaker 3: Like, how did you become right-wing?
Ashley St. Clair: So right before I started my freshman year of college,
Ashley St. Clair: Trump had a rally on my campus, like my new campus.
Ashley St. Clair: So if you look in my photos, it'll just show a Trump rally that I'm at and right next to Trump.
Ashley St. Clair: And then I start college.
Ashley St. Clair: And then I'm at Young Americans for Liberty and the turning point.
Ashley St. Clair: And that was it.
Speaker 3: But how did you like develop your worldview?
Speaker 3: Like what was it?
Speaker 3: Were you just like.
Ashley St. Clair: I didn't have one.
Ashley St. Clair: I was just very impressionable.
Ashley St. Clair: And I'm.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, this seems so cool.
Speaker 3: So in your mind, you were like, it was more so, I want to be a part of the in-group, and maybe it was like the cool frat guys or whatever, and they were all like, I guess, I don't know, kind of right-wing?
Speaker 3: Sort of.
Ashley St. Clair: I also liked, I went for philosophy, so I liked being like the contrarian token conservative in the philosophy class.
Speaker 3: Classic.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: But I didn't know what I was talking about.
Ashley St. Clair: I was talking about health care and I was on my dad's plan.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Speaker 3: Okay.
Speaker 3: So you start your ideological journey just wanting to debate people.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Speaker 3: And wanting to be a contrarian.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Speaker 3: That makes sense.
Ashley St. Clair: And wanting some sort of validation because once you get in that, you have a club.
Ashley St. Clair: My only college clubs were political.
Ashley St. Clair: So.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: And I was homeschooled in high school.
Ashley St. Clair: So.
Speaker 3: Oh.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: Doesn't that make a lot more sense?
Speaker 3: Okay.
Speaker 3: That makes so much more sense.
Speaker 3: Why didn't you start there?
Speaker 3: You should have started there.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Speaker 3: That's like most of the story.
Ashley St. Clair: And we were, people think I'm joking, but I'm like, when I was homeschooled in high school, we were in a little town in Montana where my only friend was a Mennonite lumberjack.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, that was it.
Ashley St. Clair: It was a town of, like, 250 people.
Ashley St. Clair: So then I go to college, and I'm like, oh, I'm so cool.
Ashley St. Clair: And, like, they really like what I'm saying.
Speaker 3: You're Jewish.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Speaker 3: You're a Jew in Montana.
Ashley St. Clair: Jewish Italian, so they thought we were like Whitbrow.
Speaker 3: Jewish Italian.
Speaker 3: You're Jewish.
Speaker 3: So that's, I don't even know which is worse, Catholic or Jewish from the perspective of like the average Montana person.
Ashley St. Clair: Yes.
Ashley St. Clair: One of our neighbors was this like 80 year old dude on oxygen who was like arguing about black people all day.
Ashley St. Clair: And I was like,
Ashley St. Clair: That's really racist, Jack, but...
Speaker 3: Okay.
Ashley St. Clair: It was very...
Ashley St. Clair: Then I go to college, I'm like, ooh, look at all these cool friends.
Speaker 3: So that's, I mean, that makes sense.
Speaker 3: Now this is making a lot more, everything is clicking into place now.
Speaker 3: Now that you said you're homeschooled from Montana and you go to college, which college did you go to?
Ashley St. Clair: University of Colorado in Colorado Springs.
Ashley St. Clair: Okay.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Speaker 3: All right.
Speaker 3: So you went to University of Colorado.
Speaker 3: Everyone's woke around you all of a sudden.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah, I felt like I was being like swarmed.
Speaker 3: Okay.
Ashley St. Clair: Like I must fight back.
Speaker 3: Yeah, so you felt like they were trying to indoctrinate you.
Ashley St. Clair: Yes, because Charlie Kirk said to watch your professors.
Ashley St. Clair: I was like always looking for that Professor Watchlist content.
Speaker 3: That's crazy.
Speaker 3: I didn't know that anyone...
Ashley St. Clair: It was like content.
Speaker 3: You were a whole ass nerd.
Speaker 3: That's crazy.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Speaker 3: All of the Young Americans for Freedom guys are always so...
Speaker 3: Nerdy, I feel like.
Ashley St. Clair: Well, I grew up with brothers, too, so I just played video games.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, I would do LAN parties, like LAN parties, playing Age of Empires till, like, 2 a.m.
Ashley St. Clair: So then I go to college, I'm like, oh, I'm cool, but also...
Speaker 3: You're the only girl in the YAF meetups.
Ashley St. Clair: 100%.
Speaker 3: Were they all trying to...
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: But there was all these rumors, too.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, I learned a new person I slept with every day.
Ashley St. Clair: So I was like, this sucks.
Ashley St. Clair: But also.
Speaker 3: Well, we'll get back to that in a second.
Speaker 3: Because I feel like that is now, I mean, not much has changed, I feel like, from Young Americans for Freedom than to the conservative media ecosystem.
Speaker 3: Because they do all.
Speaker 3: Oh, yeah.
Speaker 3: So we'll get to that tea.
Speaker 3: We'll get to that tea in a second.
Speaker 3: But so you.
Speaker 3: You get out of college, you're posting, you're on Periscope.
Ashley St. Clair: I drop out of college.
Speaker 3: You dropped out of college.
Ashley St. Clair: Dropped out.
Speaker 3: For the influencer route.
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, yeah, because I started dating.
Speaker 3: Who'd you start dating?
Ashley St. Clair: Do you know who DC Drano is?
Speaker 3: Oh my God.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: And so he was like, he was like mid thirties and I was 20.
Ashley St. Clair: I couldn't even order a legal drink yet.
Ashley St. Clair: I drop out of school and a month into dating, he moves me into his bunk ass Tampa apartment.
Speaker 3: Uh-huh.
Speaker 3: Okay.
Speaker 3: And you were like, we're living.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, we're from my mother's house.
Speaker 3: We're living the high life.
Speaker 3: DC Drano is one of the.
Ashley St. Clair: Binder boy.
Speaker 3: Yeah, one of the binder guys.
Speaker 3: Yes.
Speaker 3: Epstein binder.
Speaker 3: Wow, he's hot.
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, no, stop.
Speaker 3: He's sexy.
Ashley St. Clair: Stop it.
Speaker 3: Okay, so you were dating...
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah, nobody cared when I was dating an ugly broke man.
Speaker 3: Okay, so this is DC Drano.
Speaker 3: Try that in a small town.
Ashley St. Clair: But he's like, he also cosplays.
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, he does?
Ashley St. Clair: He has hands that are softer than mine, and then he will, like, wear this costume.
Ashley St. Clair: He will purposely leave mud on his truck and, like, scream.
Ashley St. Clair: He's like, people expect Drano to have mud on his truck.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, just batshit.
Ashley St. Clair: But so then he tells me, he like molds me.
Ashley St. Clair: I'm like this perfect little 20-year-old influencer.
Ashley St. Clair: He's like, here's what you post.
Ashley St. Clair: Here's what you hold on the signs.
Ashley St. Clair: Like he's telling me what to write on the sign outside of the ICE detention center.
Speaker 3: Okay, so do any of these guys like...
Speaker 3: So you were...
Speaker 3: Some ways.
Speaker 3: I mean, I don't mean like groomed in like the legitimate way, but you were like groomed in the OG way to be this like conservative.
Ashley St. Clair: Because I was so insecure and so pick me that I was like, absolutely.
Ashley St. Clair: I will.
Ashley St. Clair: Yes.
Ashley St. Clair: Yes, sir.
Speaker 3: So they so they turn you into this this this media demon.
Speaker 3: But what I don't understand is like, where are the true believers?
Speaker 3: From my perspective, I always feel like.
Ashley St. Clair: On Facebook and they're your grandma and grandpa.
Speaker 3: Yeah, but I feel like a lot of the younger crop of conservative influencers, they're very clearly angling for some kind of media opportunity.
Speaker 3: They're not real.
Speaker 3: They're not actually genuinely like, I read Rothbard, I'm a huge libertarian.
Speaker 3: They don't read at all.
Ashley St. Clair: Hassan, they don't read at all.
Speaker 3: Well, I mean, I know that.
Ashley St. Clair: No, when you talk to them about the books behind them on their shelves, none of them read them.
Ashley St. Clair: They can't tell you anything about the books behind them on their shelves.
Speaker 3: So it's just LARP.
Speaker 3: They're just fed talking points, and they're just repeating those talking points.
Ashley St. Clair: And putting mud on their trucks.
Speaker 3: I would go so far as to say, and I hate to, I mean, this is not even giving him credit at all, but
Speaker 3: I think that's part of the reason why Nick Fuentes has so much appeal is because he can demonstrate basic literacy and competence and a more sophisticated understanding.
Speaker 3: He has a worldview.
Speaker 3: I mean, he's a heinous little neo-Nazi creature, but it is obvious that he comes from a background where he has more of a...
Speaker 3: a genuine interest in this kind of thing.
Ashley St. Clair: He reads more than most of the people on Fox News.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Speaker 3: So I think that's probably part of the appeal, even though I found out that his audience is mostly older.
Speaker 3: I thought it was like a lot younger, but turns out a lot of- Are they really?
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: I thought all of his, there was one time when a bunch of the Grapers got banned on Twitter and they were coming to me for help.
Ashley St. Clair: And one of them calls me and he has like this European accent.
Ashley St. Clair: I was like, wait, are you even-
Ashley St. Clair: American.
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, no, no, no.
Ashley St. Clair: No, but thank you so much for helping me.
Ashley St. Clair: Actually, I was like, what's up?
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah, no, so on America first and his profile picture was like AF.
Speaker 3: Yeah, no, no, no.
Speaker 3: They're there.
Speaker 3: Okay, so this is actually a really interesting thing that I didn't know was going on either.
Speaker 3: There's another guy on this platform called Asmongold.
Speaker 3: I don't know if you're familiar with him at all.
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, he...
Speaker 3: Yeah, he's...
Speaker 3: So he is like...
Ashley St. Clair: He like makes me shiver.
Speaker 3: Yeah, he's like...
Ashley St. Clair: You just know he smells.
Speaker 3: Bizarro me in every way, including, you know, hygiene and dietary habits.
Speaker 3: But he...
Speaker 3: His audience is mostly European.
Speaker 3: And they all, they love LARPing as MAGA.
Speaker 3: They love, like, that's the number one thing.
Ashley St. Clair: They probably, like, identify with his lack of orthodontics.
Speaker 3: Well, that might be part of it.
Speaker 3: But, like, it's fascinating to me because there are, because on the internet, like, you know, not to sound like Mark Levin, but, like, there are a lot of people that are not.
Speaker 3: In America that are talking about American politics and present
Speaker 3: themselves as Americans, sure, there's like, you know.
Ashley St. Clair: Why is that Mark Levin, though?
Ashley St. Clair: That's just.
Speaker 3: Because he always says the third world is watching Tucker Carlson.
Speaker 3: Because he says, like, Tucker Carlson's audience is not American, which, I mean, could possibly be the case.
Speaker 3: I know a lot of WhatsApp onks that love Tucker Carlson.
Speaker 3: Like, let's be real.
Ashley St. Clair: The WhatsApp onks do love him.
Speaker 3: Yeah, like, Bangladeshi WhatsApp onks are just sharing his videos all the time.
Speaker 3: But.
Speaker 3: But like on the other side of it, it's very fat.
Speaker 3: It's fascinating because like American pop is being consumed by everyone around the world and they're all LARPing as Americans.
Ashley St. Clair: Yes.
Speaker 3: So you have like the third world is positioned, which obviously I'm sympathetic to.
Speaker 3: And those guys are LARPing as Americans.
Speaker 3: And then but they're LARPing from, you know, all these different parts of the world.
Speaker 3: And then a shit ton of the MAGA movement on the Internet.
Speaker 3: And I don't mean just like bot accounts or accounts that like are very clearly doing propaganda.
Speaker 3: I mean like people's personal consumption in their own personal experience.
Speaker 3: Like you got a bunch of right wingers from like the Netherlands.
Ashley St. Clair: Yes.
Speaker 3: Who are like half the groipers.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Speaker 3: Who are dialed in on the, you know, Asmongold commentary who.
Speaker 3: We'll constantly talk about how like Europe is falling apart.
Ashley St. Clair: Yes, because
Ashley St. Clair: But that also makes it more, so that's why people, some people within the right-wing space, they like co-opting those populist movements.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: Because it's really, really easy, and those markets are all...
Ashley St. Clair: already dialed in.
Ashley St. Clair: They love consuming American politics.
Speaker 3: Yeah, everyone loves it.
Speaker 3: Everyone loves LARPing as an American, but it seems like they can't vote here because they're not even physically here.
Ashley St. Clair: Depends on who you ask, though.
Speaker 3: Yeah, so we'll get to that in a second as well.
Speaker 3: We'll get to that.
Speaker 3: But okay, so you're dating DC Drano.
Speaker 3: He's a stud.
Speaker 3: I mean, look at how handsome his, this three-piece suit.
Speaker 3: I mean, this is...
Ashley St. Clair: Binder boy.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Speaker 3: God damn.
Speaker 3: These guys.
Speaker 3: What a journey this was.
Ashley St. Clair: When I first started making TikToks about him, he called me for two hours crying.
Ashley St. Clair: He's like, please, you know what he said?
Ashley St. Clair: He said, please show me mercy, Ashley.
Ashley St. Clair: That's what he said.
Ashley St. Clair: Wait, really?
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: I was like, mercy, I made TikToks.
Speaker 3: Have you shown him mercy?
Ashley St. Clair: No.
Speaker 3: Okay.
Speaker 3: So these guys are all, would you say that, I mean, I feel like after a certain point, like through this evolution, they do start believing their own shit though, right?
Speaker 3: Like there's gotta be, or they're not like woke.
Ashley St. Clair: They've reached like a level of paranoia.
Ashley St. Clair: And like, there's something so weird.
Ashley St. Clair: Like most of these guys within MAGA were total losers in like high school and college.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, but it's like a common theme and it really, and it really sticks with them.
Ashley St. Clair: Like it really sticks with them.
Ashley St. Clair: Like that's what they talk about when they're sad at night.
Ashley St. Clair: And I don't know why it's a common theme.
Ashley St. Clair: But it's like this is their redemption now.
Ashley St. Clair: He's like, I'm cool.
Ashley St. Clair: Everyone loves straight up.
Speaker 3: But they're not.
Ashley St. Clair: No.
Speaker 3: And does that, do they recognize that?
Speaker 3: They must, right?
Speaker 3: Because I feel like this was.
Speaker 3: a big grievance for Donald Trump too.
Speaker 3: Like something that animates Donald Trump is the fact that he never got mass appeal or broad appeal from liberal intelligentsia.
Speaker 3: He grew up in New York.
Ashley St. Clair: Palm Beach didn't want him.
Ashley St. Clair: That's why he started Mar-a-Lago.
Ashley St. Clair: They're like, he's too weird and what?
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Speaker 3: And he's rude.
Speaker 3: He's a slumlord.
Speaker 3: He's boy trash.
Speaker 3: Yeah, he was nouveau riche.
Speaker 3: He was too gauche.
Speaker 3: He wasn't old money.
Speaker 3: So the New York elite never saw him as one of their own.
Speaker 3: And I think that's what a lot of that resentment, that's where a lot of this resentment comes from.
Speaker 3: And I feel like there's a different version of that within the conservative influence of the space.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah, now he's like, I'm going to rename everything after me.
Ashley St. Clair: You're never going to be able to not look at me.
Ashley St. Clair: I'm going to be on your bridges, at your airports.
Ashley St. Clair: I don't understand how the Republicans don't think that's crazy.
Ashley St. Clair: Because I get it.
Speaker 3: It's a cult.
Ashley St. Clair: They can say I'm coming from a place of spite or whatever, scorned woman.
Ashley St. Clair: But I don't know how they look at all of this and they don't think it's insane.
Ashley St. Clair: Objectively.
Speaker 3: I mean, the craziest thing is like...
Speaker 3: Republicans hate, at least if there's one consistent principle that Republicans are supposed to hate, it's like wasting taxpayer money, right?
Speaker 3: Yes.
Speaker 3: Small government.
Speaker 3: I hate when the government is stealing from me in the form of taxes.
Speaker 3: Donald Trump's $1.8 billion slush fund that he cultivated, he created.
Speaker 3: After basically becoming the president and then suing himself was
Speaker 3: Like, I mean, that's the clearest example of just like stealing money from the American taxpayer to pay whoever he wants with this like unaccountable entity.
Speaker 3: And if they don't even get mad at that, I don't know what they can get mad at.
Speaker 3: I mean, they're just cucked.
Speaker 3: I think they're unbelievably cucked.
Speaker 4: They have no spine.
Speaker 4: Nobody wants to stand up for anything.
Speaker 4: They don't want to lose their cushy positions.
Speaker 4: They don't want to lose their job in Congress.
Speaker 4: Yeah.
Speaker 3: I mean, but we see that with like, what's his face?
Speaker 3: Well, not Thomas Massey was consistent.
Speaker 3: So I do give him credit for that.
Speaker 3: But the other guy, Bill Cassidy, who, you know, just got ousted because Donald Trump wanted to punish him for.
Speaker 3: Trying to indict him for January 6th.
Speaker 4: I think Boebert was the only one who didn't lose her primary.
Speaker 4: Yeah.
Speaker 4: It was on the Epstein voted for the release of the Epstein.
Speaker 3: Well, Bill Cassidy wasn't even on the Epstein thing.
Speaker 3: It was an older grievance.
Speaker 3: It was the January 6th stuff, right?
Speaker 3: And he wanted to punish him.
Speaker 3: And then all of a sudden, the moment that he knows he's, you know, no longer, he doesn't have to worry about re-election, he comes out and actually votes on the war powers resolution.
Speaker 3: And it's like, so you knew that this was bad from the start and you're just a piece of shit.
Speaker 4: Isn't that shittier than just not doing anything at all?
Speaker 4: You're like, oh, I mean, I'm still happy that there's a spoiler in the Republican side, but it's just like very frustrating that these guys, when they don't have anything to lose, only then do they.
Speaker 3: Do they openly admit that this kind of this stuff is awful?
Ashley St. Clair: I don't know.
Ashley St. Clair: Having nothing to lose is a superpower, though.
Speaker 3: Well, on the Democratic Party side, unfortunately, it plays the exact opposite role.
Speaker 3: And that's why you have the likes of Jared Golden, I believe, who's who's constantly last name.
Ashley St. Clair: That's so cool.
Speaker 3: Yeah, he's he's the one who's constantly stopping.
Speaker 3: He's the lone vote usually that that allows the Republicans to to to not get punished in any way, shape or form, like in the War Powers Resolution.
Speaker 3: So like the Democrats and the Republicans work in this like inverse manner where the Democrats that have nothing to lose will always be the one spoiler vote that will go and caucus with the Republicans.
Speaker 3: And then the Republicans that are the, you know, Republicans with nothing to lose will be the spoilers for the Democrats.
Ashley St. Clair: Can we get my ex-boyfriend off screen?
Speaker 3: Oh, yeah, sure.
Speaker 3: Well, you know.
Ashley St. Clair: I was listening.
Speaker 3: We're going to move on to other ex-boyfriends in a second.
Ashley St. Clair: No.
Speaker 3: So.
Ashley St. Clair: Okay, wait.
Ashley St. Clair: You have to open my gift.
Speaker 3: Oh, yeah.
Speaker 3: You got me a gift?
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Speaker 3: Whereas, oh, it's right here.
Ashley St. Clair: There's pastries, too.
Ashley St. Clair: There's Greek pastries, like baklava, too.
Speaker 3: Oh, my God.
Ashley St. Clair: But it says Happy Father's Day.
Speaker 3: Thank you.
Speaker 3: You got me so much.
Speaker 3: They look so good.
Ashley St. Clair: It's a really good bakery.
Ashley St. Clair: Pie Bakery.
Ashley St. Clair: Shout out to Pie Bakery.
Speaker 3: Whoa.
Speaker 3: This is crazy.
Speaker 3: You're trying to fatten me up.
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, yeah.
Speaker 3: God damn.
Ashley St. Clair: I like them a little fat.
Speaker 3: Okay.
Speaker 3: True.
Speaker 3: Well, thank you so much.
Speaker 3: You're welcome.
Speaker 3: What else?
Speaker 3: What is this?
Speaker 5: This is a hoodie.
Speaker 3: You got me a hoodie?
Speaker 5: Yeah.
Speaker 3: Okay, I'm going to put this down here.
Speaker 3: Oh, God.
Speaker 3: What is going to be in this?
Speaker 3: This is going to be...
Speaker 3: Let's see.
Speaker 5: You ready?
Speaker 5: Are you ready, Chat?
Speaker 3: Oh, God.
Speaker 3: Oh, no.
Speaker 3: I'm not even going to see it first.
Speaker 3: Chat's going to see it before I do.
Ashley St. Clair: I've been sent by Benjamin Netanyahu to get his Twitter account banned.
Speaker 3: You're, this is.
Speaker 3: Oh my god.
Ashley St. Clair: Clip it.
Ashley St. Clair: Okay.
Speaker 3: That's crazy.
Ashley St. Clair: It's pretty comfy.
Speaker 3: I love it.
Speaker 3: Thank you so much.
Ashley St. Clair: It's comfy, even though you're not a hoodie guy anymore.
Speaker 3: No, I'm not.
Ashley St. Clair: What is with the...
Ashley St. Clair: I'm a suit guy now.
Ashley St. Clair: I mean, you look good, but...
Speaker 3: So, I keep getting clipped on Fox News, and I thought I would be more appealing to the grandmothers and the grandfathers that are watching if I'm in a suit while they clip me.
Speaker 3: And it's worked so far.
Ashley St. Clair: You're whitewashing yourself?
Speaker 3: Yes, I'm trying to.
Speaker 3: I'm trying to do that to the best of my ability.
Speaker 3: And it's been working, though, because I keep hearing from people that, like, their grandparents will be like, who is this Hasan guy I keep hearing about?
Speaker 3: What a handsome fellow he is.
Speaker 3: And it's like, it works.
Ashley St. Clair: You know, my mom, every time I do shows, she's like, oh, I love that person.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, oh, the left winger.
Ashley St. Clair: Even Kyle Kalinske.
Ashley St. Clair: What do you mean even?
Speaker 3: That's my goat.
Speaker 3: That's the dark wing.
Ashley St. Clair: He's a little vulgar, whatever.
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: And then I was like, oh, I'm going on Hasan's stream.
Ashley St. Clair: She goes.
Ashley St. Clair: That'll be fun.
Ashley St. Clair: She's like, that'll be fun.
Ashley St. Clair: But it's fine.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: Hi, Mom.
Speaker 3: Hi.
Ashley St. Clair: She's probably watching.
Ashley St. Clair: No, you're not allowed to say hi to my mom.
Ashley St. Clair: Don't talk to my mom.
Speaker 3: Wait, why not?
Ashley St. Clair: Because.
Ashley St. Clair: Okay, hi.
Speaker 3: Hi, Mama St.
Speaker 3: Clair.
Speaker 3: Is that what it is?
Speaker 3: I don't know.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: It confuses people.
Ashley St. Clair: They're like, oh, that's not a Jewish name.
Ashley St. Clair: I'm like, my dad is French.
Speaker 3: Okay.
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, you know what I found out afterwards, too, that you have beef with Suzanne Lambert.
Speaker 3: Yeah, I didn't.
Speaker 3: I don't really know her at all, but she's like, she doesn't like me.
Ashley St. Clair: I was so confused to hear that, though, because I didn't get that from talking to her.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, she didn't say, oh, yeah, I hate Hassan.
Ashley St. Clair: This is like a random.
Ashley St. Clair: He shocked his dog.
Speaker 3: Yeah, she was like the first to market on the liberal side to be like, this guy's a dog abuser.
Speaker 3: He sucks.
Speaker 3: But I think our, like, first of all, it was a one-sided beef for the most part.
Speaker 3: I don't really know anything about her.
Speaker 3: But I think it was also because of ideological differences.
Speaker 3: I think a lot of people grab onto whatever drama they can when they have a disagreement with me on my worldview.
Speaker 3: But instead of addressing our disagreements, they will just like...
Speaker 3: You know, slander or lean in and farm the algorithm.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah, because she was surprised that I was like, they're scared of Hassan on the right.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: Because you can capture like the male audience that they don't.
Speaker 3: But that's also part of the reason why they don't like me.
Speaker 3: Because they think I'm too vulgar, I'm too bro-y.
Speaker 3: Like there's a lot of liberals who disagree with my worldview.
Speaker 3: But then there's also a lot of people on that side that also find me to be
Ashley St. Clair: But also, from what I've seen...
Ashley St. Clair: And again, like I'm not on Twitter, so I don't see as much of it anymore.
Ashley St. Clair: I always see them regurgitating like the same few clips of you.
Ashley St. Clair: And I feel like if you're live every day for that long, like there should be more, you know, like if they can only pull up like a few.
Speaker 3: I mean, there is more.
Speaker 3: There is more.
Speaker 3: And I will keep creating more clips as well.
Speaker 3: Because it's impossible for me to talk about politics in a contentious environment with real-time feedback, with people who are actively coming in here to start shit, who are way...
Ashley St. Clair: Do you get a lot of that?
Ashley St. Clair: People coming in to your chat for that?
Speaker 3: I have an army of hate watchers as well that sit in Discord servers.
Speaker 3: And they literally, all they do every day is stalk me, my family, my loved ones.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah, they do that to me too.
Speaker 3: And then...
Ashley St. Clair: It's like mostly on Reddit for me though.
Speaker 3: Yeah, it's mostly on Reddit for me as well.
Speaker 3: But they're in Discord servers, they're all over Reddit, they're all over Twitter.
Speaker 3: And they'll just, they'll wait for an opportunity to clip something out of context.
Speaker 3: And they'll just like...
Speaker 3: Negatively frame it and because I think people have gotten way dumber most people don't even look at the actual video sometimes they even clip it in context.
Ashley St. Clair: Because they don't want to though.
Ashley St. Clair: Like they really like junk food information they don't consume actual media even the right wing like they hardly actually read full articles they're just like headline consumers and I think a lot of people are but like primarily with the right wing
Ashley St. Clair: they don't they don't read like they're sequestered to Fox News and even that it's like the digital clips that they'll pull out.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: That's it.
Speaker 3: So, but if...
Speaker 3: Everyone, if the entire market is like that, then it doesn't matter what the truth is, right?
Speaker 3: Like, and that's kind of how I, that's the drama I find myself in with regular frequencies is like, if there's enough appetite for negative framing,
Speaker 3: And I do have a lot of, obviously, like ideological opponents.
Speaker 3: There's a good market for churning out this kind of content.
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, tell me about it.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: Tell me about it.
Speaker 3: I mean, it is what it is.
Speaker 3: It's a part of the business, I guess.
Speaker 3: So, you know, that and the death threats.
Speaker 3: You just have to figure out.
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, my God, so bad, too.
Ashley St. Clair: You just have to figure out how to deal with it.
Ashley St. Clair: They're really dedicated to it.
Ashley St. Clair: And they will pull up things like fragment information to make these conspiracies.
Ashley St. Clair: And I'm like, this could not be more wrong.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: But you can't address everything like all the time.
Speaker 3: Yeah, you should.
Speaker 3: My policy is don't even address it.
Speaker 3: I gave up on addressing it.
Ashley St. Clair: Sometimes I like it, though.
Ashley St. Clair: Because I like being a little cunty sometimes.
Speaker 3: Okay, that's good.
Ashley St. Clair: So, I like fighting with them.
Speaker 3: But before we talk about Suzanne Lambert and, like, clip culture, what were we discussing?
Speaker 3: So, you're done with DC Drano.
Speaker 3: I don't know what happens there, but you guys know we're dating at a certain point.
Ashley St. Clair: He had a secret sleepover with Annapolina Luna, and they claim nothing happened.
Speaker 3: So they all f*** around, right?
Ashley St. Clair: So they say nothing happened.
Ashley St. Clair: And I'll stipulate to that, though, right?
Ashley St. Clair: What do you mean a sleepover?
Ashley St. Clair: Okay, I'll tell you exactly what happened.
Ashley St. Clair: I will stipulate to their version of events that they did not f*** each other.
Ashley St. Clair: However, it's really weird.
Speaker 3: But she's a rep now, right?
Speaker 3: She's a United States representative.
Ashley St. Clair: Yes, she's in Congress.
Ashley St. Clair: And so it's not just me, though.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, all of his exes say the same thing.
Ashley St. Clair: We have, like, we've unionized.
Ashley St. Clair: We have a group chat.
Ashley St. Clair: I've never had so many exes in a group chat, and I was in a harem.
Ashley St. Clair: So, like, and they all have the same story.
Ashley St. Clair: But I was out of town, and then I come back, and there's a face mask in our shared bathroom, which was weird because I had already moved to the guest room because he was annoying the shit out of me.
Ashley St. Clair: And I'm like, whose face mask is this?
Ashley St. Clair: And he's like, oh, I thought it was yours.
Ashley St. Clair: I would like, I would never use something that cheap who was here.
Ashley St. Clair: And he's like, it was on a, but you know, she was just staying here because she's moving to the district to carpet bag because she was living, I think, in Washington at the time.
Speaker 3: What the fuck?
Speaker 3: Wait.
Ashley St. Clair: And like she will call him in the middle of the night being like, oh, look at this guy.
Ashley St. Clair: Look at this star.
Ashley St. Clair: Like weird.
Ashley St. Clair: The whole situation is weird.
Ashley St. Clair: And then I talked about this on my TikTok.
Ashley St. Clair: And you know what the next thing she does is?
Speaker 3: What?
Ashley St. Clair: Mind you, I'm saying that she was obsessed with my ex-boyfriend.
Ashley St. Clair: The next thing she does is post a video of Elon with 15 sparkle emojis.
Ashley St. Clair: I'm like, you're one weird bitch.
Ashley St. Clair: Like that's the way you respond to me saying you're obsessed with my sloppy seconds.
Speaker 3: So you think she's like, she's going after the people that you've hooked up with?
Ashley St. Clair: I think she's just a weird bitch.
Ashley St. Clair: She would say that she had like premonitions and visions and her and Rogan would like take this as fact.
Ashley St. Clair: And these people are in our government.
Speaker 3: I was about to say, why?
Speaker 3: There's so many of them though.
Speaker 3: The Navy secretary.
Ashley St. Clair: She said that his ex-wife had a rotten spiritual smell.
Ashley St. Clair: Like just, they're weird.
Ashley St. Clair: They're really weird.
Speaker 3: Yeah, I mean, even Tucker Carlson had.
Speaker 3: that as well like uh the demons yeah he's talked about being possessed by demons like or he was sleeping one time and he like woke up with scratches all over him or something what the
Speaker 3: is that why why are so many people like i've never had an experience like that am i missing out no i don't understand i'm not close enough to gone for that but like is that is that clout
Speaker 3: Or do they genuinely believe it?
Ashley St. Clair: I don't know.
Ashley St. Clair: We need more cloud with God.
Speaker 3: No, but I mean, seriously, like, is that, does that give them more legitimacy in this movement when they say unhinged crazy shit?
Ashley St. Clair: With some people, I guess, because her whole thing is, like, pretending like she has more info on, like, the JFK files and aliens than she does.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, she's just a weird bitch.
Ashley St. Clair: She was pretending to be Jewish for a minute, and then it came out that her grandfather's a Nazi.
Speaker 3: Oh, my God.
Speaker 3: Okay.
Ashley St. Clair: They were calling her the new George Santos.
Speaker 3: We have to talk about this.
Speaker 3: We have talked about this a little bit.
Speaker 3: I have some friends that I've discussed this with, not just yourself, that put me on this journey where I found out that a lot of conservative commentators
Speaker 3: who aren't Jewish actually LARP as though they are.
Ashley St. Clair: You know who else did that?
Ashley St. Clair: Rogan, do you see Drano?
Ashley St. Clair: I have a photo of him at the wall.
Ashley St. Clair: He's wrapping, he's wrapped up.
Speaker 3: Okay, are they actually saying they're Jewish or are they just like, like, philo-Semitic or something?
Ashley St. Clair: No, they're like claiming to be Jewish.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, Rogan would go around telling people he was Jewish, like that his grandmother wasn't, all this stuff.
Ashley St. Clair: But then he has like Christian tattoos.
Ashley St. Clair: He's like Jewish when he needs to be.
Ashley St. Clair: And then he's Christian when he needs to be like.
Ashley St. Clair: He did it to get like bigger you deals.
Speaker 3: What the fuck is that?
Speaker 3: It's like what the, it's the reverse of what Nazis do.
Speaker 3: Like, you know how like Nazis would be like, oh, here's a list of all the media executives.
Speaker 3: And then they'll, they'll be like, and they're all Jewish.
Speaker 3: And then you look at the list and you're like, wait a minute, those people aren't Jewish.
Speaker 3: And then there's an asterisk next to their name.
Speaker 3: And it's like suspected you.
Ashley St. Clair: Did you ever see Danny's video where he's like, I'm the guy who finds the Jews and all the things.
Speaker 3: I think I know who you're talking about.
Ashley St. Clair: So good.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: He's like, I'm the guy.
Speaker 3: So, but like, so what is that about?
Speaker 3: Why are they just like LARPing as though they're Jewish?
Ashley St. Clair: So before October 7th, it used to be like more cool.
Ashley St. Clair: Like that.
Ashley St. Clair: That's how you would get a PragerU deal.
Ashley St. Clair: That's how you get more deals.
Speaker 3: By being Jewish?
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, PragerU f***s with the Jews.
Speaker 3: Well, I mean, yeah, of course.
Speaker 3: They're like, hell yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: Let's go, Rogan.
Ashley St. Clair: You get a sit down now.
Speaker 3: There's a, you know.
Ashley St. Clair: You get more Jewish donors.
Ashley St. Clair: You get more of the.
Speaker 3: PragerU might literally be an intelligence cutout if we're being real.
Speaker 3: So it's not, and not the American one.
Speaker 3: I mean.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Speaker 3: They have deep ties with the Israeli government.
Ashley St. Clair: It used to be very beneficial to be like, I'm Jewish, or I've been to a Shabbat dinner, which, by the way, Shabbat Shalom.
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, yeah.
Speaker 3: Wait, is it?
Speaker 3: It's technically.
Speaker 3: Yeah, it's Saturday.
Speaker 3: You're right.
Speaker 3: So.
Speaker 3: I guess in some way, they're like Shabbos goys.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: They're the little Shabbos goys of the right.
Speaker 3: So that's a very strange thing.
Speaker 3: There are some very high profile people.
Ashley St. Clair: Wait, let me find the photo of Rogan pretending to wrap the taco.
Speaker 3: Whose Judaism has been called into question.
Speaker 3: And I genuinely am afraid of saying this person's name because I just am afraid of the way she looks.
Speaker 3: So I'm not going to say it.
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, Jigsaw?
Speaker 3: Okay.
Ashley St. Clair: You know, Ozempic was the worst thing to happen to her because it just, like, made that situation so much worse.
Speaker 3: Wait, she's on Ozempic?
Speaker 3: I feel like she...
Ashley St. Clair: You think she lost that weight through hard work?
Speaker 3: Was she fat?
Speaker 3: I don't even know.
Ashley St. Clair: I don't think she lost that weight through hard work.
Ashley St. Clair: I didn't even realize she was...
Speaker 3: I have never...
Ashley St. Clair: She used to be a little chunky monkey.
Speaker 3: Okay.
Speaker 3: Well, I just, I only remember Laura Loomer talking to that one, like...
Ashley St. Clair: You named her.
Speaker 3: Yes, I did.
Speaker 3: Well, you said Jigsaw.
Speaker 3: It's out already.
Speaker 3: But yes, Laura Loomer has a high school yearbook photo.
Speaker 3: And I don't know if it's like doctored or not, but she's wearing a cross in the high school yearbook photo.
Speaker 3: And there's suspicion that she's not.
Ashley St. Clair: My mom has a video of her, like, being taught to draw a star, David.
Ashley St. Clair: Did you ever see that?
Speaker 3: No, I also am not.
Speaker 3: You know, I don't know any of these.
Speaker 3: I know of these people, and I very actively stay away from them because they freak me out, and they gross me out.
Speaker 3: So, but...
Ashley St. Clair: Wait, where is that?
Speaker 3: But yeah, from what I understand, and also make sure you don't show your phone onto...
Ashley St. Clair: There's him pretending to rap.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, you would think by, like, the second rap, you'd be like, this is a bad idea.
Speaker 3: So, when you got...
Speaker 3: You said...
Speaker 3: Since Rogan wanted to out himself as a subject of my TikTok, here's how far this man went pretending to be Jewish for business deals on the paid trips to Israel.
Speaker 3: He's not even Jewish, though I'm sure you can still find his old tweets claiming to be when it was good for business.
Speaker 3: He also says, I'm just attacking America for its patriots when only one of us took paid trips to Israel.
Speaker 3: He's as much Jewish.
Ashley St. Clair: I was offered, too.
Speaker 3: He's as much Jewish as Elizabeth Warren is Native American.
Speaker 3: His brother allegedly said they have like 1% Jewish heritage and he is not, nor has he ever been practicing.
Speaker 3: Whatever my mental health issues, I ain't doing whatever the hell this is.
Speaker 3: Pretend to be someone.
Speaker 3: You're not is why your marriage lasted less than a year.
Speaker 3: He then went around smearing his ex-wife, who's literally the nicest girl ever, as a gold digger.
Speaker 3: I genuinely have no idea why these people out of themselves.
Speaker 3: When I use fake names and this right here isn't even any personal relationship tea for me.
Speaker 3: His Jew cosplay is public.
Speaker 3: That's crazy.
Speaker 3: I thought they just like go and, you know, kiss the wall and do the tefillin to just be like, see, I'm...
Ashley St. Clair: You can't do tefillin unless you're Jewish.
Ashley St. Clair: Before they wrap it, they're like, are you Jewish?
Speaker 3: Oh, I didn't know that.
Ashley St. Clair: So that's why I'm saying by the second wrap, you think he would be like, damn.
Speaker 3: I always thought it was such a cool...
Speaker 3: I think it looks cool.
Speaker 3: It's like you're like Spartan.
Ashley St. Clair: I mean, we could work something out.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Speaker 3: I didn't realize you had to be Jewish to do tefillin.
Ashley St. Clair: They ask you.
Ashley St. Clair: They're like, are you Jewish?
Ashley St. Clair: So he had to tell that guy yes.
Speaker 3: The wall kissing is not.
Speaker 3: Because I know there's motherfuckers who are definitely not Jewish who are kissing the wall.
Speaker 3: So that's not.
Ashley St. Clair: Mike Huckabee is probably there right now.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Speaker 3: Mike Huckabee makes out with the wall.
Speaker 3: But that's just his own personal.
Speaker 3: I've said this before.
Speaker 3: I think Mike Huck.
Speaker 3: Like, okay.
Speaker 3: Let me hear your perspective on this.
Ashley St. Clair: His daughter is really nice, though.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, Sarah is really nice.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, a nice person.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, okay.
Ashley St. Clair: Politics aside.
Ashley St. Clair: She was very nice.
Ashley St. Clair: Why do you not like her?
Speaker 3: Hard for me to, I don't like any Republican.
Ashley St. Clair: Okay, but like, just seeing her with her kids, like she was super nice.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: And when you're with some of these people personally.
Speaker 3: She literally legalized child labor in her state as the governor.
Speaker 3: Yes.
Ashley St. Clair: Okay, I haven't paid attention.
Ashley St. Clair: Okay, look, I'm already going to be canceled.
Speaker 3: For me, it's like, I don't really care about how.
Speaker 3: They are in the real world or in their...
Ashley St. Clair: How did she legalize child labor?
Speaker 3: In their...
Speaker 3: They just signed it into law.
Speaker 3: State legislature lowered restrictions.
Ashley St. Clair: Okay, I'm just talking about personally because some of these people...
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, my God.
Ashley St. Clair: The rumor is she got two nose jobs and she still looks the way she does.
Speaker 3: Laura Loomer, I believe in quiet, listening to others, and always keeping an open mind.
Ashley St. Clair: No, no, that's not.
Ashley St. Clair: No.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Speaker 3: And she has a cross.
Speaker 3: She has a cross on.
Speaker 3: Well, what happened is like when she went to college, she was already an operative where she tried to start an ISIS fan club.
Speaker 3: I think she was working with James O'Keefe.
Speaker 3: Right?
Speaker 3: Chat, correct me on this if I'm wrong, but if I'm not mistaken, she was a James O'Keefe operative.
Ashley St. Clair: She tried to start an ISIS fan club?
Speaker 3: Yes, and she got expelled.
Speaker 3: Because her whole point was like, oh, these guys love Muslims so much, they're going to let me start an ISIS fan club.
Speaker 3: And so she petitioned to start an ISIS fan club, and the college was like, no.
Speaker 3: What the f***?
Speaker 3: And you're expelled for trying to start an ISIS fan club.
Speaker 3: And so it backfired on her.
Speaker 3: And then she just only doubled down her entire...
Speaker 3: Like, she's the only person I know that's been banned from every app for being Islamophobic.
Ashley St. Clair: And then she...
Ashley St. Clair: And then she doubled down and locked herself to Twitter headquarters.
Speaker 3: Yeah, that was awesome.
Speaker 3: And now she's won, though.
Ashley St. Clair: I feel like people should just spam this in her comments, like, anytime she posts anything.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, this is all that needs to be said to her.
Speaker 3: Yeah, but what I just spam that.
Speaker 3: But what's crazy about this legendary Huckabee child labor photo?
Speaker 3: That's funny.
Speaker 3: What's crazy about it is that she, I first knew about Laura Loomer because she had this clip going around, right?
Speaker 3: And this is, oh, God.
Ashley St. Clair: Someone said, I think being too ugly can radicalize.
Speaker 3: Yeah, look, this is the famous clip, right?
Speaker 3: This is the famous clip.
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, with Mike Ma.
Speaker 3: I don't know who that is, but he's...
Ashley St. Clair: So he was on Milo's tour.
Speaker 3: Okay, so he's...
Ashley St. Clair: This was during, like, peak Milo Yiannopoulos tour days.
Speaker 3: Oh, God.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Speaker 3: Okay.
Speaker 3: Yeah, but he...
Speaker 3: Pigsaw.
Speaker 3: Oh, my God.
Speaker 3: Here.
Speaker 3: This is the famous...
Speaker 3: But I have to issue a...
Speaker 3: Nuclear cringe warning here.
Speaker 3: I know you guys in this community have seen this clip many times.
Speaker 3: Have you ever seen this clip?
Ashley St. Clair: It's really bad.
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, you've seen this clip?
Speaker 3: Okay, here it is.
Speaker 3: So good, you're like beautiful.
Speaker 3: Thank you.
Speaker 3: Like an Arian to Jenna Goddess.
Speaker 3: I love it.
Speaker 3: Thank you.
Speaker 3: You're Arian too.
Speaker 3: I know, I'm Jewish.
Speaker 3: And she goes, look at his head, his head cocks.
Speaker 3: As soon as she said, no, I'm Jewish.
Ashley St. Clair: I know, but I'm Jewish.
Speaker 3: Like, what's up?
Speaker 3: Was he going to f*** her if she was Aryan?
Ashley St. Clair: I told you, you used to get, like, clout for being Jewish back in the conservative days.
Speaker 3: Yeah, okay, there's going to be echo chat.
Ashley St. Clair: The OG mega days.
Speaker 3: Shut the f*** up.
Ashley St. Clair: Wait, is there echo?
Speaker 3: Yeah, there's going to be echo because we're listening to the video.
Speaker 3: It's okay.
Speaker 3: Because you're supposed to be serious.
Speaker 3: Don't mess with my hair.
Speaker 3: God damn it.
Speaker 3: Fix it.
Speaker 3: Fix my hair.
Speaker 3: If a man ever recoiled like that,
Ashley St. Clair: When I touch his hair, I would literally never show my face ever again.
Speaker 3: Yeah, I think Laura Loomer doesn't have any setbacks on or self-restraint.
Ashley St. Clair: That is really embarrassing.
Speaker 3: That's her superpower.
Ashley St. Clair: I think Trump called her to wish her a happy birthday.
Ashley St. Clair: I think it's her birthday.
Speaker 3: Wait, today's her birthday?
Ashley St. Clair: I think so.
Ashley St. Clair: I don't know.
Ashley St. Clair: Maybe I'm spreading misinformation.
Ashley St. Clair: I think today is her birthday.
Speaker 3: Loomer's downfall, this was back in 2018, and she's up now, so it doesn't matter.
Speaker 3: But Loomer's downfall is funny because she started out as an O'Keefe rat and had her career peak at Muslim-bashing Twitter asshole, best known for getting blackout drunk and hitting on a Nazi.
Speaker 3: Yeah, except she won.
Speaker 3: Like, this was...
Ashley St. Clair: Like, you gotta give her respect for that.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, she won't die.
Speaker 3: I don't want to give her respect for that.
Ashley St. Clair: She won't go away.
Speaker 3: I think, I mean, I think she is, in many respects, like, the perfect political operative for how bad things have gotten for our times.
Speaker 3: And that's the reason why her career keeps, like...
Speaker 3: Her career keeps advancing in spite of the realities that she is an insane person.
Speaker 3: Like, demonstrably insane person.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah, she's just like the thug they use.
Speaker 3: But, like, she has no redeeming qualities.
Speaker 3: She has none.
Speaker 3: She has no redeeming qualities.
Speaker 3: She's not hot.
Ashley St. Clair: No.
Speaker 3: And the only reason why I bring that up is because, like...
Ashley St. Clair: That should not be the first option.
Speaker 3: No, no, but my point is Trump obviously cares about that, right?
Speaker 3: Like, Trump cares about the physical appearance.
Speaker 3: I don't know.
Ashley St. Clair: Have you seen Mar-a-Lago?
Speaker 3: No, but in Trump's inner circle, like if you look at some of the people that he hires, like he either hires for loyalty or he does care about like the way that
Speaker 3: people around him are perceived, like their physical appearances.
Ashley St. Clair: Yes, that would be it.
Speaker 3: And Laura Loomer is hard to look at.
Speaker 3: Why do you think he hates his sons?
Speaker 3: I think it's literally because they're ugly as shit.
Speaker 3: They're losers, but also they're ugly as shit.
Speaker 3: And I think Trump hates that.
Speaker 3: You don't think so?
Speaker 3: That's why he loves Ivanka.
Ashley St. Clair: That makes sense.
Speaker 3: Like, he's...
Ashley St. Clair: She's very aesthetically pleasing.
Speaker 3: Yeah, she's...
Ashley St. Clair: But I think he likes Ivanka too much.
Speaker 3: Yeah, that's true.
Speaker 3: But she's also in with the liberal in crowd, right?
Ashley St. Clair: She's like very popular in Hollywood.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Speaker 3: And I think Trump loves that because that's all he wanted.
Speaker 3: Like if, let's say I wanted to play in the NBA, okay?
Speaker 3: And then I...
Speaker 3: Do you?
Speaker 3: I mean, I was never going to be able to do that.
Ashley St. Clair: If they gave you an offer right now, would you do it?
Speaker 3: I mean, yes, but I would never be able to do that because I'm dog shit.
Speaker 3: But my point is, let's say I want to play in the NBA.
Speaker 3: I marry a WNBA player, okay?
Speaker 3: And then two of my kids are ass.
Speaker 3: They're like, for some weird reason, they're like five foot three, okay?
Speaker 3: And then the one child I have is like 6'10".
Speaker 3: I'm going to care about that child.
Speaker 3: And for Trump, Ivanka is the child that made it to the NBA because she got in with the liberal intelligentsia, with the in crowd, with the Hollywood people.
Speaker 3: That's all Trump ever cared about.
Speaker 3: That was his major gripe.
Speaker 3: So his next of kin was, you know, a failure.
Ashley St. Clair: She just had to marry, like, Satan to do it.
Speaker 3: Yeah, exactly.
Speaker 3: So, anyway, yeah, Trump is a looks maxer.
Speaker 3: Well, he can't looks max himself, but he's a looks maxer for the people around him.
Ashley St. Clair: Is everybody looking nice and handsome and thin?
Speaker 3: So we got Laura Loomer here talking about how she's...
Ashley St. Clair: Are you trying to get me, like, attacked?
Speaker 3: I mean, you're on this broadcast.
Speaker 3: You're going to get attacked no matter what.
Speaker 3: And I'm going to get attacked.
Speaker 3: So we're in this together.
Ashley St. Clair: Why are you going to get attacked?
Speaker 3: Why am I going to get attacked?
Speaker 3: What do you mean?
Speaker 3: Laura Loomer talks about trying to get me deported every day.
Speaker 3: She genuinely will.
Ashley St. Clair: She could actually succeed at that.
Speaker 3: I'm an American citizen.
Speaker 3: So that would be like, that would be such a...
Ashley St. Clair: We're in like half of the people that went to El Salvador.
Speaker 3: Yes, but the constitutional crisis that that would create is far too large for the Trump administration to invoke when they don't have it.
Speaker 3: They don't have the popular approval to be able to lean into that kind of thing at this point, I think.
Speaker 3: It is a genuine concern.
Speaker 3: It's something that I think about.
Speaker 3: But, you know, I always used to tell my audience, like, I'm the last in the line.
Speaker 3: By the time they get to someone like...
Speaker 3: myself if they're denaturalizing someone like myself a high-profile media figure to like who is an American citizen who lived here as a taxpayer that means everyone else is already in the camps you know so I don't worry about it too much
Speaker 3: All right, let's watch the rest of it.
Speaker 6: You posted on Instagram recently when you got reinstated on Facebook.
Speaker 6: It was so hot.
Speaker 6: Oh!
Speaker 6: I appreciate it.
Speaker 6: It's so hot.
Speaker 3: I'm gonna grab my coffee.
Speaker 6: People want to put me in a gas chamber.
Speaker 6: Ugh.
Speaker 6: Because they're obsessed with the...
Speaker 6: I don't know.
Speaker 6: I think they're just memeing on me, but it's okay.
Speaker 6: It's okay.
Speaker 6: I feel like that sometimes.
Speaker 6: I know.
Speaker 6: We're just y'all because we had a test and it's not on us.
Speaker 6: Oh my gosh.
Speaker 6: Yes!
Speaker 6: No.
Speaker 6: Yes, that's what it is.
Speaker 6: We got it.
Ashley St. Clair: Did you ever see the photos of her as a nurse?
Speaker 3: No.
Ashley St. Clair: She's like in this like slutty nurse costume.
Speaker 3: Oh no.
Ashley St. Clair: I think she gets mad at like the hot e-girls because she tried so hard and people were still like, no, it's not going to work.
Speaker 3: I mean, yeah, at some point you got to give up.
Speaker 3: Like why?
Speaker 3: Just be.
Speaker 3: Be true to yourself.
Ashley St. Clair: And I feel bad because I felt bad for her at one time.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, she would send me these texts.
Ashley St. Clair: She's like, I'm alone on Christmas.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, I don't have family.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, all this stuff.
Ashley St. Clair: And I'm like, I feel so bad for this girl.
Ashley St. Clair: But then she just goes, like, batshit insane.
Speaker 3: I mean, but that's exactly who you would expect.
Speaker 3: There's always those you expect to go batshit crazy.
Speaker 3: But again, this is rewarded.
Speaker 3: Like, there's always been hatchet men and rat and operatives like that that have led colorful lives like Roger Stone, right?
Speaker 3: So there is already, yeah, there is already, I mean, he's a full Nixon back tattoo, right?
Speaker 3: Like that's insane.
Speaker 3: And he's a swinger.
Ashley St. Clair: Really?
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: Oh.
Speaker 3: And he's a swinger, full Nixon back tattoo.
Speaker 3: He is like the classic Republican operative with a colorful persona.
Speaker 3: But now the entire movement is comprised of people like this.
Ashley St. Clair: Yes.
Speaker 3: So it's basically turned into this insane...
Speaker 3: It's an insane movement led by insane people with no real ideological agenda, no real discernible goals.
Speaker 3: They're just, their North Star is Donald Trump.
Speaker 3: And Donald Trump, I don't think, is an ideological fascist either.
Speaker 3: I think he's just found himself most comfortable in that slot.
Speaker 3: So he's just doing the, he's going through the motions because like that's what, that's what allows him to seize more power.
Speaker 3: So they're all rudderless in many respects.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah, but isn't that ideologically fascism?
Speaker 3: To a certain degree, yes.
Speaker 3: But there is not like...
Ashley St. Clair: Isn't that the definition?
Speaker 3: Like, it...
Speaker 3: In practice, it doesn't matter because it is fascist, right?
Speaker 3: This administration is fascist.
Speaker 3: The only reason why I make that distinction is because he's just not sophisticated or well-read enough to have any sort of ideological backbone beyond...
Speaker 3: Self-interest.
Speaker 3: Like, he's not...
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah, well...
Speaker 3: You think he's...
Speaker 3: I mean, you might know better than I do, but that's my assessment.
Ashley St. Clair: No, I also think it's...
Ashley St. Clair: I think there are...
Ashley St. Clair: I mean, self-interest, but also he does have a deep desire to protect, like, those within his circle or sphere of influence, not just for himself, but, like, there's...
Speaker 3: Yeah, but doesn't he chop them down all the time?
Speaker 3: I mean, look at Pam Bondi.
Ashley St. Clair: When they can't do anything for him.
Speaker 3: Yeah, Pam Bondi was always loyal.
Speaker 3: So that's what I mean.
Speaker 3: His highest priority is not to, like, design a white society or whatever.
Speaker 3: His highest priority is to make as much money as possible and gain as much power as possible.
Speaker 3: And the unitary executive theory is on the right.
Speaker 3: And he's like firmly established himself as the guy who can consolidate the base.
Speaker 3: He wants power and he's vain.
Ashley St. Clair: I think that's fracturing, though.
Speaker 3: You think so?
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: The base is being fractured away from Trump.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, there's a very small percentage of people, at least from 2015 to even up to 2024, like, it is fracturing severely.
Ashley St. Clair: That's why you're seeing people like Tucker or Candace or Megyn Kelly and all of these people fracturing out.
Speaker 3: So I think about that a lot.
Speaker 3: And I don't know if they actually have, like, you know, any influence on the man.
Speaker 3: MAGA base still.
Speaker 3: I feel like the MAGA base just goes with Trump no matter where he goes.
Ashley St. Clair: I think Candace probably has more influence because she has so many women in her audience and they will never admit it, but it's white women are the reason that Trump won.
Ashley St. Clair: Like without white women, he wouldn't have won.
Ashley St. Clair: And so Candace being able to fracture women like that, I think is, she has a lot more influence than any of the other ones in terms of that.
Speaker 3: It's true.
Ashley St. Clair: So.
Speaker 3: That's definitely true.
Speaker 3: Yeah, she does have a lot of white women in her audience.
Speaker 3: It's crazy.
Ashley St. Clair: Just women generally.
Ashley St. Clair: She's got a lot of black women in her audience, too.
Speaker 3: She's got a lot of liberal women in her audience as well.
Speaker 3: And that I find insane.
Speaker 3: But, like, they love...
Speaker 3: The way she covers real world news as a true crime drama with like insane conspiracy theories baked into it.
Speaker 3: It's unbelievably appealing to a lot of people.
Ashley St. Clair: And for some, she's actually saying things that she saw within MAGA, whereas like people like Tucker or Marjorie Taylor Greene or Megyn Kelly, they know a lot more.
Ashley St. Clair: And someone like me or even Candace know.
Ashley St. Clair: But they're not saying anything.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah, they're not saying anything.
Speaker 3: They won't say it.
Speaker 3: They won't leak it.
Ashley St. Clair: And I feel like that's the actual indicator of if their mind is changed.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, leak it.
Ashley St. Clair: Spill their secrets.
Ashley St. Clair: Stop keeping secrets for them.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, if you're still keeping secrets for them, you might as well be on their side.
Speaker 3: Well, that's because Tucker, I think, is like designing for a future post-Trump.
Speaker 3: He is, he's trying to position himself as like the guy who will own the anti-war isolationist lane.
Speaker 3: Because I think that's what he sees the base moving towards, like the younger Republicans moving in that direction.
Speaker 3: And he wants to have...
Speaker 3: He wants to have credibility in that space so he can either run himself or lend that credibility to potentially J.D.
Speaker 3: Vance.
Speaker 3: Because he's very...
Speaker 3: Tucker is reluctant to talk about Palantir.
Speaker 3: And for me, with guys like this in the right-wing sphere that are like, I'm no longer...
Speaker 3: With Trump, that's often like one telltale sign that they're still invested in a new evolution of the right when they don't go after Palantir or Peter Thiel at all.
Ashley St. Clair: Or big tech, big tech like generally.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: Because that's overtaking the entirety of the right wing and the administration and all of the levers of power within our government is big tech.
Ashley St. Clair: So, I mean, they're driving Donald Trump.
Ashley St. Clair: Donald Trump is like at behest of tech oligarchs at this point.
Speaker 3: So let's get let's talk about that.
Speaker 3: So you how do you arrive at how do we arrive at Elon Musk?
Speaker 3: You go from Drano and you're still posting on on Twitter or Periscope.
Speaker 3: Is that what you said?
Ashley St. Clair: I was going live on Periscope sometimes, but mostly Twitter.
Ashley St. Clair: I was just shitposting on Twitter.
Ashley St. Clair: And then Rogan got me into Instagram.
Ashley St. Clair: Instagram had me holding the poster boards and I'm like selling anti-socialist social club shirts.
Ashley St. Clair: Selling the t-shirts.
Ashley St. Clair: And then we'll, there were a few chapters.
Ashley St. Clair: There were a few chapters.
Ashley St. Clair: I worked at a company co-founded by Benny Johnson.
Speaker 3: Oh my God.
Speaker 3: He's gay, right?
Ashley St. Clair: There are people.
Speaker 3: All I know, I know for a fact that he is not allowed to go on work trips without his wife present now.
Ashley St. Clair: Now?
Ashley St. Clair: Because he used to.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: He used to.
Speaker 3: He used to go on work trips without his wife.
Speaker 3: I wonder why he's not allowed to go on work trips without his wife any longer.
Ashley St. Clair: He used to.
Ashley St. Clair: Maybe there's more.
Ashley St. Clair: 2020, 2021, 2022.
Ashley St. Clair: He used to.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: He's like a psychopath, though.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, incredibly, incredibly, like, verbally abusive, horrible person to work for.
Speaker 3: That's so funny.
Speaker 3: It's, you just not, I can't see him being verbally abusive.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah, because he puts on, he puts on like this front, but he's, he's psychotic.
Ashley St. Clair: He would make me cry.
Ashley St. Clair: It takes a lot to make me cry.
Ashley St. Clair: He would call me screaming, saying that I owed his wife and his newborn baby an apology for like, he was psychotic.
Speaker 3: Wait, why?
Speaker 3: What did you do?
Ashley St. Clair: Because he didn't like the way some shoot was going, that we didn't have insurance on it.
Ashley St. Clair: And I'm like, I don't own the company.
Ashley St. Clair: I can't get the insurance.
Ashley St. Clair: But he would scream, just psychotic, psychotic.
Ashley St. Clair: But so then, whatever.
Ashley St. Clair: Then I'm at the Babylon Bee working for Seth Dillon.
Speaker 3: Oh, my God.
Ashley St. Clair: Technically, I am.
Ashley St. Clair: I was working, I was running the operations for a few companies that Seth owned.
Ashley St. Clair: So it was the Babylon Bee, Libs of TikTok.
Speaker 3: Mm-hmm.
Ashley St. Clair: Because he owns that for a minute.
Speaker 3: Where are these guys getting the money?
Speaker 3: It's all funded, right?
Ashley St. Clair: Who?
Ashley St. Clair: Seth?
Speaker 3: Like, all of these...
Ashley St. Clair: Seth does well.
Speaker 3: So, these operations, though, like, what does their revenue structure look like?
Speaker 3: Because there's no...
Speaker 3: They don't have enough eyeballs or enough advertisers, I feel like.
Speaker 3: Yes, they do.
Speaker 3: They do?
Ashley St. Clair: Yes, they do.
Speaker 3: They have eyeballs or they have the advertisers?
Ashley St. Clair: Yes, both.
Speaker 3: Really?
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: They make a lot of money.
Speaker 3: That's interesting.
Ashley St. Clair: And Seth is different than the other ones because him and his brother also have other companies, like tech-adjacent companies that they had because his brother is an engineer.
Ashley St. Clair: So they had those that they were able to use and help fund things.
Ashley St. Clair: But yeah, they make a lot of money.
Ashley St. Clair: Haya was making and is making a lot of money with Lips and TikTok.
Speaker 3: What is Haya?
Ashley St. Clair: Haya.
Speaker 3: Haya?
Ashley St. Clair: Haya Rayshik, who runs Lips and TikTok.
Speaker 3: Oh, wait, how?
Speaker 3: Through Twitter?
Ashley St. Clair: Through Twitter, through Substack, through advertising.
Ashley St. Clair: The Substack...
Speaker 3: People are like, oh, I really want this psychotic doxer.
Speaker 3: I want to run ads on this psychotic doxer's platform.
Ashley St. Clair: And she would call me and I'm like, Haya, you can't dox kids.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, if you're going to post kids and I can't stop you from that, you have to blur their faces.
Ashley St. Clair: She was psychotic to work for.
Speaker 3: So, but honestly, you work for her too?
Ashley St. Clair: So Seth owned Libs of TikTok, LL.
Ashley St. Clair: Eventually he sells it and I was like, oh, thank God.
Speaker 3: I genuinely, okay, so this is the one area where I speculate.
Speaker 3: I mean, I'm in media.
Speaker 3: This is, I have a very successful media operation on my own, but it's entirely funded by subscriptions that people voluntarily subscribe to my broadcast by way of Twitch.
Speaker 3: I have a million other opportunities to generate revenue.
Speaker 3: I choose not to take them, right?
Speaker 3: Like I, there are sponsors and corporate sponsors that constantly come to try to give me big deals.
Ashley St. Clair: And you don't take them?
Speaker 3: No, because I think it's silly.
Speaker 3: I already have enough money.
Speaker 3: It doesn't matter.
Speaker 3: But, but like,
Speaker 3: So I know that there is definitely a lot of money out there.
Speaker 3: I mean, like, or even if you were loose with your morals.
Ashley St. Clair: They don't say no to anything.
Speaker 3: Yeah, I was going to say.
Ashley St. Clair: No is not in their vocabulary when it comes to money.
Speaker 3: Because like NFTs, when it first came out, I got a million calls.
Speaker 3: They were like, dude.
Ashley St. Clair: So did I.
Speaker 3: And they were like, look, we will give you unfathomable amounts of money if you just like say NFTs are good or if we make an NFT for you.
Speaker 3: And it wasn't like a like a deal where you know they were telling me that i'm going to have an nft that's uh you know price goes up what do they want just like a they would just straight up they would just straight up want to give me piles of cash so i can
Ashley St. Clair: like did that with me with that and crypto yeah crypto and cryptocurrencies nfts i of course was
Speaker 3: Like, this is a scam.
Speaker 3: I'm never going to do it.
Ashley St. Clair: I was like, I can take the Hawk 2 around.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: I will get a coin.
Speaker 3: This is before Hockto.
Speaker 3: This is when NFTs were first being launched.
Speaker 3: So I, of course, said no to it, but I know that a lot of people said yes to it, and they got a f***ing ton of money.
Speaker 3: Polymarket offered me a million dollars.
Ashley St. Clair: They offered you a million dollars?
Speaker 3: For just one day of coverage for the election.
Ashley St. Clair: I should have gotten so much more from them.
Speaker 3: No, no, no.
Speaker 3: That was their starting.
Speaker 3: That was their starting price was $1 million.
Speaker 3: You just have a polymarket ticker through your election night coverage.
Speaker 3: And I was like, no, of course I'm not going to do that.
Speaker 3: And then they got raided the next morning.
Speaker 3: But...
Ashley St. Clair: Sometimes they'll do that and set people up too.
Speaker 3: Maybe, but haven't got me yet because I say no to everything.
Speaker 3: But my point is, but this was Biden.
Speaker 3: This was Brandon's FBI.
Speaker 3: So I don't think Brandon would set up one of his strongest soldiers like that.
Speaker 3: But my point is.
Speaker 3: If you have loose morals and if you're only invested in the bag, there are definitely a lot of companies that will give you money.
Speaker 3: So I see that.
Speaker 3: But as far as like real eyeballs, as far as like real motion in the real world, I think a lot of the conservative ecosystem
Speaker 3: relies on in the same way that like New York Times has an asterisk or a sword next to the bestsellers list when the people purchase their own books.
Speaker 3: I think they do that in the Substack world as well.
Speaker 3: I think they just like dump.
Ashley St. Clair: She did it.
Speaker 3: You don't think so?
Ashley St. Clair: No, I know it because I was in the back end.
Speaker 3: So she's organically, there's like tens of thousands of people that are subscribing to her, hundreds of thousands of people that are subscribing to her sub stack because they're like, I love that you're doxing random queer teachers.
Ashley St. Clair: Correct.
Speaker 3: That's insane.
Speaker 3: That's actually shocking.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: She was making a lot.
Ashley St. Clair: She's like, oh, I'm buying a new house.
Ashley St. Clair: Look at this designer I'm getting.
Ashley St. Clair: She had a stylist.
Ashley St. Clair: She's like.
Speaker 3: She had a stylist?
Ashley St. Clair: She had a stylist.
Speaker 3: Her stylist ass.
Ashley St. Clair: I know.
Ashley St. Clair: I was like, you need a new one.
Speaker 3: Wait, was her stylist also like you had to keep within the orthodox?
Ashley St. Clair: The stylist was orthodox.
Speaker 3: She had an orthodox stylist.
Ashley St. Clair: One time, okay, this was not my job.
Ashley St. Clair: I was running operations for Seth's company.
Ashley St. Clair: She's like, can you get me kosher milk?
Ashley St. Clair: Why would I go get you milk?
Ashley St. Clair: Like, I'm not getting you milk, bitch.
Ashley St. Clair: She was trying to run people around to do everything for her.
Ashley St. Clair: But, yeah, she made a lot of money.
Ashley St. Clair: So then I'm at the Babylon Bee.
Ashley St. Clair: And then Elon bought Twitter.
Ashley St. Clair: And Seth did an interview with him.
Ashley St. Clair: Elon followed me, slid into my DMs.
Speaker 3: And you were like, this is, I mean.
Ashley St. Clair: I was like, fuck yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: I was 23.
Ashley St. Clair: I was like, ooh, I've been chosen.
Ashley St. Clair: Because at that time, you probably remember.
Speaker 3: I mean, it's probably an upgrade from DC Drano.
Ashley St. Clair: Okay, exactly.
Ashley St. Clair: My ex is putting mud on his truck on purpose.
Ashley St. Clair: So, like, it's cool.
Ashley St. Clair: So, and you remember at that time, everyone was paying so much attention to who Elon was following, like, when he first took over Twitter.
Ashley St. Clair: So, like, when he followed me, I was getting congratulation texts.
Ashley St. Clair: From like right wing to her.
Ashley St. Clair: So like I was within this cult and I'm like, I genuinely, I don't understand.
Ashley St. Clair: Our new cult leader has followed me.
Ashley St. Clair: I've been picked.
Speaker 3: I'm telling you right now, this is the exact opposite of the way I see the world.
Speaker 3: I would, if I found myself in this situation, I would kill myself.
Speaker 3: I would be like, no, not in your shoes.
Speaker 3: I'm saying like, if I was one of those people that was sending you.
Ashley St. Clair: We wouldn't have had this stream.
Speaker 3: No, I'm talking about people sending you text messages being like, oh my God, congratulations.
Ashley St. Clair: And then they would reach out to me like these conservative donors.
Ashley St. Clair: Everyone's like texting you.
Ashley St. Clair: They're like, oh my God, can you send this to Elon?
Ashley St. Clair: We have this project.
Ashley St. Clair: Like it was really intense, like very intense.
Ashley St. Clair: Because they were so obsessed with it.
Speaker 3: Oh, my God.
Speaker 3: We are peasants.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Speaker 3: We're all like.
Ashley St. Clair: They're like, please, Sam, I have a sliver of clouds, a sliver of gold.
Ashley St. Clair: And I was like, oh, my God.
Speaker 3: That's like medieval peasant shit.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: And then I was like, no.
Ashley St. Clair: I'm going to gang you.
Ashley St. Clair: It was so bad.
Ashley St. Clair: But so, and then, yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Speaker 3: Okay, so.
Ashley St. Clair: So then we interview him at Twitter.
Ashley St. Clair: Well, so he slides into my DMs and he's like, are you living in San Francisco or Austin?
Ashley St. Clair: I'm like, I'm in Austin a lot, but I'm supposed to be in San Francisco whenever you get back to Seth about an interview date.
Ashley St. Clair: Within like 30 seconds, Seth calls me.
Ashley St. Clair: He's like, Elon just got back.
Ashley St. Clair: We're going to San Francisco on Thursday.
Speaker 3: He wanted to fuck you, so you leveraged that to get a fucking interview for Babylon Bee?
Ashley St. Clair: I was a Babylon Bee employee for...
Ashley St. Clair: I was a Babylonian employee first.
Ashley St. Clair: So I was like, let me do a solid for Seth here.
Speaker 3: That's crazy.
Ashley St. Clair: And yeah, so then we were on the plane there like 48 hours later.
Ashley St. Clair: And then he's like, he texts me after the interview.
Ashley St. Clair: He's like, feel like going to Providence tonight.
Speaker 3: He took you to Providence?
Speaker 3: Oh, God.
Ashley St. Clair: And we stayed at this place that doubled as a Masonic lodge.
Speaker 3: Wait, in L.A.?
Ashley St. Clair: No, in Providence.
Speaker 3: Oh, Providence.
Speaker 3: I thought when you said Providence, I thought you were talking about the Michelin Star Sushi Restaurant in Los Angeles.
Ashley St. Clair: No.
Speaker 3: Oh, that's why I was like, you meant Rhode Island.
Ashley St. Clair: Yes.
Speaker 3: Okay, yeah, yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: So he's like wheels up at midnight.
Ashley St. Clair: So I'm like, I'm like, guys, I got to go.
Ashley St. Clair: So I'm skedaddling.
Ashley St. Clair: I bring my little suitcase to the private airport.
Ashley St. Clair: And then I'm on his jet.
Ashley St. Clair: I'm like, this is nicer than commercial for sure.
Speaker 3: Mm-hmm.
Speaker 3: Okay.
Ashley St. Clair: Then he did his little silverware tricks.
Speaker 3: What's a fucking silverware trick?
Speaker 3: What does he do?
Ashley St. Clair: He was like balancing wine glasses on silverware.
Ashley St. Clair: I have a photo of it.
Ashley St. Clair: Because he does it and then he's like, do you want to take a photo?
Ashley St. Clair: I'm like, I can.
Ashley St. Clair: He wanted me to take a photo of it.
Ashley St. Clair: Hang on.
Ashley St. Clair: I'll show you.
Ashley St. Clair: Wait.
Speaker 3: Why?
Speaker 3: I just, he's so autistic.
Speaker 3: It's crazy.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: Wait.
Ashley St. Clair: No, not that one.
Ashley St. Clair: Don't talk to his phone number.
Ashley St. Clair: This was from the plane.
Speaker 3: Oh, that's like straight up the...
Ashley St. Clair: That's on his...
Speaker 3: Yeah, he even has the, he's stimming with his mouth.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Speaker 3: In the photo, he's like.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah, so then like, and then we just didn't stop talking or meeting up after that.
Ashley St. Clair: And then the Fionn Nation attacked.
Speaker 3: So what's the deal?
Speaker 3: He wants to like repopulate the earth or something?
Speaker 3: Like what the fuck is that about?
Speaker 3: Like he has like, is it a breeding fetish?
Speaker 3: What is it?
Ashley St. Clair: I don't know.
Speaker 3: Or is he just like a loser who got a lot of money so now he wants to like fuck as much as he can?
Ashley St. Clair: He got so much weirder like after I was pregnant.
Ashley St. Clair: Like just changed completely.
Speaker 3: Towards you or just in general?
Ashley St. Clair: Towards me.
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, okay.
Ashley St. Clair: Like just like kind of.
Ashley St. Clair: mean, like very, a lot more like controlling and snappy.
Ashley St. Clair: And it was just, and then he tried to get me to use surrogates.
Ashley St. Clair: He texted me and he's like, to reach Legion level before the apocalypse, we need to use surrogates.
Ashley St. Clair: That's what he texted me.
Ashley St. Clair: I saw that.
Ashley St. Clair: And I was like, no, thank you.
Ashley St. Clair: And then he tried getting me to have a C-section, like elect to have a C-section.
Speaker 3: Why?
Ashley St. Clair: Because he said, oh, it's better for the brain size.
Ashley St. Clair: I'm like, no, thank you.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, I'm not going to elect my, this works fine, no thanks.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: It just got really weird.
Speaker 3: We...
Ashley St. Clair: Like, very weird.
Speaker 3: Where is he getting this information from?
Ashley St. Clair: Probably Twitter.
Ashley St. Clair: Probably from some Nazi on Twitter.
Speaker 3: So that's the other thing.
Speaker 3: So he's...
Speaker 3: Look, I've talked to Vivian about this as well, like this transformation that took place.
Speaker 3: And she was telling me that like, no, he was always kind of like that, but he was just like hiding it.
Ashley St. Clair: I think so.
Ashley St. Clair: And I think he hides it from people like in his personal life too, like just how like,
Speaker 3: I don't even know how you can hide it at this point.
Speaker 3: I mean, it's pretty public.
Ashley St. Clair: Now he's just like, fuck it.
Ashley St. Clair: But it, yeah.
Speaker 3: There's a desperation and not dissimilar to Trump, actually.
Speaker 3: There's this like constant need for admiration that he has.
Speaker 3: And he wants people that despise him to like him a lot.
Speaker 3: Which, I guess in a weird way...
Ashley St. Clair: I don't think so.
Speaker 3: You don't think so?
Ashley St. Clair: No, I think he really hates and wants to smite all of his enemies.
Speaker 3: Okay, well that's not great for me, I think.
Speaker 3: Because I don't think he likes me too much.
Ashley St. Clair: No, I don't think so.
Speaker 3: No, he fucking tweets about me all the time, which at first it was like...
Ashley St. Clair: Same.
Speaker 3: At first, for you, it makes sense.
Speaker 3: You guys, you know, you guys had sex, so...
Speaker 3: Did you not?
Speaker 3: Wait, is that not...
Speaker 3: Wait, I jokingly said he mailed his cum in a napkin.
Ashley St. Clair: Don't say that!
Ashley St. Clair: That is so gross!
Speaker 3: But, like, what...
Ashley St. Clair: Hassan!
Speaker 3: Okay, well...
Ashley St. Clair: Where's the spray bottle?
Ashley St. Clair: Okay, I apologize.
Ashley St. Clair: Is your mother watching this?
Speaker 3: No, she would be horrified with the things that I say.
Ashley St. Clair: I'm going to call your mom.
Speaker 3: No, she'd be horrified with the things that I say.
Speaker 3: I say on this broadcast.
Ashley St. Clair: Completely inappropriate.
Speaker 3: Okay, so.
Ashley St. Clair: No, I didn't get a napkin, Hasan.
Speaker 3: So he didn't mail it?
Ashley St. Clair: Don't, don't.
Speaker 3: He didn't mail it?
Ashley St. Clair: No.
Ashley St. Clair: Okay.
Ashley St. Clair: There was no mailing, Hasan.
Speaker 3: Okay.
Speaker 3: So.
Ashley St. Clair: That's really close.
Speaker 3: Anyway, the point I was making, perhaps a little bit in a crude way, was that you guys were intimate with one another.
Speaker 3: I don't fucking know this guy at all.
Speaker 3: He should not know who a random Twitch streamer is.
Speaker 3: Why the fuck does he know who?
Ashley St. Clair: Because he's like, Twitter's like breaking his brain.
Ashley St. Clair: Or like what was left of it.
Speaker 3: Well, mine too.
Speaker 3: Which is why if he like ended up banning me after this interaction, it would probably be good for my mental health, honestly.
Speaker 3: Because it's like, it's so bad.
Ashley St. Clair: It's really bad.
Ashley St. Clair: Like objectively, and I'm not just saying that because I hate that platform and everything on it.
Ashley St. Clair: But it got a lot worse.
Ashley St. Clair: I used to love Twitter.
Speaker 3: Yeah, me too.
Speaker 3: I'm still a power user, unfortunately.
Speaker 3: Which is part of the reason why I don't think he'll ban me.
Speaker 3: Because I'm like...
Speaker 3: I am a noticeable percentage of the real human interactions that takes place on that fucking website.
Speaker 3: Not bottom shit.
Ashley St. Clair: How do you gauge that?
Ashley St. Clair: Or are you just like guessing?
Speaker 3: I just assume, but also because like anytime I say some shit, it drives discourse for at least like a day and a half where people are just like, this is the dumbest thing I've ever heard in my entire life.
Speaker 3: Fuck you.
Speaker 3: I want to kill you right now.
Ashley St. Clair: Isn't it great how much people just want to kill you for her?
Ashley St. Clair: Like political?
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Speaker 3: I mean, I'm used to it, but it's a fucking neo-Nazi shithole.
Speaker 3: Of course, of course, there's a lot of people who want to kill me.
Speaker 3: I hate Nazis.
Speaker 3: But so we're yeah, there will be like well Twitter trends nowadays are obviously fake because it's like AI and it just only shows you like what your interests are but like
Speaker 3: I'm just gauging it off of like real impressions that that take place on the I feel like when you're online enough and like you're autistic about it enough, you know, yeah, I have a good gauge of that sort of thing, but apparently not with
Speaker 3: the funding vehicles for Republican operations, because clearly I genuinely thought that these guys were really boosting their numbers, like Barry Weiss's sub stack, getting all those.
Ashley St. Clair: They invited me to do some show for the free press and I was like, red, 8.42 p.m., no thank you.
Speaker 3: Yeah, but that's what I mean.
Speaker 3: I feel like there's a lot of, there's a more sophisticated funding vehicle that like hides the fact that it's not actually grassroots, but it's entirely astroturfed is my speculation.
Speaker 3: Because it doesn't make sense.
Ashley St. Clair: No.
Ashley St. Clair: I mean, you could probably get your favorite MAGA influencer to tweet whatever you want for a couple hundred to a thousand bucks.
Speaker 3: Yeah, for sure.
Speaker 3: I mean, so there's like group chats, right?
Speaker 3: There's like Twitter chats and you were part of this network.
Speaker 3: So let's talk about that.
Ashley St. Clair: And they have members of the admin in it too.
Ashley St. Clair: Like there's members of the Trump administration, like during the campaign, they had campaign calls and messaging within.
Ashley St. Clair: this group chat, here's how we respond to this, here's how we don't respond to this.
Ashley St. Clair: And it's incredibly coordinated.
Ashley St. Clair: And this is going back like to the 2017 days when the group chats really started picking up.
Ashley St. Clair: But then this past election cycle, they added a lot more of the admin members and campaign members like James Blair's in them.
Ashley St. Clair: Some of the Trump kids are in them.
Ashley St. Clair: Caroline Levitt, members of Congress, they're all in it.
Speaker 3: Yeah, there is definitely a lot more cross-pollination across different vectors.
Speaker 3: And like this has always been the case, going back to our starting point, the conversation with Charlie Kirk, going from writing an article on his high school newspaper to being elevated to Fox News and then instantly taking that newfound
Speaker 3: clout to foster freeze.
Speaker 3: And saying like, I want to start this thing where I do basically lobbying for student governments in high school and in college.
Speaker 3: And for the longest time, Turning Point USA wasn't actually successful in changing the minds of the youth.
Speaker 3: They were, their primary audience was older people.
Ashley St. Clair: I think they were.
Ashley St. Clair: On the college campuses, like the whole socialism sucks stuff, that was,
Ashley St. Clair: Because it was so trendy and provocative online and you could get this like social clout or social media clout from it that people actually took those ideologies to heart.
Ashley St. Clair: So I think they were effective on, at least from my experience, because it was effective for me.
Ashley St. Clair: who was otherwise, in my opinion, very thoughtful in my classes and my papers.
Ashley St. Clair: And then I got involved in this and I was completely stupid.
Speaker 3: But I would say that like, as far as like real world influence, like it didn't bear itself out in the data in the elections at all, right?
Speaker 3: Like people were not like going out and voting for the Republican Party until TikTok was slated to be.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah, you're talking about.
Speaker 3: I'm talking about post-TikTok.
Ashley St. Clair: Voter propensity.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Speaker 3: Post-TikTok purchase, or before TikTok got purchased, sorry, but TikTok was about to be banned.
Speaker 3: There's an election cycle that's taking place.
Speaker 3: China's obviously very responsive to this kind of stuff.
Speaker 3: They're very tapped in.
Speaker 3: So what I saw, and you can tell me if I'm wrong on this.
Speaker 3: Is that China basically was like, oh, if we open up the algorithm faucet a little bit for, you know, right wing influencers that have direct access to Donald Trump, Charlie Kirk specifically, and they go super viral.
Speaker 3: Charlie will take that information back to the president.
Speaker 3: Yeah, because he did a 180.
Speaker 3: Yes.
Speaker 3: 180 on TikTok.
Speaker 3: And Trump will actually want to save TikTok.
Speaker 3: Democrats wanted to take it out because of AIPAC and because of Israel.
Speaker 3: Democrats were like, we've wanted to take out TikTok already.
Speaker 3: It's unaccountable.
Speaker 3: The algorithm is still controlled by a foreign company, a foreign government.
Speaker 3: And obviously, they're the major China hawks.
Speaker 3: And they're also massive Israel dick riders.
Speaker 3: So when, you know, post-October 7, they were like, we're.
Speaker 3: We're going to use this as an opportunity to just completely cut out TikTok.
Speaker 3: We're going to force the purchase of TikTok or we're going to ban it outright.
Speaker 3: The reason why they didn't ban it outright and they were able to leverage a deal, in my opinion, is because Trump saw the boost that he got in the youth vote.
Speaker 3: By way of Charlie Kirk and Turning Point USA, and he recognized that TikTok was a major role in this, and that's the reason why he basically gave a lifeline to TikTok to continue operating on U.S.
Speaker 3: Soil and then force the purchase of it, like exchange of ownership to the Ellisons.
Speaker 3: That is when Charlie actually had some impact with the youth.
Speaker 3: Because I, like, even when you look at the approval ratings of Charlie Kirk.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah, he really blew up on TikTok, too.
Speaker 3: Yeah, before TikTok, though, I remember covering this at the time because, you know, there's a lot of, like, right-wing media watchers, like Media Matters and the like.
Speaker 3: Their whole shtick was getting money from older Republicans that are super wealthy to make them feel like they were converting the youth with regular frequency.
Speaker 3: But their ad spend was entirely for like the 65 plus year olds.
Speaker 3: They weren't actually even...
Ashley St. Clair: Really?
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Speaker 3: They weren't actually targeting young people at all.
Speaker 3: They were targeting older people and duping them into believing.
Ashley St. Clair: Well, that makes sense, too, because there's a new thing that just came out about how so many of the Turning Point chapters are fake.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: Like they don't exist.
Ashley St. Clair: They went and...
Ashley St. Clair: They called these chapters.
Ashley St. Clair: They're not there.
Ashley St. Clair: The school has no record of this.
Ashley St. Clair: So that makes sense.
Speaker 3: No, it was a little bit of a scam to dupe older people into thinking that they were actually...
Speaker 3: To dupe older people into giving them money with the idea that they were actually convincing young people to vote Republican and become Republican.
Speaker 3: There might have been some successes, yourself included, by way of social...
Ashley St. Clair: I don't know if we'd call me a success there, but...
Speaker 3: I mean, you became a Republican operative, so that's what I mean.
Speaker 3: You were young, you were in college, you were an annoying debate lord, and you were like, this is my people, right?
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, yeah.
Speaker 3: You found yourself...
Ashley St. Clair: I did those Piers Morgan hits.
Speaker 3: Yeah, you found yourself in the throes of the right-wing media ecosystem.
Speaker 3: And that is, I think...
Ashley St. Clair: But it wasn't even like so much.
Ashley St. Clair: It was that I was really good at taking the talking points.
Ashley St. Clair: I do have to go in a second, too.
Speaker 3: Yeah, I was going to see where...
Speaker 3: Because I know you got some stuff going on.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah, I got to...
Speaker 3: So...
Ashley St. Clair: I think you know, Kim.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Speaker 3: So, we've talked about the tea.
Speaker 3: So, they're fucking each other.
Speaker 3: They're all getting paid.
Speaker 3: Many of them are not, like, true believers, or at least they become somewhat true believers, but they don't, like, I guess, practice it in their real lives.
Speaker 3: Who is the most, like...
Speaker 3: Genuine conservative actor who is like legitimately like that you know traditional
Ashley St. Clair: I think some of the more Christian people, like the Allie Beth Stuckies, really believe that.
Ashley St. Clair: And the things that they say, though I disagree with them, they genuinely believe the things that they're saying.
Ashley St. Clair: I think that hyper...
Ashley St. Clair: Actual Christian evangelical group, I feel like they probably believe things a little bit more.
Ashley St. Clair: I think Matt Walsh actually believes what he says.
Ashley St. Clair: Though he's completely wrong.
Speaker 3: But he also has to dial it back though on some stuff, I think.
Speaker 3: Yes.
Speaker 3: Like Israel.
Ashley St. Clair: Yes.
Speaker 3: I think like on the, if Matt Walsh was not a part of the Daily Wire operation, he would be probably Nick Fuentes territory, I think, on Israel.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Speaker 3: Like he's just.
Ashley St. Clair: But I think he genuinely believes the things he says.
Speaker 3: Yeah, on the other stuff, yeah.
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Speaker 3: Like, you know, trans people and whatnot, or, you know, degeneracy of the left or whatever.
Speaker 3: Okay.
Speaker 3: Who's the least, like, who's the least consistent?
Ashley St. Clair: I think most of the people, like, in the admin are incredibly self-serving.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, they don't actually have convictions besides, like, white nationalism.
Ashley St. Clair: And they will go where the money is.
Ashley St. Clair: Okay.
Ashley St. Clair: Like the people in the White House are incredibly self-serving grifters.
Ashley St. Clair: They're all fucking each other.
Ashley St. Clair: There's affairs.
Ashley St. Clair: There's this.
Ashley St. Clair: There's that.
Ashley St. Clair: There's the drug.
Speaker 3: All the Moms for Liberty ladies, too.
Speaker 3: I mean, they all swing.
Speaker 3: Like Nancy Mace's.
Speaker 3: Like, we've seen the videos.
Speaker 3: Like, they all...
Speaker 3: I think they just get really bored living wherever they live, and they just, like, all fuck one another, and they do parties.
Ashley St. Clair: I think members should have to wear a GoPro on their head and be, like, drug and alcohol tested at all times.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, there should just be, like, a live stream on their head.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, we should not know more about, like, Johnny Somali's life than...
Ashley St. Clair: Members of Congress.
Ashley St. Clair: They just need like a GoPro and drug tests.
Speaker 3: I don't know if I want to know what Lauren Boebert's getting up to.
Ashley St. Clair: In the theater?
Speaker 3: In the theater, yeah.
Speaker 3: So, all right.
Speaker 3: There's one other question that I wanted to ask you before I let you go.
Speaker 3: You mentioned that there were some things that took place with Doge, specifically as it pertains to the last election.
Speaker 3: What did you mean by that?
Speaker 3: Like, what's going on there?
Speaker 3: Did Elon play a role in stealing the 2024 election?
Speaker 3: I'm not a...
Ashley St. Clair: So all I know is what he has sent me and what his engineers and employees have told me.
Ashley St. Clair: But in October of 2024, he sent me texts, which you can look at if you want.
Ashley St. Clair: You want to read the text?
Speaker 3: Sure.
Speaker 3: Why not?
Ashley St. Clair: Here.
Ashley St. Clair: I'm not making this space laser shit up.
Ashley St. Clair: And everyone's like, oh my god, she sounds so crazy.
Ashley St. Clair: I'm like, well, this is what he said.
Ashley St. Clair: I don't know what to tell you guys.
Ashley St. Clair: On iMessage, of all places.
Speaker 3: Well, I don't think, you know, Apple is going to...
Ashley St. Clair: Okay, but don't read my pick-me stuff.
Speaker 3: Okay, it's fairly...
Ashley St. Clair: Because I was being pick-me.
Ashley St. Clair: Okay, what?
Ashley St. Clair: This was October 5th, 2024.
Speaker 3: What the fuck does that even mean?
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah, you tell me.
Speaker 3: Wait, why does he, he actually talks like this?
Ashley St. Clair: Yes, he actually talks like this.
Ashley St. Clair: And I wasn't being hyperbolic when I said this.
Ashley St. Clair: Can I read this one?
Ashley St. Clair: Yes, you can read the whole thing.
Ashley St. Clair: Okay.
Ashley St. Clair: You can read anything except my pick me.
Speaker 3: Okay, I'm feeling more optimistic after tonight.
Speaker 3: And tomorrow we unleash the anomaly in the matrix.
Speaker 3: And then this is not something on the chessboard, so they will be quite surprised.
Speaker 3: In air quotes, lasers from space.
Speaker 3: What?
Speaker 3: And you made a joke.
Ashley St. Clair: It was a Marjorie Taylor Greene joke.
Speaker 3: Yeah, you made a Jewish space laser joke.
Ashley St. Clair: I said, finally a focus on the Jewish vote.
Speaker 3: And he laughed at it.
Speaker 3: And then I have over 10,000 lasers in space right now.
Ashley St. Clair: So he doubles down and says, and quantifies his number of space lasers.
Speaker 3: I'm reading your text messages back.
Ashley St. Clair: But I say, I was like, I don't want to be deposed.
Speaker 3: Oh, God, you literally sound like him.
Speaker 3: You sound, you changed the way you talk.
Speaker 3: I told you I was so pick me.
Ashley St. Clair: I was so pick me.
Speaker 3: You're using the terminology.
Ashley St. Clair: It was so bad.
Ashley St. Clair: Don't even, don't even.
Speaker 3: That's crazy.
Ashley St. Clair: I was so pick me.
Ashley St. Clair: It's like, it makes me want to throw up and die.
Speaker 3: Simulation.
Ashley St. Clair: Stop, stop.
Ashley St. Clair: Badass sci-fi drama.
Ashley St. Clair: Stop it, stop it.
Ashley St. Clair: But I said I don't want to be deposed.
Ashley St. Clair: And what does he say?
Ashley St. Clair: I was like, I would ask more, but I don't want to be deposed.
Speaker 3: You should have asked more.
Ashley St. Clair: Okay, no, no, no.
Ashley St. Clair: You stop.
Speaker 3: Oh, what the fuck?
Speaker 3: You guys send memes to each other?
Speaker 3: You're so lame.
Speaker 3: Oh my god, I can't believe he literally like, this is...
Ashley St. Clair: That's enough.
Speaker 3: That is the most, wait, he's Gen X, right?
Ashley St. Clair: I don't know.
Speaker 3: That's the most failennial ass like text message.
Speaker 3: Aren't you Gen Z?
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: That's nasty.
Speaker 3: That was way worse than you.
Speaker 3: Trying to talk like him in your text messages.
Speaker 3: That is like sending like epic memes.
Speaker 3: Wow.
Ashley St. Clair: I want to die.
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, my God.
Speaker 3: Wow, that's embarrassing.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah, but so he did say that stuff.
Ashley St. Clair: And then, okay, so in conjunction with that, then he's sending me the internal data from America Pack where he's, like, tracking the real-time Delta vote metrics.
Ashley St. Clair: He has, like, the cash prizes as incentives.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, it was...
Speaker 3: Yeah, it was not illegal.
Speaker 3: I don't even understand how that was just, like, allowed.
Speaker 3: But I guess you can do that.
Speaker 3: If you're a billionaire, you can do that.
Speaker 3: If you're Israeli, you can do that.
Speaker 3: It's cool.
Speaker 3: It's great.
Speaker 3: America is up for sale.
Speaker 3: Okay, so go on.
Ashley St. Clair: I'm feeling my heart's beating faster after you read my cringe big red.
Speaker 3: That was, yeah, that was the most consequential thing that I learned about you.
Ashley St. Clair: There were so many memes too.
Ashley St. Clair: Some of them were good.
Speaker 3: I'm sure.
Speaker 3: You want to show me a good one?
Ashley St. Clair: He said worse things about 9-11 than you.
Speaker 3: Yeah, that's not...
Speaker 3: Everyone has.
Speaker 3: That's not even surprising.
Speaker 3: But show me one of your good memes then.
Speaker 3: No.
Speaker 3: No, it's all like cringe as fuck.
Speaker 3: It's so cringe.
Ashley St. Clair: Some of them were good.
Ashley St. Clair: I have some good memes.
Ashley St. Clair: You think I don't have good memes?
Speaker 3: I don't think that any of the ones I saw there were good.
Speaker 3: They were all like nine gag.
Speaker 3: Like you were communicating with one another with nine gag memes.
Ashley St. Clair: I'm like sweating.
Speaker 3: Okay, that's crazy.
Speaker 3: Anyway, go on.
Ashley St. Clair: What am I going on about?
Ashley St. Clair: What do you want?
Speaker 3: So he's like showing you all this data, all this meme.
Speaker 3: All the stuff that he's tracking.
Ashley St. Clair: I gave him that black MAGA hat.
Ashley St. Clair: I'm responsible for dark MAGA.
Speaker 3: Ugh, gross.
Ashley St. Clair: I put it on him at my house and he's like, I'm dark MAGA now.
Ashley St. Clair: And then he's like, can you get one of these in gothic font?
Speaker 3: Okay, seriously though, like, at no point did you find that to be cringe at the time?
Speaker 3: You were just like swept away?
Speaker 3: Like what?
Ashley St. Clair: No, I was like, he's saving free speech in the world.
Ashley St. Clair: But part of me, like, I was starting to like look side-eye like once I was pregnant because I saw the way he was treating Claire like Grimes and I saw...
Ashley St. Clair: Some things that I was like, this is not gonna be good.
Speaker 3: Let me answer this.
Speaker 3: This is the one area that I do actually find very interesting with Elon is that like, obviously he's a very thin skinned guy and he's very sensitive.
Speaker 3: But he, like, on the one hand, he opened up the faucet of neo-Nazi sentiment on Twitter, and he did it very deliberately, and it's very obvious that he's using it in the same way that, like, billionaires use the Washington Post, for example, right?
Ashley St. Clair: No, it's way different.
Speaker 3: No, but he's using it as a way to peddle influence, right?
Ashley St. Clair: Sort of, and manipulate influence.
Ashley St. Clair: I would say it's more similar to a Cambridge Analytica on methamphetamines than it is a Washington Post.
Speaker 3: You have a more direct hands-on approach because it's a social media platform.
Speaker 3: And I think he probably does it even in ways that even Mark Zuckerberg doesn't.
Speaker 3: He's very blunt with the way he's trying to engage in social engineering.
Ashley St. Clair: No, he lies all the time.
Speaker 3: No, but I mean like he is using Twitter to change people's minds in a certain way.
Ashley St. Clair: Well, he's feeding it into his own behavioral inference model, which is now part of a trillion dollar company.
Speaker 3: Yeah, so, and it's working, unfortunately.
Speaker 3: I feel like people have gotten dumber, people have gotten more vicious, more reactionary, more violent.
Speaker 3: So it has been successful to a certain degree.
Speaker 3: But what I find very interesting is that
Speaker 3: Someone like myself probably would have been banned first day.
Speaker 3: So there is something there as far as like allowing people to still speak out against Israel to a certain degree.
Speaker 3: And I don't understand where that fits in his in his mentality, because like if someone is obviously disruptive to a degree where he's like frustrated, he will ban them.
Speaker 3: Like the guy who was tracking his flights.
Ashley St. Clair: He did it to Laura Loomer, too.
Ashley St. Clair: So during the H-1B visa debacle in December of 24, he literally directed the engineers.
Ashley St. Clair: He's like, anyone associated with Laura Loomer is dead to me.
Ashley St. Clair: And he like de-checkmarked her, demonetized her and everyone in the affiliate organization she was a part of.
Ashley St. Clair: So he very much does that.
Ashley St. Clair: But it's only for personal beefs.
Ashley St. Clair: The other data is more valuable because you can do a lot with the data on your enemies, like what you want to do there.
Ashley St. Clair: The data on revolutions is really, really valuable.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, why do you think, OK, I'll deploy Starlink where there's fucking revolutions.
Ashley St. Clair: That's awesome.
Ashley St. Clair: Now I have all the data.
Ashley St. Clair: on revolutions.
Speaker 3: This is something that I've heard from other people who are also in the AI space as well.
Speaker 3: Like trying to understand or trying to log behavior is one of the things that they focus on quite a bit.
Speaker 3: Yanis Varoufakis and I talked about this as well.
Speaker 3: We were at a tech summit where we were around like some very powerful people and they were just openly, you know, leaking this information.
Ashley St. Clair: It's the final terrain of extraction.
Ashley St. Clair: Like this is what
Ashley St. Clair: broke my brain i was like oh they don't have labor anymore really they're just going to extract like our consciousness and our soul like it is like the death stage of capitalism to the point that like
Speaker 3: it might be the end of all of us they're they're looking for like their their behavior they're mapping out behavior patterns this is 100 real they're also looking at the way like in chaotic situations like in gaza for example
Speaker 3: during this genocide a lot of those uh surveillance companies and a lot of AI companies were logging data on what happens.
Speaker 3: When a bomb explodes or when a civilian area is targeted and they're mapping out ambulance routes and taking that data and potentially selling it to hospitals
Speaker 3: for crisis management in the United States of America.
Speaker 3: They look at that data as unbelievably valuable information.
Ashley St. Clair: So ask yourself why the guy who is tweeting anti-Semitic shit all day every day, like says Jews are no friends of the Anglos because they believe in race mixing, he reposted.
Ashley St. Clair: that, Elon, why he's still speaking in Israel and is friends with Israel.
Speaker 3: Well, because Israel doesn't give a shit about anti-Semitism.
Ashley St. Clair: Because it's the technology.
Speaker 3: Yeah, and also, I don't think Israel, I think Israel benefits from anti-Semitism.
Ashley St. Clair: They will performatively care about anti-Semitism.
Ashley St. Clair: If there was any other big figure who they were not benefiting from their technology, 100%, they'd be like, Jonathan Greenblatt, get him.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: Right away.
Speaker 3: Yeah, no, Jonathan Greenblatt never talks about Elon Musk and has defended his Sig Heil, which, by the way, that was a Sig Heil, right?
Ashley St. Clair: I, I, um, we were not on great terms then.
Speaker 3: I know, but like, there is, you were intimately familiar with Elon Musk.
Speaker 3: I suspect that there is like, what I say about Donald Trump is like, he's not an ideological fascist.
Speaker 3: I don't say about Elon.
Speaker 3: I think Elon Musk has a very clear worldview.
Speaker 3: I can't fully understand it, but it's some kind of esoteric fascist.
Ashley St. Clair: It's very eugenics based.
Ashley St. Clair: Technocracy.
Ashley St. Clair: And I did not realize that until like much later, unfortunately.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: There was, like, especially when I was pregnant, there were things that he would say that, like, would take me aback that I was like, wait, like, is this a race thing?
Ashley St. Clair: Because, you know, I get...
Speaker 3: At least South African.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah, I...
Speaker 3: And white South Africans are either the most base people you've ever met or some of the most...
Ashley St. Clair: I was incredibly ignorant to a lot of those histories and things of that nature.
Ashley St. Clair: But he would say things that I was like, oh, like this, it's about race for you.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, this is...
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Speaker 3: It's so stupid, too.
Speaker 3: Like, they pour endless amounts of time, energy, and effort into, like, scientific racism that is discarded.
Speaker 3: Junk science.
Speaker 3: Yeah, debunked for good reason.
Speaker 3: Not because, like, for woke reasons.
Speaker 3: Debunked because it's just, like, is objectively not correct.
Speaker 3: And yet they just still go back to that.
Speaker 3: And it's cope.
Speaker 3: But I understand why.
Ashley St. Clair: Because he would be like, oh, Grok is more bass now.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, ask it about IQ and all this stuff.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, race IQ.
Ashley St. Clair: And he, like, had me asking Grok this shit.
Ashley St. Clair: And I'm like, what the fuck?
Ashley St. Clair: It's happening.
Speaker 3: So, like, I mean, how can you have this much, how can you command this much power over the entire planet and also be this childlike, like, this silly at the same time?
Speaker 3: I don't understand it.
Ashley St. Clair: I don't know.
Ashley St. Clair: I don't know what has to happen in your life that you get, like, stuck developmentally at that age, but...
Speaker 3: Yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: That's it.
Ashley St. Clair: Okay, I have like five minutes.
Speaker 3: Okay.
Ashley St. Clair: I have Kim asking my ATA.
Speaker 3: So you don't know what Elon Musk may or may not have done as far as tampering with the 2024 election, which I don't even think, I don't believe that stuff anyway.
Ashley St. Clair: All I know is what he told me, what his engineers told me, the things that were incredibly concerning to me
Ashley St. Clair: about, and I hope someone who can do more about this reaches out so that I can discuss those things more freely because I'm not going to dox those engineers.
Ashley St. Clair: Like, I'm just not.
Ashley St. Clair: I don't want them to be in danger.
Ashley St. Clair: The things that happened with Doge that the engineers told me was concerning as well.
Ashley St. Clair: Like people within his companies who were not special government employees who had this information.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah.
Speaker 3: And there's been a lot of revelations on that stuff on that front to like data that was exchanging ownership into private hands.
Speaker 3: And and we don't know what he was doing with that data as well.
Ashley St. Clair: Why was he interviewing the NASA administrator?
Ashley St. Clair: He texted me and said, I'm interviewing the NASA administrator at Mar-a-Lago.
Speaker 3: I mean, that does make sense.
Ashley St. Clair: Yeah, but why?
Speaker 3: Because he's a private contractor that wants to...
Ashley St. Clair: That's so not okay.
Ashley St. Clair: Why was he interviewing these admin picks?
Ashley St. Clair: Like, that's...
Speaker 3: No, that I do understand.
Speaker 3: That actually makes a lot more sense than all this other stuff because he's like the space guy.
Speaker 3: Trump obviously trusts him on the space issue.
Speaker 3: And the American...
Speaker 3: government is literally a money faucet for private interests and he obviously is one of the major, SpaceX is the company, right, for space exploration and whatnot.
Speaker 3: So from Trump's perspective, that makes total sense.
Speaker 3: I do understand that.
Speaker 3: I wonder...
Ashley St. Clair: That's exactly why he shouldn't be doing it.
Speaker 3: Well, yeah.
Speaker 3: I don't think it's ethical.
Speaker 3: I don't think it's right.
Speaker 3: I want NASA to be a publicly funded institution.
Speaker 3: I don't want there to be a piecemeal private enterprise that, like, take over that responsibility.
Speaker 3: They're saying letter talk.
Speaker 3: I'm being misogynistic.
Speaker 3: Go on.
Speaker 3: What else?
Ashley St. Clair: Nothing's worse than the napkin comment.
Speaker 3: All right.
Speaker 3: Well, I apologize.
Speaker 3: Well, it wasn't a napkin.
Speaker 3: It was a male.
Speaker 3: Like, I just, I thought he...
Ashley St. Clair: Mailed in a napkin.
Ashley St. Clair: Okay.
Speaker 3: Okay, well.
Speaker 3: I just, which, is it worse?
Speaker 3: Which one's worse, having sex with Elon Musk?
Speaker 3: Ah!
Speaker 3: Or, or.
Ashley St. Clair: Stop.
Speaker 3: Or artificial insemination.
Ashley St. Clair: You know what's worse is you reading my text.
Speaker 3: Yeah, that was worse.
Speaker 3: Yeah, actually, that was far worse than the napkin comment, but I apologize.
Speaker 3: I apologize for that.
Speaker 3: All right, last thing, last thing.
Speaker 3: Going back to you, what was the turning point for you?
Ashley St. Clair: There were, I get this question a lot.
Ashley St. Clair: There wasn't, it was cumulatively and then there were.
Ashley St. Clair: was a moment that was like, oh, I have to choose if I want to be a good person.
Ashley St. Clair: So like cumulatively, I saw so many things that I was uncomfortable with.
Ashley St. Clair: But because like the infrastructure of a cult is that everything in your life is around it, like your finances, your social community, everything.
Ashley St. Clair: So changing your political beliefs is blowing up your entire life.
Ashley St. Clair: It wasn't just like, oh, I believe something different.
Ashley St. Clair: I'm punching like the most powerful people in the world in the face.
Ashley St. Clair: But when I was offered the NDA and $40 million, I had to sit there and say,
Ashley St. Clair: What do I believe like is this do I want to trade being materially comfortable for like doing what's right and so that was
Ashley St. Clair: a choice that I had to make like then.
Ashley St. Clair: But if I hadn't had the experiences cumulatively of like seeing the things that I did, I don't know that I would have come to the decision.
Ashley St. Clair: But it's really hard to leave a situation like that.
Ashley St. Clair: And I feel so much regret for being a part of
Ashley St. Clair: that rhetoric and like I read some of the old things and I'm like, I feel like it's not, I feel so dissociated from it because I feel like it was just so nasty and I contributed to so much harm, but
Ashley St. Clair: I'm just happy to be out and to like consume real information and real books and like be around real people.
Ashley St. Clair: In my life again instead of like just MAGA people like that was my my whole life was MAGA for like since I was a teen
Ashley St. Clair: And so then I'm out.
Ashley St. Clair: And it was...
Ashley St. Clair: I'd rather that over the private planes any day.
Speaker 3: Okay.
Speaker 3: Ashley St.
Speaker 3: Clair, everybody, thank you so much for coming on.
Ashley St. Clair: Of course.
Speaker 3: This was great.
Ashley St. Clair: Enjoy the pastries.
Ashley St. Clair: They're actually really good.
Speaker 3: I hope I wasn't too ruthless to you with the exception of that one comment.
Speaker 3: You cooked yourself with the memes.
Ashley St. Clair: You weren't supposed to scroll.
Ashley St. Clair: You're like so invasive.
Speaker 3: Yeah, I know.
Ashley St. Clair: Do gaming.
Ashley St. Clair: I game.
Ashley St. Clair: I do game a little.
Speaker 3: I don't.
Speaker 3: They always yell at me for it.
Speaker 3: I used to, but I don't have time anymore.
Ashley St. Clair: We'll do Fortnite Friday with Connor.
Speaker 3: Hell yeah.
Ashley St. Clair: Okay, thank you.
Ashley St. Clair: I'm gonna go toodaloo.
Speaker 3: Okay.
Ashley St. Clair: Wait, do you want me to move this?
Speaker 3: No, no, I got it.
Speaker 3: Don't worry about it.
Speaker 3: Thank you, thank you so much.
Speaker 3: Here, I'll walk you out.
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, he's a gentleman.
Speaker 3: Yes.
Ashley St. Clair: Your legs are really tall.
Speaker 3: Hassan Reaction is one of the best ones in the React channel.