David Pakman: I'm very interested today in speaking with Ashley St.
David Pakman: Clair, social media content creator, former MAGA firebrand, now speaking out against the movement.
David Pakman: Ashley, I really appreciate your time.
David Pakman: Thanks for being on.
Ashley St. Clair: Of course.
Ashley St. Clair: Thank you, David.
Ashley St. Clair: I told you off air, but my mom loves your show.
Ashley St. Clair: So you're a we love your mom.
Ashley St. Clair: Hi to Ashley's mom.
David Pakman: What tell me this.
David Pakman: What how do you get pulled into the MAGA activism to start with?
David Pakman: Like, does someone recruit you?
David Pakman: Does it surface naturally from social media posts?
Ashley St. Clair: For me, it started as a combination of both, both on my college campus and on social media.
Ashley St. Clair: So being Gen Z, I was chronically online.
Ashley St. Clair: So I'm inundated with the Twitter sphere and that sort of content.
Ashley St. Clair: And then I was also 18 years old in college and pulled into the Young Americans for Liberty and the Turning Point campus chapters.
Ashley St. Clair: And combining that with the right-leaning conservative post, it was very quickly that I got invited to my first Turning Point event.
Ashley St. Clair: I'm getting my own special graphics.
Ashley St. Clair: They're promoting my tweets.
Ashley St. Clair: I'm meeting Don Jr.
Ashley St. Clair: And Charlie Kirk, and they're texting me, telling me I'm doing a great job.
Ashley St. Clair: And at that time, something I discuss quite often about it is I was very vulnerable.
Ashley St. Clair: I was a very insecure and broken 18-year-old who came to college trying to find herself and what's supposed to be an exploratory journey.
Ashley St. Clair: I was very quickly wrapped up in what I believe is a cult in which my identity was formed.
Ashley St. Clair: for me.
Ashley St. Clair: So that social validation and the social media validation was very appealing to me at that age.
David Pakman: So you were getting all of this positive feedback about what you were doing, which then reinforced your beliefs that what you're doing must be good, which then fueled your commitment to keep doing it is what I'm hearing.
Ashley St. Clair: Yes, especially at that age when you're young, the the acceptance of the crowd is really important.
Ashley St. Clair: So it didn't matter if I was getting detractors because I'm like, look, I have a thousand people in my comments who are telling me I'm right and good job.
Ashley St. Clair: So, you know, that kind of.
Ashley St. Clair: Foregoes critical thinking about your own opinions.
Ashley St. Clair: You're like, look at all the people I have on my side.
Ashley St. Clair: And when you're that young and you're getting 10,000 followers, we kind of get immune to the number on the screen now in our current age.
Ashley St. Clair: But when you're that young and you see you have 10,000 people, you're like, oh my God, I have a stadium of people who love me.
Ashley St. Clair: And then it's 20, 40, 100.
Ashley St. Clair: And so that just compounds the issue upon itself.
David Pakman: One of the we're going to get to kind of the logistics of how it operated.
David Pakman: But I do think it's very interesting that you're describing it as cult like.
David Pakman: But one of the things I've spoken about is that the political right knows what it's doing in terms of getting people young and also organizing these events that make people feel like they're part of something like we can debate whether this is even a good thing in general.
David Pakman: But there seems to be a huge asymmetry where like the left doesn't really have this stuff.
David Pakman: And I think that what you're you're sort of the example of why in 2024, young men, 18 to 29, went for Trump at a greater level than in any recent election.
David Pakman: I mean, they do know what they're doing to a great degree.
Ashley St. Clair: Yes.
Ashley St. Clair: And especially for the young men in 2024, like this is on the heels of like the Andrew Tate-isms of it all.
Ashley St. Clair: And these young men are really looking for a community or validation or a sense of identity.
Ashley St. Clair: They're like, who am I?
Ashley St. Clair: What does it mean to be a man?
Ashley St. Clair: You know, Matt Walsh is like, what is a woman?
Ashley St. Clair: But they can't define what a man is.
Ashley St. Clair: They're all very confused about what it means to be a man.
Ashley St. Clair: And so they find this validation in these social circles of MAGA, in which I did as well.
Ashley St. Clair: It's and I describe it as cult, like because of the entire infrastructure of it, it's.
Ashley St. Clair: If you're to leave, you're not just changing your vote or your political opinion.
Ashley St. Clair: You're blowing up your entire life, my social circles, my friends, my income, all of the above.
Ashley St. Clair: And there's also a very coordinated effort to sequester these people off from information that runs counter to it.
Ashley St. Clair: So right away, you know, we saw in 2015, 2016, fake news, don't trust the media.
Ashley St. Clair: Charlie Kirk starts the professor watch list that you should be critical of your professors.
Ashley St. Clair: Don't trust them either.
Ashley St. Clair: Don't trust these institutions.
Ashley St. Clair: Trust Truth Social and Twitter more than the New York Times.
Ashley St. Clair: And, you know, of course, these institutions and media outlets are subject to.
Ashley St. Clair: the same human flaw or fault of bias that anyone else is, but they are much more reputable than truth social posts.
David Pakman: Can you talk a little bit about the speculation that if you look online, you often see hurled about all sorts of different influencers and they could be anywhere on the political spectrum.
David Pakman: They are saying what they're saying because it's lucrative.
David Pakman: They're getting paid for saying certain things.
David Pakman: Is it really that simple?
David Pakman: Like, is there money available just for saying stuff or is it really, hey, you're going to be a content creator for a particular company.
David Pakman: So like you're getting paid for your work or talk a little bit about those dynamics.
David Pakman: Like, is it lucrative?
Ashley St. Clair: There's several things going on.
Ashley St. Clair: So it is lucrative for some people and there's different avenues in which they monetize this.
Ashley St. Clair: Like people like Benny Johnson are making six figures a month on Facebook monetization alone.
Ashley St. Clair: Obviously, there's the sponsorship deals in this.
Ashley St. Clair: There's also the paid campaigns for influencers in which they get paid for tweets, for messaging that they never have to disclose because of our current FEC rules and regulations.
Ashley St. Clair: If it's not a good or a product, they don't have to disclose it.
Ashley St. Clair: So they don't have to disclose any of this.
David Pakman: But it's also it's not let me just let me pause one thing because I want to make sure I understood that part.
David Pakman: My understanding was if it's not a good or a product, they don't need to do an FTC disclosure.
Ashley St. Clair: Yes.
David Pakman: And if it's not FEC would govern if it's for a candidate.
David Pakman: But again, if there's no active candidate or good or service, I think then there's no disclosure required.
Ashley St. Clair: Yes, that.
Ashley St. Clair: That's a correct clarification.
Ashley St. Clair: Okay.
Ashley St. Clair: I always mix up the letters, all the letters.
Ashley St. Clair: It never makes you feel more dyslexic.
Ashley St. Clair: So, and they don't have to disclose this.
Ashley St. Clair: And there's also, it's lucrative for some, right?
Ashley St. Clair: But for most, you're just getting the bare minimum.
Ashley St. Clair: You're really not making bank off of this.
Ashley St. Clair: But simultaneously, they have very bad Google search results now.
Ashley St. Clair: Being a MAGA influencer, they're going to have a hard time getting a job when they're posting racist stuff online all day or posting.
Ashley St. Clair: So then it compounds on itself where, okay, maybe it's not that lucrative, but what other option do I have?
Ashley St. Clair: Because now I've kind of put myself in this bubble.
Ashley St. Clair: So when I talk about it being the infrastructure of the cult, they're very financially dependent, even if it's not lucrative.
Ashley St. Clair: Again, for many it is.
Ashley St. Clair: They're getting paid thousands of dollars for tweets and posts and this and that.
Ashley St. Clair: But for the majority of these people, it's not that lucrative, but they don't have any other options and they are financially dependent because of the structure of MAGA on MAGA.
Ashley St. Clair: So again, leaving is not just changing an opinion.
Ashley St. Clair: It's blowing up your entire life.
David Pakman: One of the big aspects that's kind of intertwined with all this is the way that this content is pushed out on the social media platforms, which kind of takes us to X.
David Pakman: And in the midst of all of this influencing, you had this brief relationship with Elon Musk.
David Pakman: Is this all related in the sense of he was pulled into Trump's universe for a while?
David Pakman: You were doing the MAGA thing.
David Pakman: I mean, how?
David Pakman: How do these things even come together?
Ashley St. Clair: So the Twitter algorithm, the X algorithm, is incredibly concerning because it undoubtedly is pushed towards really extremist right-wing content right now.
Ashley St. Clair: But I think this fixation on Elon because of his own really right-wing slop ideas.
Ashley St. Clair: Ignores the other issues who are actors in this, like Mark Zuckerberg, who are bankrolling this.
Ashley St. Clair: These individuals, these right-wing figures are making so much money on Facebook.
Ashley St. Clair: They're making so much money on YouTube.
Ashley St. Clair: And so they're being bankrolled by most of these big tech platforms.
Ashley St. Clair: And then X is more concerning.
Ashley St. Clair: Twitter is more concerning in terms of like the behavioral inference for our elections and what's happening there and the propaganda aspect of it.
Ashley St. Clair: In terms of the financial aspect, the other big tech companies are certainly accountable there too.
David Pakman: So when you were at the peak, I guess we would call it of your MAGA influencing, that's when you came into contact directly with Elon Musk while you were also putting content out on X.
Ashley St. Clair: Yes.
Ashley St. Clair: I was at I was working for Seth Dillon at the Babylon Bee at the time.
David Pakman: And the eventual falling out with Musk, did that hurt your reach as a MAGA influencer?
David Pakman: And if I'm getting the timing of this slightly wrong, then you tell me.
David Pakman: But did that coincide also with you starting to have a diminished reach?
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, absolutely.
Ashley St. Clair: It.
Ashley St. Clair: And I knew it would.
Ashley St. Clair: When I made choices that I did in terms of coming out publicly regarding certain matters that I can only discuss in a very limited context, but I knew that was going to happen.
Ashley St. Clair: I was very aware that there would be repercussions for me speaking out and being public about certain matters.
Ashley St. Clair: And my reach was diminished significantly.
Ashley St. Clair: But then that happened again because now I'm suing XAI because Grok had undressed me, including photos of me as a child.
Ashley St. Clair: And once I did that, I then lost my blue check.
Ashley St. Clair: I was demonetized.
Ashley St. Clair: So this is just like a longstanding issue that's been happening.
Ashley St. Clair: But yeah, certainly it was that reach was diminished.
Ashley St. Clair: But it wasn't just me.
Ashley St. Clair: I watched this occur behind the scenes to many detractors of the owner of that platform
Ashley St. Clair: in which once there was a scuffle or something that he disagreed with, he would direct the engineers to de-checkmark them or de-boost them, what have you.
David Pakman: I'm getting we're going to move on from this, but I'm getting the sense from how you're hesitant to even say the name Elon Musk.
David Pakman: Is there an agreement in place that limits your ability to talk with me fully about that aspect?
Ashley St. Clair: I can't.
Ashley St. Clair: I'm just not at liberty to discuss certain things, because, as you know, there's there's a child involved.
Ashley St. Clair: So I cannot discuss certain matters.
David Pakman: I got it.
Ashley St. Clair: As much as I would like to.
David Pakman: Fair, fair.
David Pakman: When it comes to pick one issue.
David Pakman: For a while, you were like a big anti-trans activist.
David Pakman: And as I understand this,
David Pakman: You've now reversed your views on that and even expressed some regrets about that.
David Pakman: Did you how did you come to focus in on that issue?
David Pakman: Was there was I don't want to call it pressure necessarily, but like, were you encouraged that like, hey, here's an emotionally salient issue you could be posting and talking about?
Ashley St. Clair: I think that's part of it.
Ashley St. Clair: You see the engagement that it's getting, but also the way in which it is presented to you is very much presented like propaganda.
Ashley St. Clair: You see these extreme cases about an issue that you are not educated on, particularly involving trans youth.
Ashley St. Clair: And so you see these really extreme examples and they will post the most heinous content online and make that representative of an entire community.
Ashley St. Clair: So you really believe that this is the case.
Ashley St. Clair: And then your perception, you're looking for this confirmation bias in everything that you see.
Ashley St. Clair: And I was coming from a deep place of ignorance and thinking that this was the most important issue.
Ashley St. Clair: It's framed as, you know, we're protecting women and children.
Ashley St. Clair: And of course, this is the only time that the right wing and MAGA will ever say that they care about women and children.
Ashley St. Clair: And so you really get caught up in that.
Ashley St. Clair: But I have great remorse for my role in that and the harm that I've caused.
Ashley St. Clair: And I'm hoping that at least.
Ashley St. Clair: Humbling myself to take accountability and try to right those wrongs and make amends in my local community will help others who potentially feel the same way that I did at certain times while I was in MAGA.
David Pakman: Do you have insight when it comes to whether it's the trans issue or any issue?
David Pakman: How much of the apparent audience and engagement of some of these creators is what we might call organic and how much of it is artificial in the sense that there are players paying to boost this content, if the question makes sense?
Ashley St. Clair: It's both.
Ashley St. Clair: Yes, I think it's both.
Ashley St. Clair: There's also discussions.
Ashley St. Clair: I still have the text messages with various MAGA creators in which we're discussing trans content and the conversation is like, oh, that will fly.
Ashley St. Clair: Oh, that will do well.
Ashley St. Clair: That will do numbers.
Ashley St. Clair: And so it's very much dehumanized and viewed in the context of content and numbers.
Ashley St. Clair: And there are not only individuals, but organizations that will fund content or messaging campaigns regarding the trans issue, regarding, and they've made it an issue.
Ashley St. Clair: I say trans issue, but it's not an issue.
Ashley St. Clair: The trans panic, I will say.
Ashley St. Clair: And this is very prolific throughout MAGA.
David Pakman: Last thing I want to ask you about, we saw after the White House Correspondents Dinner shooting that immediately everybody's tweeting about this proves we need the ballroom.
David Pakman: And to some people, that was evidence that the shooting was staged.
David Pakman: I don't happen to believe that.
David Pakman: I believe that this was an opportunism that took place and that there is coordination as to the messaging.
David Pakman: You were part of witnessing that coordination, right?
David Pakman: Can you tell us about that?
Ashley St. Clair: They have these group chats and these group chats.
Ashley St. Clair: Let me be clear.
Ashley St. Clair: There's there's group chats with just very big mega influencers.
Ashley St. Clair: There's group chats with members of the.
Ashley St. Clair: administration, people like James Blair, members of the Trump family that are in these group chats, in which they coordinate their messaging and responses to these things.
Ashley St. Clair: The Trump campaign would do calls with influencers unpaid, in which they would just direct them on the messaging.
Ashley St. Clair: Others are paid.
Ashley St. Clair: And there's also the social validation aspect of, oh, I'm now added to this group chat with Eric Trump or this member from the administration, and they want me to tweet this.
Ashley St. Clair: And so there's that social validation aspect as well, and you'll get a retweet from them.
Ashley St. Clair: But in regards to the ballroom, I saw all of that discourse as well and people saying that it's staged.
Ashley St. Clair: But there's really only two options.
Ashley St. Clair: There's either they're so stupid that they all saw this objectively and came up with this in a vacuum that they saw this horrific situation and said Trump needs a ballroom or it's coordinated.
Ashley St. Clair: So there's...
Ashley St. Clair: In either one, they're either stupid or coordinated or both.
David Pakman: I lean towards both.
David Pakman: That's my instinct.
David Pakman: All right.
David Pakman: Ashley St.
David Pakman: Clair, really appreciate your time, your insights.
David Pakman: We'll link to Ashley's various profiles online.
David Pakman: Do not.
Ashley St. Clair: Do not link to my profiles.
Ashley St. Clair: Do not link to them.
Ashley St. Clair: I am just suggesting the current books that I'm recommending are Evil Geniuses and Dark Money.
Ashley St. Clair: I prefer to.
Ashley St. Clair: Both great books.
Ashley St. Clair: Yes.
Ashley St. Clair: Fantastic books.
Ashley St. Clair: So I want to promote reading books cover to cover and thoughts in their entirety.
Ashley St. Clair: If people find me, they find me.
Speaker 3: But thank you so much, David.
David Pakman: Well, I recommend reading this cover to cover as well.
David Pakman: We're united on that.
David Pakman: All right.
David Pakman: Thank you so much for your time.
David Pakman: I appreciate it.
Speaker 3: Thanks, David.