Today, we have a little bit of a different kind of guest.
She spent 10 years as a top influencer in the MAGA world, helping to elect Donald Trump, served as a brand ambassador for Turning Point USA, was a political commentator, and is maybe most well known for having a child with the world's richest man, Elon Musk.
And now she has turned her back on all of them and has been telling all.
Ashley St. Clair, welcome to Haley on the Go.
Hey, everyone, welcome back to Haley on the Go.
This is Haley.
This is your weekly podcast where we talk to the people you care most about, about the issues that matter most to you.
Make sure to follow and subscribe wherever you get your podcasts to never miss an episode.
Episodes drop every single Thursday.
Let's dive right in.
Hello, hello, Haley.
Is this what the kids call like frame-mogging because you are in stark contrast to me right now?
You look amazing as well.
You look so wonderful and put together and I'm in a hoodie here, but thank you for having me, Haley.
No, thanks for taking the time.
I really appreciate it.
I think I, like so many people, have been really enamored, I would say, with your public divorce with MAGA and its leadership and the details you have been sharing about its internal coordination, how it develops influencers, share specific talking points.
And I want to dive into all of that with you.
It's so fascinating.
Before we do, I would like to spend a little bit of time talking about you and your journey into this space to help my audience learn more about you and also learn why they should trust you or not trust you.
I think you can be a bit of a polarizing figure.
You spent more than a third of your life sharing some really hateful rhetoric and messages against minority communities, but these are viewpoints that you now publicly have apologized for and said you have immense guilt over.
And I know disavowing these beliefs have come at immense both financial and physical risk for yourself, and we'll talk more about that.
But how did you get to the point of even being a MAGA influencer and sort of the face, a face, for this movement?
Yeah, of course.
I want to start off by prefacing that I'm not looking for anybody to trust me.
I know there's just going to be people who don't, and I'm not, when I speak about these things, I'm not looking to garner now a left-wing audience or get trust, but rather just speak openly and honestly about my own experiences throughout this MAGA, what I believe is a cult, because I did get involved very young.
I first got involved in this as a teenager when I first started college at 18 years old and started going to my first turning point events at 19, 20 years old.
And when you're that age and you have, you're supposed to be forming your own identity and being independent and you're out of the house for the first time, and you're getting swept up in this, this new sense of identity and you have all of these followers and these high up figures.
It was very quickly that I was pulled into and in the same room with Charlie Kirk and all of these figures who are then kind of molding you.
I still have the texts of Charlie going through my Twitter page and saying, hey, maybe post this or go this direction, don't do this.
And so it was, it all happened very, very quickly while I'm in college and simultaneously doing beer bongs and then having Charlie, you know, guide me on what to say.
And I'm going to these events and I'm a special guest and I'm like a micro e-celeb within the MAGA world.
And it just kind of snowballed.
Something people need to understand about the pathologies of cults and the structure, the architecture of cults is that it was a lot more than just my political opinions.
Those were very much shaped by older men I dated, older men who were influencing me and my own need for validation and acceptance as a young girl.
Yeah.
But the structure of this cult is that you are also dependent on them financially.
For me to leave was not just for me to change my political beliefs, but to blow my entire life up, to lose all career opportunities, what little I had of it left.
But it wasn't as simple as just leaving.
And so I'm hoping to give people a more nuanced view into what that experience was.
And I know that's also going to be detrimental to me because if I am just going to sit here, I could have a very nice career if I just sat here and denounced MAGA and now I'm this left-wing advisor.
But rather I want to tell people where I went wrong and the places where I should have spoke up that I didn't, the places that I chose material comfort over doing what was right and why some people make those decisions.
And I think it's tremendous to use your voice that way because it's a cautionary tale that a lot of people need to hear.
You were so young and being exposed to beliefs, to power, to affirmation, to money is something really hard at a young age to have the ability to turn away from.
So it's important that we're sharing these stories.
We're talking about what's happening because so much of life right now exists on the internet and people turn to the internet for comfort, for community, for all of these things.
So I appreciate that.
There is a deep question, and I know you touched upon you're not looking for people to trust you, which I think that is a good perspective to have, although I think you've been very honest about your experiences, is there is a deep question around the grift.
And you've exposed sort of some of the pay-to-play and we'll dive deeper into that.
But how much of the push and pull of like, do I leave, do I stay was the money versus genuine beliefs that you had?
And during the time period, even before you were considering leaving, how much of it was the opportunity versus the belief system?
It's kind of both because there are moments where you question things and then you have these older, more respectable figures who kind of pull you back in and say, here's why you shouldn't divert from these ideologies.
Here's why you're wrong.
And simultaneously, leaving is really scary because my most recent child was not my first child.
I had my older son in 2021.
So to leave that was to destroy my ability to feed my son, to have a roof over our head.
And again, I don't say any of this to excuse the behavior, but rather to shine a light on why some people don't leave sooner.
It's really difficult because at this point I had and still have one of the worst digital footprints imaginable.
So it's very hard to go get a job at Starbucks or Pinterest when you have this digital footprint that is so horrific and you have things that are hateful towards groups of co-workers you might have as a barista.
It's not as simple as, oh, well, why don't you just tumble yourself and flip burgers?
They don't even want me to flip burgers when I'm saying the things that I was.
And so it is really, really difficult to leave that environment when you have said the things that you have.
And not to excuse anything that anyone says at any age, but the internet really awards that kind of extremism content and fuels views, likes, engagement, especially certain platforms based off of how extreme you are on either side.
And so as you start to see that kind of reward, it's easy to go probably push yourself deeper and deeper.
Well, it's much more than just, I don't like when people frame it as just the likes and the dopamine, which it is, right?
They design these social media platforms like slot machines.
You slide it and you get the dopamine hit from your notifications, but it's also a feedback loop of affirmation for what you're saying, for your ideologies where you have, it doesn't matter if this person agrees with me because I have 5,000 people who agree with me and some of the top figures.
So it's also this feedback loop of affirmation of your own opinions, as well as what is really pertinent throughout MAGA.
One of the first things they did was they cut off your access to information, right?
They tell you to distrust your professors.
They had the professor watch list where you're always listening to make sure, ooh, this professor can now be content.
I can report this professor.
Distrust the news.
It's fake news.
Trust nothing except truth social and Twitter.
So your access to information is cut off.
And then your only information is this feedback loop from people who are affirming these really bad ideas.
So in the moment, it doesn't feel like you're doing something hateful.
And for me, it took me stepping back to really see the gravity of the harm that I had caused and the hatefulness of a lot of that rhetoric.
Because in the moment, you're being affirmed that this is the strong and mighty path and that you're a part of a good movement.
I'm not sure how into philosophy you are, but when you look back on it, it's like Thrasymachus yelling at Socrates that might is right.
And that is very much the pathology of MAGA that they pull you into.
And what you said about sort of removing your pathways to knowledge is so true.
And it goes beyond the proliferation of the concept of fake news, but even goes so far as to say you shouldn't trust science.
You shouldn't trust subject matter experts.
So we're seeing that and the impact.
It's also they want you to ignore the larger structure of things, especially as it relates to capitalism.
They want you to believe that if you have socialist beliefs, then socialists don't have any nice things.
And that couldn't be further from the truth, right?
Or they want you to ignore CRT or critical race theory because that does expose the larger structure of capitalism and what's happening now.
They don't want you to know that the Silicon Valley bros and the men on Wall Street would be very proficient in plantation accounting because it's the same language.
And so they really, this is why they have the war on the Department of Education and this access to information.
100%.
And one of the people who controls a platform and a lot of this information is Elon Musk.
He is a father to 13 children that we know of with a bunch of different partners.
You had a child with him and now are engaged in a custody battle.
So I know you may not be able to answer questions about him, but I would like to talk a little bit about it and maybe answer what you can.
And if not, we will move on.
But you had a child with Elon in September of 2024, which was peak election season, about two months ahead of November.
And he was instrumental in helping get Trump elected.
Elon Musk spent approximately $288 million to support Donald Trump, making him the top individual donor in the country.
What was it like being in contact with him during that time?
And to the extent that you were in contact or exposed to him, what is your opinion on why he was so invested in making sure Trump was president?
I, you know, again, I'm not at liberty to discuss a lot of items related to this as much as I would like to.
But I think people need to understand that any of these tech bros surrounding Donald Trump during the inauguration are not doing this out of altruism or actual convictions, but rather because they're getting something out of it.
These Silicon Valley tech oligarchs are the most self-interested people in the world.
Okay, you want to talk about gold diggers, nobody has dug more gold than them.
They're at the top of the list for digging the most gold and extracting the most resources.
So people really need to understand what's happening, especially with our social media platforms.
And I've described social media and AI at times as kind of the final terrain of extraction for capitalism.
And they are really doing this last pillage on what I believe is our consciousness and our souls, because there's, they don't have as much labor to extract.
And so now they're extracting us.
And I think people need to be very invested in their own data rights and their own rights to their personhood.
And I talk a lot on this platform and on my pages about AI and the dangers that they pose, especially to women, which we will talk more about, because I know that you have had experiences with it.
But I did want to ask a little bit more during Trump and Elon sort of public fallout last year, you were already estranged or publicly feuding with Elon and you tweeted, hey, at real Donald Trump, let me know if you need any breakup advice, which was funny.
So I have to ask how you knowing both of them, personally, to some extent, do you think they're actually broken up?
Or was that sort of a ruse or distraction?
I'm not sure.
I don't know the details.
So I'm kind of against hypothesizing about it too much.
But what I would say is these are both very, they're very similar.
So two bulls in a China shop doesn't really work.
Okay, very fair.
Good insight.
My last Elon question and we'll move on because I want to learn more about you.
Your journey is we know Elon's on a mission to repopulate the world.
He's even gone so far as to say he would donate his sperm to people.
And there are rumors that he has purchased his own compound or cold in Austin to ask all his baby mamas to live there.
Can you confirm or deny if that's a real thing?
I cannot speak about it.
It's totally okay.
I understand the intrigue.
No, I had to ask because I do find it really intriguing that a party that is sort of based on family values has so many people so closely related to them that does not display those sort quote unquote traditional values.
No, but they will.
They will place them on women, right?
So I was the one who was at the receiving end of Oh, you single mom whore, this and that.
When this news broke, the one the onus for family values was primarily placed on me, and not the man in that situation.
So I, that is, I think, really common in society, whether it's MAGA or not, just placing this sort of unfair, unequal standard on women, on women of color, and just holding them above where we hold men.
And I want to dive deeper into your experiences with MAGA and what you've sort of exposed on social media.
Before we do that, last year, you publicly sold your Tesla for money and said that was because Elon Musk cut your son's child support payments by 60% as punishment for disobedience.
And this is something I know you cannot comment on, but has sort of been wildly reported on as a tactic of his.
So just before we dive in, what would you say to the people now who sort of question like you were in it for the money, and then the way that they say it are not in for the money, but money opportunities.
And then as sort of people say, the leopard ate your face.
And now you're like reverse grifting.
What would your response to be those people?
Well, first of all, I'm not at liberty to discuss anything involving custody for obvious reasons.
But there is a large cohort who is saying, oh, she's grifting now.
I'm not making any money off of this.
I've turned down enough money to be like the GDP of a small nation at this point.
I'm back in school with plans to go to law school.
I'm not putting TikTok shoplinks on my get ready with me's.
And even since coming out against MAGA, I have received offers from center left and left leaning organizations to be a paid spokesperson on TV and basically say what I'm saying now, but be paid.
And I've declined that because I think I need to right the wrongs of my past.
And I don't want to be paid for what's coming out of my mouth anymore.
I want to rebuild an actual career and go back to school and go to law school and hopefully do effective advocacy work within the system that I think is responsible for a lot of this harm.
And I respect that.
And I truly do believe that we have to create a space for people to be able to change their minds, to grow, to learn.
You were so young when you were exposed.
And if we don't allow people to publicly change their minds, then we will never advance and move away from where we are right now.
So I am grateful that you're speaking out against both where your viewpoints were at one time, but also the system that helped created it.
And I will say too, you know, there's obviously there were things that I did for money that were not okay, specifically as it relates to these paid influencer campaigns.
However, I also think there's a piece of that that ignores the abusive financial coercion that happens within these structures of cults like MAGA or any other cult where that is necessary for so many people.
And again, it does not excuse it.
However, this structure is incredibly deliberate to keep people involved.
And they, to my understanding or knowledge, oftentimes do kind of pry off of young people who are in need of financial support or assistance or security in that way.
So yeah, I don't know that there's any more vulnerable, you know, malleable brain than young college kids or young students.
Now they're going into high schools with turning point and saying, you know, you don't need school, just work for us, just be a professional MAGA spokesperson.
That's incredibly predatory, especially when you're staring down student loan debt, about economy, you know, security is so key.
You have been opening up about sort of the way that MAGA has helped mold young people's voices and the experiences within.
Can you talk a little bit about what coordination you saw and experienced?
There were different levers and facets of coordination.
As I had mentioned in, you know, previous appearances that I've done, they have a lot of paid campaigns.
So these influencers are paid just to put out messaging, to put links out to news sites, and they don't have to disclose any of this because of our current FEC regulations and loopholes.
They do not have to disclose anything that's not really like a product, a good, or a service.
And so they are able to do a lot of this coordinated messaging.
There's also these coordinated group chats and campaign calls and calls with the Trump team that I was on, in which they really direct the messaging and say, hey, here's how we respond to this, or don't respond to this, and put out those talking points that way.
And then there's also a more undiscussed is that once some of these big figureheads are given the talking points, it puts the rest of the micro influencers in line to get that social media engagement because they're like, oh, maybe I'll get a retweet from, you know, the big guy or what have you.
So while it's coordinated and they're paid and there's facets of this that are coordinated, it then trickles down to get the rest of the MAGA influencer base in line.
And I think that this coordination is something that people on the left suspected was happening for a long time, but didn't 100% know necessarily that it was.
Are you able to quantify at all some of those payment numbers you have seen?
Not saying that that was you personally, but just- It can go anywhere from a couple hundred, you know, a few hundred dollars for a tweet to tens of thousands of dollars, $100,000.
Like it is, I was offered a very large chunk of change, even just to promote Rick Grinnell for Secretary of State.
They do this down to admin picks, to messaging, to what have you.
Some of it is like per view, some of it's per click, but there is a lot of money flowing through this.
And they also make an insane amount of money on social media monetization, specifically Facebook.
That was very, very prominent.
Mark Zuckerberg and Facebook are responsible for lining the pockets of most of these right-wing propagandists.
They're making anywhere from five to six figures a month on Facebook video monetization.
Yeah.
It's crazy to think about.
More than the money, what I was really fascinated with what you shared was these group chats because the message coordination amongst people on the right is frankly impressive.
And anyone who says otherwise, like it's been very effective.
And recently I saw my newsfeed filled with anti-birth control propaganda.
That was the exact same language, the exact same sentence from dozens of influencers and creators.
I was wondering if you knew or could speak to who's like the mastermind behind this messaging?
Because there's a few people involved in the anti-birth control discussion.
And I know that because I had been speaking out about informed consent for women because I had a really bad experience on birth control.
It led to more severe depression.
Which is real.
Yes, it is real.
But at the end of the day, women just deserve informed consent and knowing what they're getting into rather than birth control is evil or like Charlie Kirk had said that it's like black tar heroin.
That's just insane.
But there's Peter Thiel money involved here.
And I am very aware of Peter Thiel being involved in one organization in particular that is pushing this anti-birth control messaging.
We talk about EBU on this podcast.
I'll name it if you can't, don't worry.
He's very involved in that.
And then when I was putting out some of this messaging just about the different symptoms that the hormonal birth control pill can cause, Elon had actually offered me, he said, this is something that my foundation can fund.
This is, would you like to do a documentary on this?
Would you like to do this?
And he was offering money for this.
I ended up not going through with that, but there is money being poured into the anti-birth control pronatalist messaging and a lot of it.
A lot of it.
We know that this is really a priority for a lot of men around the Trump administration right now, but in general, justice coordinated messaging.
I find it hard to believe these group chats are being run by Trump.
They're very effective.
And so was curious for an insight behind, a little look behind the hood.
So since speaking out, you have been a target of an AI deepfake campaign on Grok, Elon's website.
And I spent a lot of time on my platform talking about the significant dangers of deepfakes to women, according to research from the Center for Countering Digital Hate.
Over a span of just 11 days that they reviewed, Grok generated approximately 3 million sexualized images.
23,000 appeared to depict children.
This reflected an estimated average pace of one sexualized image of a minor every 40 seconds.
I know you are currently also in the midst of a lawsuit around what happened here too.
And being an advocate around the prolific issue right now with deepfakes targeting women, are you able to talk at all about what happened to you in this?
Yeah, of course.
So right now, we have initiated a lawsuit in New York against XAI and Grok for these deepfake images that were made of me.
And when we say deepfake, I do think it dilutes how hyper-realistic this was.
There were real items from my home, including my son's backpack, in the images where I am undressed, turned around, bent over.
Like there is only, it looks like a piece of dental floss covering my entire bottom half.
And videos that look hyper-realistic.
And I can't even tell you how many there are that I will never be able to unsee of not just myself as an adult, but as a child.
There were images of me at 14 that were undressed.
And other children, I saw a girl that looked about four years old, who I watched the users say, you know, put her in a bluey micro print bikini, cover her in white sticky donut glaze.
And so now I don't even know whose daughter, whose child I saw, like four years old, undressed and covered in what's supposed to be semen.
And there is no accountability for this.
Our own government, because of who's in power, is not doing anything about this.
There's obviously prosecutions and probes in Europe and in France.
It's geo-targeted, yeah.
Yes.
We have to protect our women and children and our citizens here from this abuse, because it's prolific.
And now, of course, they're countersuing me because they claim that me even initiating a lawsuit is a terms of service violation against XAI.
So now I'm dealing with a countersuit in the northern district of Texas, where the only judge owns Tesla stocks.
And they are claiming that I owe a minimum of $75,000 in anticipatory damages for them having to fight this case in New York.
So they're even fighting victims.
And thankfully, I've been through the ringer enough that I'm okay to fight this.
But most victims are not.
And this is something that is spanning women across the world, but not just women, women and girls, whether it's women running for leadership, whether it's athletes, celebrities, or children in elementary schools.
This is something happening that people are experiencing everywhere.
And so the advocacy is necessary and the attention...
It pushes women out of the conversation too, because now we have less inputs into what they're training.
If we are to take their building, we don't know what with these AI systems, but these AI systems are trained on us and our inputs and what we're talking about on social media.
And so if you're removing women from the inputs, because they are scared to go on social media, because they may be sexually violated or undressed or harassed, then they have less of a voice to train a system that is supposed to be making recommendations for humanity.
And so they're building systems that are inherently going to be biased towards men, as they always have.
And when it comes to these systems, it's not just keeping us out of building the or building the actual AI, but it's making it so that women don't want to be on the platforms.
It's silencing voices.
We saw a report come out that female journalists are stopping to use certain platforms or holding back because they are afraid of retaliatory actions, like what happened to you, happening on these platforms in mass where deepfake news are made of them.
And so instead, it is silencing them, which I do believe is a goal of the men behind this kind of technology.
So all that to be said, I am sorry you're going through this.
Thank you for using this to talk about it publicly, though.
Yeah, of course.
And I could have.
I'm hoping if everything goes the way that it should, I'm hoping that it sets some sort of precedent that helps other women who were victimized by this.
And if anyone is a victim of it and you're in New York specifically, Kerry Goldberg, the attorney that I have on it, is fantastic.
Her email signature is literally fighting stalkers, pervs and internet trolls.
She's incredible and has been such a light throughout this situation.
Well, thank you for providing that resource.
And maybe we'll reach out and have her on the pod because she would love that.
Yeah.
Before I know we're running out of time, I have one more topic and then we'll make sure you get to end with a final note and kind of a message of what you want people to take away from your story.
But recently you came out about Madison Cawthorne, who is running for Congress again.
And in August 2020, during his past congressional campaign for Congress, several women accused him of sexually aggressive behavior, sexual misconduct, sexual assault.
In 2021, BuzzFeed investigation found 20 people who said that Cawthorne had harassed female classmates during college.
When he announced his new campaign, you shared that you had a personal experience with Cawthorne and that you had shared that with members of Madga, including Benny Johnson.
For a party that is predated on the concept of quote, protecting women, how much known inside cover up around predators is going on?
Oh, it's prolific.
There's people that are in the White House and on the admin now.
There's other members that are very involved in the policies of this administration that it's known that they are sexual predators and it is pushed under the rug or they're put in less public positions just so that there's not as much media coverage around them.
But it's prolific.
And that was one of the things that was the most difficult.
Having my own personal experience with Madison Cawthorne and then seeing those articles come out.
And I knew that those women were telling the truth.
And I couldn't.
I was at a company that he was a client of when my experience happened.
And I couldn't tell them like, you're not crazy.
You're right.
Like this.
This happened to me, too.
And instead, I watched Madga call these women crazy and just doing it for attention.
And that was incredibly difficult to watch.
And the best I can do now is speak about it now.
And I know that doesn't undo the harm of me not speaking out sooner.
But but it's it's prolific.
These systems don't just exist because of what you are one individual like these are systems that are going to take a really long time to break down.
And so thank you for for doing that and for sharing your story.
Both your experience.
But I'm also I'm also aware of, you know, the harm and the role that I played.
And I'm understanding that for many people, I'm the most accessible person they will ever have to Madga.
And so I understand them needing to vent those frustrations.
And like, I'm not getting offended by it.
I just want people to know I'm not grifting here.
I'm just talking about my experiences.
But I understand their their frustrations with me and the role that I played as well.
So I want to give you an opportunity to close us out with for the people who are listening who are following along.
Maybe they're frustrated.
Maybe they're they're interested in your story and how you're exposing and just shedding light on the way that Madga has been sort of, I would say grooming young voices from a young age to be part of their party and their movement.
What do you want the takeaway to be?
I think the takeaway should be it is so important to provide people with information.
Because again, that's one of the first things they do is cut off your access to information.
And I want them to know that there are very prominent women, especially who are on television for Madga, that are these Madga talking heads who have reached out to me in the last few weeks.
And they have said, I'm, I'm scared.
I'm really scared.
But I, I agree with you.
I want to speak out but I don't know what I'm going to do.
And I hope that despite how cruel and unempathetic many of these characters have been, including myself, to understand that it is a cult in a lot of ways.
And that there are a lot of people trying to leave.
And I do think that they need to take accountability for their own actions when and if they do leave.
But to understand that it's a lot more nuanced than just hate for cliques.
And that a lot of these individuals were groomed very young into this, and they're looking for a way out.
And I'm not sure exactly the the avenue for them to leave, but it's going to take a lot of work.
And I don't think pushing them further into that is going to be helpful in digging us out from the current hole that we've found ourselves in.
I agree.
I can understand people's hesitancy and anger that they feel towards these people, especially if they, you know, feel personally impacted or affected by language spoken.
But also if we want to move forward from the hateful rhetoric that I think is running the country right now, we have to allow people to change.
So thank you for using your voice, for sharing that message, for spending the time to come talk to us today, Ashley.
Of course, of course.
And I want to apologize again.
I'm such a scheduling nightmare, but you have been fantastic.
And I think you've been having, you know, very necessary conversations with your audience.
And congratulations on doing the right thing from the beginning, Hayley.
Some of us were not as lucky to have good parents guide me there.
Thank you.
I was very lucky to have parents guide me there.
But, you know, if any of the women talking to you are looking for a place to share their stories, send them our way.
But thank you, Ashley.
Of course.
Thank you so much, Hayley.
Talk soon.
Bye.