You've been outspoken about the coordinated campaigns that you say are driving MAGA accounts and influencers online.
You've done these TikTok videos that have gone viral, exposing some of the chats with some of your receipts.
Just to be clear, what is the accusation here for people who are not following you on TikTok?
Is it that MAGA influencers, the people you see on Twitter, the people who are pundits on cable news, they are all in one chat and they are getting specific talking points sent to them by Caroline Leavitt and the White House?
Well, there's not just one chat.
There's multiple chats that they operate in.
And these chats also have, some are just sequestered to large MAGA influencers in which they send these paid campaigns.
Others have members of the administration.
Others have, you know, the Trump children and they coordinate this messaging and react to things in real time.
Here's how we respond or don't respond to any given issue at any given time.
They also have paid campaigns in which messaging is pushed out.
And it is very much coordinated through both paid messaging and just wanting to be in the club and not be ostracized.
Were you in these chats yourself?
You've seen this firsthand?
Yes.
Those screenshots are from me.
I was in these chats.
And these chats are not just, you know, lower level freaks.
These are big names of the conservative media machine.
Members of Congress, members of the administration, people at the White House, people with the last name Trump.
Would someone like a Tucker Carlson have been in there until recently?
Tucker would not have been in something like this.
He doesn't really use social media.
But you mentioned, for example, the Trump children.
You're talking about Don and Eric are in these chats, getting right into what the talking point should be.
I was in one in which Eric was in one, yes.
And who's in charge of all this?
You say coordinated, like who is the person pulling all the strings?
So members of the administration, people like James Blair, who run messaging for the admin and the White House and the campaign.
And there's also people who run these consulting houses, these right wing consulting houses that push a lot of this out because they have some plausible deniability and they can hide the money.
So once the money goes from the campaign to the consulting house, they can then distribute it to the influencers.
And it's not on any FEC report.
So what you're basically saying is when I see a MAGA person online take any position, my starting point should be, is this really his position or did it come from the White House?
Is this really his position or was he paid for it?
Correct.
How much do you get paid for these things?
It depends on the influencer.
Some people will get more of these paid campaigns because they lower their rates and they're the lowest straight around.
But they can go from anywhere from a couple hundred dollars to thousands of dollars for these tweets.
I can get a MAGA influencer to tweet stuff I want for a couple of hundred bucks, like a cameo.
Oh, yes, you can.
Yes, you can.
Oh, wow.
Now I'm getting all sorts of ideas which I shouldn't have.