We need to talk about the rack on Kristi Noem's husband.
Get ready with me while I update you on the White Trash White House.
If you don't know who Kristi Noem is, she was the governor of South Dakota and essentially she was a professional culture war participant.
So she built a huge part of her brand on anti-woke, anti-trans, Christian, nationalist family values.
She signed and supported multiple policies and efforts restricting trans rights, particularly around youth health care and school.
So a very particular fixation on trans issues and what other people are allowed to do with their bodies, which gets very interesting.
Kristi also had a series of scandals before she entered the second Trump administration.
Most notably when she released her book, she said that she unaligned her dog with a...
because the dog was not trainable.
A little bit of a sociopath.
She married her husband very young.
I believe they were high school sweethearts, so the story goes.
And they were just promoting the genre, the typical Christian family values.
All the while, it's basically an open secret in MAGA and the Republican Party that she is also sleeping with Corey Lewandowski, who's also married.
So she gets appointed to run DHS, Department of Homeland Security, and go on this immigration tirade.
And throughout her time at DHS, she's really leaning heavily into the Bible.
She's defunding NGOs and organizations that don't promote Jesus, typical Christian nationalist stuff.
She's taking trips to El Salvador in full glam.
She's having taxpayer-funded trips with her little mistress, Corey, and pretending like none of this is happening.
So fast forward to this week, and it is revealed that Kristi Noem's husband is very into bimbofication play.
Basically, if you're not familiar with bimbofication, I, you know, congratulations on having a peaceful internet experience.
But basically, it's a fetish of over-feminization and exaggerated gender presentation.
So this guy is just pretending like he has massive tits, okay?
He's putting balloons with a little tie to the front so that they look like, I mean, these, these, I'll let you see the photos yourself.
So this has a lot of overlap, obviously, with everything that Kristi Noem has been publicly railing against.
And she wasted no time saying that she was blindsided by this, and she is devastated.
She wants prayers, you know, they just need prayers, which I'm not sure exactly what your family's, what prayers would you like?
Like, please God, stop my husband from being into having massive tits.
Like, what exactly is the request to God here?
But this is just, not only is it delicious irony, like, I love this, this made my week.
It just goes to show, especially with the Christian Nationalists and the Republicans who go on these moral crusades, and they don't have their own house in order.
They are, they are a wreck.
This is the white trash White House.
Okay, guys.
What I find incredible is how quickly Kristi Noem came out and confirmed these messages were from her husband, and that this was real.
Because, mind you, for years, her husband has been dealing with hearing that she is sleeping with Corey Lewandowski.
He even confided in one of the models he was sending these photos to saying, oh, I know, and there's nothing I can do about it.
In fact, when she was testifying on, I believe it was the House floor, her husband is sitting behind her, and she's asked about her affair with Corey Lewandowski.
And this man said nothing.
He has been, he's just been sitting there apparently, you know, and then pretending like he has big tits.
Republicans and the right, particularly like the Christian Nationalists, have gone on this crusade against the woke mind virus.
And that, you know, they're transing the kids.
And if kids read the wrong books, they're going to be into like cross dressing, whatever.
So what was it that did it for your husband?
Did he read the wrong book in third grade?
Is that why your husband is taking your children's balloons and pretending he has massive tits, Kristi?
So I don't know, maybe it's a good idea to not build entire political movements around restricting people because this is what happens.
Another thing that is rather delicious irony, as someone who was involved in the right wing and received a lot of backlash from the right wing, the most consistent backlash I received and insults I received were based on me being a single mother.
My familial status, that I don't hold Christian values, yada yada who.
And meanwhile, it's not just Kristi Noem, it's all of these people do not hold these values.
They are a mess.
And one thing I can tell you is that no matter the criticisms of me or whatever, my house is a lot more well adjusted than that.
You can say whatever you want about me, but when balloons go missing in my house, I just think the kids must have popped them.
You know, no judge, I mean, full judgment for Kristi Noem.
I do feel bad for her husband because within these messages that he's sending to these models that he's communicating with on these bimbofication sites or whatever he's doing, he expresses that he knows that his wife, that he loves her and he knows that she's sleeping with Corey Lewandowski and he says there's nothing I can do about it.
It really is never just about policy with these people.
These people who should be journaling or in therapy are instead crafting legislation and shaping the lives of other people over their own internal struggles.
Why are our lives and the lives of millions of other people being determined by what's going on in your own internal plot line, your unresolved marriage issues, like your search history, your entire administration is about nobody can explore this, we must ban words, ban pictures, don't open them up to the woke mind virus, and your entire household is an open incognito tab.
And while it's fun to have a heyday with this because it's honestly just hilarious that this is happening to these people, Kristi Noem's husband did not hurt anyone.
He had private interests, private kinks that he seems relatively ashamed of even though he shouldn't, but he hasn't hurt anyone.
He doesn't have real victims in this, as do many people in the administration, as do many people in our Congress and Senate who are not being held accountable the way that they should be.
So maybe when appointing people to positions in which they are responsible for the lives and outcomes of millions and millions of people, more emphasis should have been placed on the fact that she tortures fucking puppies instead of the fact that she's a married Christian godly woman and she has the family structure that you prefer.