Get ready with me while I tell you why I just turned down a paid TV spokesperson position
and I'm also just going to talk shit about Fox News as well.
For those who don't know, my name is Ashley St. Clair. I was a MAGA influencer
involved in MAGA politics for almost a decade. I know. Now, since coming out about some of my
experiences on the right and coming out in favor of a few more progressive positions since
leaving the MAGA cult, I've been offered several paid opportunities, two of which
they wanted me to be a paid TV and media spokesperson for certain positions that I
already hold. Nonetheless, I have declined them because I am not going to go from being
a paid stooge on TV for one party and then go to being a paid stooge on TV for another one.
I'm not interested in it and there are other avenues for me and everybody else to make money
but I am drawing the line at being paid for the words coming out of my mouth.
Oh, I'm almost out of this. Since I came out explaining how these MAGA influence operations
work and how these MAGA influencers are paid, there has been a lot of rhetoric I've seen in
my comments and amongst the general dialogue of this situation saying that, see, Democrats need
to pay their influencers. We need more of a paid apparatus and take my opinion with a grain of salt
but I don't think the option is to pay Democrat influencers. You need to ban the ones that are
getting paid now because this is only allowed to fester through great loopholes within our
laws and regulations regarding political messaging. And I have always had this opinion
about Republican media because I have had my fair share of Fox News appearances
and what's astonishing about places like Fox News is they really just give you a boatload of topics
that you have no business talking about. They will also change these topics. There was one time
that I was on air and in my ear, 30 seconds before we're supposed to go on air, they changed the
subject and they're like, we're going to talk about something you have no business talking about.
There was another time at a right-wing news organization that I walked out of the studio
because I was there to speak on one matter and right before I'm supposed to go on air,
they tell me they want to talk about Ukraine and I, at this point, I don't even know why they're
fighting. I'm not a foreign affairs expert and I walked out of the studio. Particularly with places
like Fox News, so many of these people who go on air and speak so confidently about these issues
should not be speaking on these issues. And I know this because I was one of the people
speaking on issues that I had no business speaking on. And I know this sounds so, so bad. I just
know this is going to sound bad. But when I went on Gutfeld's show, you walk out to the studio and
it really feels like that scene from the Joker and everything's just fake and insane. And Greg
Gutfeld's like vaping in between takes on the commercial break. These people are all ridiculous
clowns. And depending on what the back-end politics were going on at Fox Studios or Newsmax
or what have you, there were times that I was told, hey, you know, we're not going to criticize
Trump right now. We're not going to criticize this person. And they very much filter what you
can and cannot say. These people who pretend to be free thinkers and the champions of free speech,
they're all talking heads for propaganda. And none of these people would be doing this for free,
okay? This economy that we have created in which they can get paid for their viewpoints is
disastrous. And if we go back to the Tenet Media scandal, for those unfamiliar,
Benny Johnson and a slew of other conservative talking heads were wrapped up in a federal
investigation for being paid by Russia through an organization called Tenet Media. And now when
this came out, people like Benny Johnson and others said, we were victims. We had no idea
that this money was coming for Russia. We thought they just wanted to pay us $400,000 a month
because we're so smart and awesome. But what was fascinating about that entire scandal
is that Benny Johnson and all of these right-wing creators claim that Tenet and Russia didn't want
them to adjust their content at all. They never gave them talking points. And so after a situation
like that, wouldn't you say, why does Russia like the shit I'm saying so much? Wouldn't that cause
some introspection to say, hmm, I wonder why adversaries of the United States think everything
I'm saying is perfect. No, no, it's changed nothing. Because for me, if Israel came to me
and said, we want to give you a boatload of cash, change nothing, what you're doing is awesome.
I think I would do a 180. I'd be like, what the hell have I been saying that Israel agrees with
me? I would really, I'd disappear for a little bit. But these people don't have that introspection
to even ask, hmm, why was a foreign nation really interested in what I was saying on my podcast?
So how do we fix some of this? I'm not sure. All I do is, you know, ponder about my own experiences.
But I think one way is a lot of these consulting firms that are paid by PACs and campaigns,
they should not enjoy any financial privacy. Okay, if you are getting boatloads of cash from
different campaigns and PACs and political orgs, we should be able to see all of your financials
and who you're paying as well. These campaign finance transparency laws need to be extended
to the operators, the main operators, which are these consulting firms, which pay these influencers
and other people being paid to spread propaganda, because that's what this is. And I know it because
I spread the propaganda, okay? And I get a lot of questions about how I change my views. And I'm
going to do a video, a longer form video on that soon. However, what people need to understand
is, again, it was a culmination over time. When I saw some of these things, they did not sit right
with me right away. But what was I going to do? I was going to get out of Fox News Studio at 21
years old and live stream and say, it's all fake, and they're all stupid. You know, it was, there was
a lot of internal struggle. And then I'm being convinced out of it by other people. And that's
not an excuse for my behavior or promoting this stuff. However, there was, there was a lot of
internal conflict within my own conscience about all of this and what I was witnessing as I was
witnessing it. And while publicly my positions on things like say, the trans community may have
appeared one way, in private, there were witnesses to me stating this trans panic needs to stop and
me stating that I was uncomfortable with the way certain things were framed around these issues.
And there are people who do know the truth about that with me. There are people who know the truth
and can say that this is not something new. I've always held these positions and my real harm is
not articulating that publicly. Because I should have the moment that I was uncomfortable with the
rhetoric that was being spread and I disagreed, I should have spoke up and I chose to have these
discussions privately and try to change minds privately, which was not the right course of action.
And this may be where I lose some people. But yes, we need to fight what these tech oligarchs
are building. We need to fight against the technocracy. However, we also need to work on
feeding the system the most honest version of humanity possible if they're going to aggregate
our consciousness. What is being aggregated of what we are right now, I think is really, really dangerous.
The loudest inputs right now are the dumbest, stupidest, most disconnected individuals I have ever met.