Get ready with me while I tell you about the time I had to call Alex Jones, yes that Alex Jones, and tell him that I am not transing my one-year-old baby.
So, for background, I was a right-wing MAGA influencer for almost a decade, I know.
Now, throughout my time in MAGA, I promoted a lot of harmful rhetoric, particularly in relation to trans individuals, mostly because I didn't understand what I was talking about.
I ended up taking a hiatus from the internet and doing a lot of reflection on what I had been a part of, what I actually believed, and getting off the internet was really helpful in me finally forming my own opinions, because I had not really been off the internet since I was a child.
Fast forward to a few months ago, and someone on Twitter asked me how I felt about the harm that I had done to the trans community with my rhetoric, and I answered honestly, saying that I feel great remorse for the role that I played, especially considering personal connections now within my family and the trans community, and this sent right-wing Twitter into a spiral.
I knew that this would send right-wing Twitter into a spiral, which is why I was hesitant to speak out about it sooner, because I never wanted the focus to be on myself, especially with the damage and the harm I had done to certain communities.
Nonetheless, somehow my remorse for my previous actions and words turned into right-wing Twitter saying that I was going to trans my one-year-old baby.
Now this lie ended up being boosted by the biggest accounts on Twitter, and this took on a life of its own, that I was now transing a one-year-old.
I don't even think you can do that.
Nonetheless, that did not stop an onslaught of threats, tweets, people threatening to take my baby with them, to save the baby from the woke mind virus and stop me from transing the baby.
Now eventually, this made its way to Alex Jones, who if you didn't know, he still has a show somehow, and the caption for his show tweet says that Ashley St. Clair is chemically castrating her one-year-old child and, you know, we have to save her from this evil witch, whatever.
I guess Alex Jones didn't learn his lesson from smearing parents and their children after Sandy Hook.
Nonetheless, he posts this and obviously his very deranged followers start sending me very concerning messages.
This is also affecting my personal life.
There are people reaching out to me, asking about this, reaching out to my family, and so I just give Alex a little ring-a-ling and I tell Alex that I will sue him and turn his studio into a trans Antifa studio.
I do not care.
I know he has no money, but I will take the desk he sits at if he does not remove this this post because it's untrue.
Now Alex, to his credit, ended up removing this post.
He never did issue the apology or correction that he stated he would on our call.
It's a lot of excuse, but you watch my show now.
I've been sick the whole time.
I shouldn't be here.
I was kind of out of it.
I just want to say that those were false reports and that I talked to you and you said it's completely untrue and then when I went and looked, I didn't see any quotes of that.
But he removed the post and Alex decides to ask.
He's like, well, you know, if it's not true, why is XYZ person saying it?
And I told him, very frankly, Alex, so that idiots like you would repeat it.
Mind you, at this time, I am also initiating a public lawsuit against Grok and XAI for undressing photos of me, including of me as a child.
And because of this, there's a lot of media that wants to chit chat with me about the lawsuit because it affects everyone.
And of course, this is brought up on almost every interview I do that I might be transing my one-year-old baby.
You are apologizing for past comments that you've made about the transgender community.
You wrote, I feel immense guilt for my role and even more guilt that things I have said in the past may have caused my son's sister more pain.
What's your response when that's the post?
I'm not at liberty to discuss it further, but I think anyone with more than a third grade breeding comprehension level knows what I was saying there. And throughout this, there are also people still making images and videos of me being burned at the stake and people running away with my baby in their arms made by Grok.
Also very present in this discourse is a lot of MAGA Republicans, right-wingers saying that I'm only doing this to grift as if this is beneficial to me at all.
But MAGA and the Republicans live in such a hive mind mentality.
I used to date a very prominent right-wing Instagrammer, I don't know, bad time in my life, but he always drove into my head.
Mind you, I was 20 years old dating this 36 year old man.
He was like, never cross the base, never cross the MAGA base, whatever you do, just don't cross the base.
And I think that pathology is really, really present among MAGA that that makes it very difficult for you to change your mind.
Because at all times throughout my time, I was much more concerned about getting canceled or attacked by the right than I ever was about the left.
And it really took me getting off of the internet and reading information for myself, reading books, talking to people who are actually impacted by these issues to realize how much the Republicans scapegoat such small communities.
I mean, this is an issue that affects like less than 1% of the population and it's a top political platform, you know, ushered in under the guise of protecting women.
We need to protect women and children.
And this is the only time where they ever say that they need to protect women and children.
And every other time they are voting and advocating against all of our interests.
And this was something that I did not realize while within this right-wing ecosystem is that all of these issues that affect these smaller populations, while you think and you may ignore it because it doesn't affect you personally, it will come for you too.
I guarantee you half of the times these disadvantaged communities are used as a testing ground to really go after what they're looking for.
And that's larger scale oppression.
One of Trump's first executive orders while in his second term was about trans athletes.
And with everything going on, we're about to be taken over by the final terrain of extraction for capitalism that is AI.
And we are worried about trans athletes.
Are we serious?
And I, it really, there's so much cognitive dissonance that I had to operate with within this because these are not real issues.
Just the mockery of the trans community too, from the right, while they're like, Oh my goodness, a man can't be a woman.
You're delusional.
The people within politics, particularly right-wing politics are some of the most delusional people I've ever met in my life.
They think they're men and they're actually, okay.
So, and I know this because I was a part of it, but so many of these people on the right just operate for clicks and engagement because MAGA really is just Hollywood for ugly dumb people.
Okay.
These are the people who really wanted to be theater kids, but they're, you know, they never made it.
And then you have their heroes like Jesse Waters doing entire prime time segments on mocking trans people.
Ooh, boy thinks he's a girl and making fun of them.
Meanwhile, Jesse Waters, let's talk about Jesse Waters.
I've been on his show a few times.
He cheated on and left his wife and family for a much younger producer.
So, you know, I think you might be the one with a few identity issues, Mr. Waters.
Anyways, thank you for being a part of my little deconstruction journey, and I hope to continue and grow.
I'm still growing and still learning.
Drop in the comments something that you believed that was really harmful that you've changed your mind on and TTFN.