MAGA influencers and some people in the white trash White House are not happy that I talked about how they make their money and how they coordinate their messaging.
So let's get into it.
My original upload of this video included the name of the app that the S workers use to review these men and find out if they're safe.
And after I uploaded it, an S worker had reached out to me and told me that this can negatively impact them.
So I am, I have deleted the original video and I'm re-uploading it with the name of the app censored to protect this resource that they use within their community to stay safe.
For those who don't know, my name is Ashley Sinclair and I was involved in MAGA politics for almost a decade.
I know.
So the other day I posted a get ready with me while I explained how the MAGA influence campaigns work, how so many of these people are paid, and how so much of the messaging is coordinated through group chats with the administration, yada yada who.
Now I want to preface this by saying when I do content here, I am doing it one, to just have a good time and be my age, to finally be 27 and do some little makeup videos, get ready with me, while also trying to be helpful and talk about the journey that I've been on deconstructing and leaving what really felt like a cult to me.
This is my personal experience and I'm really, I'm just living my life, okay?
I am not trying to have a career as an influencer, okay?
Been there, done that.
It's overrated.
I am working on going to law school and that's where I really want to make the change that I believe is going to be the most impactful.
However, when I made this video talking about how these MAGA influence campaigns work and that so many of these individuals are paid, a lot of the people who were paid were not happy about this at all.
One of these people is a very popular Instagram blogger who I'm not going to name for now.
I'm going to name her because I really want to know.
It's on my Instagram story for now.
But she decides that she's very upset that I am calling out these influence campaigns because she is one of the people who gets paid for this and does not disclose it to her audience.
However, instead of attacking or trying to rebut anything I said, which she can't do because everything I said was true, she decided to make personal attacks about my personal family situation and that was where she messed up.
I generally try to hold space for people who have not come to the same conclusions that I have about MAGA and the Republicans because, you know, I do have empathy for these people.
I knew them.
I knew their kids and I feel like a lot of them do feel stuck.
This individual decided to make it personal when her own house is in disarray and and that's what you need to understand about most of these family values MAGA party.
This is the white trash White House guys.
They are engaged in so much debauchery that is just B-A-N-A-N-A-S that you would not believe.
This Instagram gossip blogger, we will call her Jane, she has been on a rebrand.
She was one of the people who was attacking Amber Heard early on and she's been talking about freeing Ghislaine Maxwell, like she's a real, she's cuckoo for Cocoa Puffs, okay?
But she has been on this rebrand where she's pretending to be a real journalist with access to the White House and her relationship with Bobby Kennedy, who's also a mess by the way.
Nonetheless, she pretends to be this journalist who just worked her way to the top and she's so smart and credentialed now.
Meanwhile, the only way she has access to the White House is through two of the messiest white trash individuals I have ever had the displeasure of knowing.
So Jane basically gets all of her access to the White House by taking advantage of these very broken people who are addicted to a variety of things, who slur their words before noon and cheat on their husbands with men and women while promoting MAGA family values.
And if you want to talk about gold digger, I have some stories for you.
Nonetheless, Jane comes for me.
Now one thing I know about Jane, I've met her a handful of times, we've texted on occasion, we were cordial, but one of the times I was out with Jane, who has so much to say about my life and my family, there is an app called this is where you know, mattress actresses, those type of workers can review men to know if they are safe.
And you know, it's it's a community for those within that industry to know if a man who wants to pay for their intimacy is safe.
One of the nights that Jane is out with me and several other people, we are just popping anybody we can into the to see who has been reviewed by these, these women, we are finding people from Rudy Giuliani's team, we are finding people in politics, just having a grand old time.
And then we pop in Jane's husband, who pops up with a review.
Jane is very distraught, she goes to the bathroom, she is crying, she is calling her husband to her husband says that it must have been someone from offer up who was reviewing him, which I'm not sure why someone from offer up would review you on an app for but you know, whatever to each his own.
And so now this woman, I really, I don't like getting involved in this petty drama, I feel like I have much more important things to do.
Okay, I'm working on AI governance, I want to go to law school, I'm trying to live my life and just be a mom and do things that I think are impactful.
However, the reason I think this is relevant is because of the hypocrisy.
These people like to throw stones while they live in glass houses in this white trash White House, and they are all a mess.
I decided to post this information on my Instagram stories.
And after I did so I found out many more things about Jane and her husband, one of which her husband has been arrested for some pretty serious things, mind you.
Nonetheless, I, I really don't want to continue the feud because I don't think it's necessary.
And I think it's beneath me.
But if these people want a FAFO, I will roll in the mud.
If I have to roll in the mud for my babies and my family because you want to keep smearing me.
It's been a year and these people are still talking about me still talking about my family situation, all because I called them out for them not having any actual values and doing tricks on it for a couple bucks on their Instagram stories.
Now I believe because I was calling out James debaucherous connects in the White House.
This caught the attention of some of the people within and around the White House, such as Katie Miller, the wife of Stephen Miller, who I very quickly blocked and called out as well because her peewee German ass husband used to message me on signal every day, begging for retweets during the election, and I'm just, I am so tired of these people.
It is so important to pay attention to who gets upset when it is called out.
Oh my God, I have too much caffeine and I'm trying to put on these eyelashes.
It is important to see who gets upset when they are called out for taking money in politics.
Because the only thing I did was tell everyone how people are getting their biscuits buttered.
All right.
And the counter to this is, well, you know, we have to make money somehow.
Well, how about you get a real job?
I don't know.
That's a thought, but these people think they're too good to get a real job.
They're incredibly entitled.
And throughout my entire time as a MAGA influencer, I always held real jobs at real companies with an actual salary.
You do not have to sell out and sell petition signatures or what have you.
Sorry, I skipped a few steps here, but I was running out of time.
My family has been through enough this past year, the attacks, the smears.
So if you are going to continue to come for us, to come for me and disrupt my peace and the peace of my family, you better make sure your own house is in order.
Because remember, I know where a lot of the bodies are buried.
These people genuinely just have very dark demonic energy.
And I want to be nowhere near this white trash White House and all of those drunkards.