Get ready with me while I tell you about the first time I was cancelled and then fired from Turning Point for being in a photo with...
I can't say his name because I'm pretty sure it's banned on here.
For those who don't know, my name is Ashley St. Clair.
I was a MAGA influencer involved in MAGA politics for almost a decade.
I know.
Also, I did an at-home brow lamination because we're balling on a budget here, but I like it.
Now, me even telling this story should be proof enough that I am not trying to launder my image because this was not a good moment.
There were lots of very poor decisions made here on my part and there's really just no way around that.
However, I think it's important for me to tell the good, the bad, and the ugly, and part of taking accountability is admitting my less-than-stellar moments, of which there are many.
And because I'm a woman of the people, we are giving this one more try because I got a lot of comments saying that I need to warm it up on the back of my hand and try it that way.
So, you know what?
We are going to listen to the people and see if this works.
Now, important context for this blip in my life, in my time in MAGA politics, is going to be my relationship with Mr. Tampa, who has gone ahead and for some reason unknown to me and everybody else watching has named himself as DC Drano.
So, I would encourage you to go to my playlist and watch my other video on my MAGA influencer ex-boyfriend so that you have the right context and setting in time for this story.
I believe this story and my experience is also indicative of how sometimes people can be really beaten out of more reasonable positions because this starts with me tweeting that I thought it was absolutely batshit insane that Alabama, I believe it was Alabama, was going to ban abortion exceptions including for and you know when when family members uh engage in coitus for lack of a better term.
Okay, I'm not sure what I'm allowed and not allowed to say on TikTok.
This individual Nicholas, we will call him Nicholas, I believe, he was not happy about this.
Okay, he said that I was just a whore who loved you know abortion, I'm pro-choice, I'm a fake conservative, blah blah blah.
And then he challenges me to a debate and me being freshly 21 and completely ignorant to you know various other controversies around Nicholas and completely unaware of how influencer politics really operated at this point, I was like sure, of course, I will debate you.
And then very quickly people told me that I should not do this and that I this was a bad idea.
So I was like okay, never mind, I will not do this.
And that made everything 10 times worse because then Nicholas and his followers found out that I'm Jewish and a woman so that was just to them that was the worst thing in the world.
They attacked me relentlessly um with very very anti-semitic um misogynistic remarks saying that I should be you know r-worded yada yada who.
And at this time this was the first massive amount of hate and I mean this was like thousands of individuals attacking me and threatening me online saying that they wanted to turn Jews into lampshades very very crazy stuff okay.
And I was just beside myself I really did not know how to deal with this and then Nicholas had accused me of being an underage s-worker and cam girl which this accusation has become quite prolific um but it's not true not even a little bit true.
And eventually someone who knows Nicholas and knew me said hey why don't we squash this beef and you can have a chit chat with him in person at a private dinner.
And me being young and just thinking of course I would love to talk to someone and ask them to their face why they have engaged in these attacks these relentless attacks on me sure I will do that.
At this time remember I am also dating Mr. Tampa.
Me and Mr. Tampa traveled down to a hotel I believe it was in Miami where this dinner was though I can't quite remember.
But immediately Mr. Tampa is very upset that I'm doing this and as most insane narcissistic men do when they're upset he starts throwing up violently and crying saying that this is a very bad idea.
You know he was right about that but I have no idea why these narcissistic men always like to throw up when they're upset.
Why is this a thing?
Now the individual who set up this meeting between me and Nicholas um he would later turn out to be more likely than not a pdf file.
Okay so these were not exactly the best uh bunch of grapes to be making wine out of if you know what I mean.
So I meet Nicholas for this dinner uh Mr. Tampa stays back and continues just throwing up in the hotel room but it went fine uh Nicholas I tell him all of these things he's saying are smears to which he apologizes.
It's also very weird meeting some of these radical figures because you're like wait why are you like normal in person is this a bit what is going on here?
After this dinner um mind you I also have a very hard time at this point in my life telling people no.
I'm a people pleaser and these people have just been attacking me relentlessly.
I really didn't want to say no to anything and they invite me back to keep chatting about things at some house they were seeing at I don't know mistake.
I went back and eventually uh they say you know we should all take a photo.
No idea why I'm like sure geez unbeknownst to me I had no idea who many of these other individuals were and if you thought Nicholas was bad these people were were far worse something I would not find out until the media reached out uh after this photo.
Now I was not exactly of sound mind at this point either because as I said I had just turned 21 so I ordered god knows how many drinks at dinner and by the time we took this photo there was no making reasonable rational decisions.
Not that I was making them prior to drinking but uh certainly didn't help.
Nonetheless this photo is posted by other people.
I never posted the photo uh and it goes very very viral.
As I had mentioned in my video about Mr. Tampa simultaneously unbeknownst to me I was about to start dying with a kidney infection that had gone to my blood the very next day.
So simultaneously I am like wow I really uh I don't feel great.
I think I'm gonna go to the hospital uh while I am getting calls from turning point from Tyler Bauer um because at this time I was unpaid turning point brand ambassador and Tyler Bauer called me and told me in his words that I was gonna have to be quote-unquote put in the doghouse for a little bit because of this photo and that they did not want to be called white nationalist sympathizers.
I was like okay don't know what that means I'm dying so I have to go.
So at this point I am dying in the hospital and I have so many media outlets reaching out to me for comment on this photo and this dinner and I am giving them statements on morphine okay because again I'm dying and I am just like I was at a very diverse dinner.
What why did I do that?
I don't know um so then I see the headlines and it says turning point fires brand ambassador turning point summersides with brand ambassador and I'm like oh I guess that's what the doghouse means but also how do you fire me?
I was never fucking paid.
And because I am merely just a girl I was posting selfies dying from the hospital which caused everyone to think that I was faking it because I was simultaneously getting canceled.
So within a matter of days I went from being attacked relentlessly for being a Jewish woman to now according to the headlines I was a white nationalist sympathizing brand liability for turning point.
Needless to say I never tweeted that I was pro-choice ever again and instead pretended to be the opposite.
Anyways let me know if you guys want a part two to this story because there's a lot more that happened.
I was never technically disconnected from turning point and then for some reason because I was in this photo it like gave me weird street cred I guess with like the white nationalists so that they were defending me even though I was Jewish and a woman they were like overlooking it.
It was like it was a lot okay.