Get ready with me while I tell you about how the pay-to-play MAGA influence campaigns work.
For those who don't know, my name is Ashley St. Clair and I was involved in
MAGA politics and was a MAGA influencer for almost a decade. I know.
Now, MAGA and really MAGA, not so much just GOP messaging, is incredibly coordinator and
I was initiated into this very young, about 19 years old, when I was first brought on
to Turning Point. That was when I was invited to my first Turning Point event
and was really thrust into this MAGA influencer ecosystem.
In 2015-2016, MAGA and their operators realized how important and consequential social media was
for politics. This really started during the Obama years when they harnessed the internet
and email campaign messaging and then MAGA took it to the next level with things like
Cambridge Analytica and coordinated messaging on sites like Twitter.
Their main avenues for this influence are group chats, paid influence campaigns, and parties.
Now, for the group chats, they operate with large influencers, particularly on Twitter.
That is their primary mode of communication is Twitter. They will have these giant group chats
that make influencers and individuals feel important because they are in group chats with
members of the administration, people on the Trump team, in which they coordinate these messaging
tactics. They also have coordinated calls with these campaigns and with these politicians so
you feel that you are important. What I really want to focus on though is the paid campaigns
because this is able to fester through many loopholes within our own regulations and laws
because since what they're promoting is messaging or petitions or campaigns and not a service or
a product, they do not have to disclose that they are paid for this on social media.
They have these Republican operatives, some of which were former White House,
who build out these platforms that these right-wing influencers can log onto and
see active campaigns and sign up for and get paid for promoting certain messaging,
certain initiatives, certain petitions. This pay is typically per click. Sometimes it's a
flat rate, but it is everything from, hey, tell your audience to call their members of Congress
and vote a particular way on this bill or have your followers sign this petition,
promote this propaganda, X, Y, Z. The structure is indistinguishable from ad campaigns that you
would do for a traditional company. If you take Tarte, for example, or a cosmetic brand or what
have you, typically when they get influencers, they will also have a company copy or things that
they should say, a script. So do these right-wing influencers. They are given a script, they are
paid, and they post it. The only difference is that they do not have to disclose that it's an ad
because of our current laws and regulations do not require them to do so since it is not a good
or a product. Now, some of these consulting firms that pay for this stuff, they will show up on FEC
records because the campaign or the PAC or the candidate pays them. But once they pay this
consulting firm, it's gone. There is no further disclosures required by the consulting firms
or anything like that. So this is a good way for them to hide exactly who they're paying for
messaging because it just goes through these firms that do not require any additional reporting to the
FEC. And again, they also have these group chats with members of the administration and high-up
officials that, especially when a scandal or controversy breaks out, all of this messaging
is coordinated. Hey, here's how we respond to the files. Here's how we respond to the war. Here is
how we respond to everything. So there's this entire ecosystem of large influencers. All of the
largest influencers that you have seen in the right wing, 99% of them are paid or compensated
or having their back scratched in one way or another. And then this trickles down because
the people under them, these smaller influencers, are not aware of this. So when they're looking
to these larger accounts in response to controversies or messaging, what they're
seeing is actually very coordinated and very sophisticated influence campaigns from the top.
There is no free thinking here whatsoever. They are waiting to get marching orders
and a direct deposit. This also works on a smaller scale for influence campaigns because there are
private, very wealthy donors that will pay independent journalists to do certain projects
or videos. And that never has to get reported to the FEC because it's between two private
individuals, even though the messaging and the influence is for political purposes.
This happened to me at one point when there were a lot of scandals going on with the airlines and
immigration, which I unfortunately had a role in boosting that rhetoric. I had a very wealthy
billionaire who reached out to me because he had personal beef with Southwest. So he wanted me to
do a sting operation on Southwest to see if they were flying migrants around the country.
I did not do that. To obfuscate things even more, this happens between private companies as well.
So some of the biggest private companies within the right, particularly the right wing media,
they will be reached out to by people who want particular messaging. I was aware of this several
times in regards to Israel, where Republican companies, right wing companies, private media
companies were offered millions of dollars to promote pro-Israel messaging and just sprinkle
in things. So they're also doing this very covertly when they're making these asks. They're saying,
you know, let's just sprinkle it in here and there for a larger scale, long-term influence campaign.
And issues like this with money in politics really began around the 70s, late 70s. And there's
a particular case that I've been fascinated by, which is Buckley v. Vallejo and other subsequent
precedents that basically solidify money as speech. And what you do, this happened like right
on the heels of the civil rights era, right? And all of these individuals are now able to participate
in democracy, at least on paper, in the same way as everyone else. Well, a lot of people,
particularly very wealthy corporate men, were not happy about this. So they got right to work
saying, well, we need to differentiate ourselves. And they basically complained to the courts
and complained that corporations were basically political minorities and that they should be able
to participate in politics and that money is speech. And our court affirmed this. The Supreme
Court has affirmed many times that money is free speech. So by definition, there are a lot of people
in this country who have more free speech than others. And our current system is incredibly
archaic in the sense that it does not account for the internet and that these influencers do not have
to disclose when they're paid in the sense that basically money can be hidden in politics through
these consulting firms. And I have seen it time and time again. They throw money around for everything.
At one point, I was offered a lot of money to promote Rick Grinnell for Secretary of State when
the Trump administration admin picks were happening. And I can guarantee you he was not the only one
in this pay to play scheme. And at the other end of almost all of these payments
are also confidentiality agreements, meaning that even if these individuals involved had a
change of heart and realized that they are participating in great evil, that they cannot
speak up about it or they will get sued into oblivion. So not only have the wealthy created a
system in which their political influence means far more than yours, but they've also been the
architects of a system in which they have these manufactured reputations and narratives and they
manufacture silence through these incredibly asymmetric contracts in which people could
lose their livelihoods and reputations for speaking.