Get ready with me while I tell you more about the pay-to-play within the White House and MAGA,
as well as why I think MAGA is the real party of DEI. For those who don't know, my name is
Ashley Sinclair and I was a MAGA influencer involved in MAGA politics for almost a decade,
I know. For a party that is so obsessed with meritocracy and squashing DEI,
they themselves are the biggest proponents of DEI on the planet. Because what DEI means to
MAGA and the Right is basically just questioning the credentials of anybody who is not white or a
man. But MAGA and its accolades are the biggest proponents of DEI, and I will call this MAGA DEI,
and what this stands for is Donald Escorts and Investors, because that is what gets you a job
worthy of being in the White House among MAGA. First and foremost, we have D. Donald,
and that is their loyalty to the God Emperor Oompa Loompa Trump. And this has been going on
and prolific throughout MAGA for many, many years. There were many instances in which people
were blacklisted from being featured at Turning Point or different organizations because they had
criticized Trump. Now, this is now extending even to events at Mar-a-Lago, at which the social
medias of anyone who is screened by Secret Service, their social media is now being screened
by Secret Service, and if they have anything that is anti-Trump, they will not be allowed in.
Now, the E in their DEI, MAGA DEI, is for escorts, because so many of this depends on
who is fucking who. And this is not just for women, this is also for men. But,
obviously, I spoke about Ozempie and how she has sucked. Being involved in these influencer circles,
there were always people that would show up at events, primarily women, but they would show up
at events at the White House or random MAGA events, and there was kind of a question of what is this
person doing here? And, oh, it turns out they're fucking someone from the Trump campaign. It turns
out they're fucking someone from the White House. And this also applied to appointments within the
administration. People who have no business being in our government, at our State Department,
at the White House, are there because they fucked the right person. Even take Kristi Noem, for
example, she would not have been appointed to DHS if she was not fucking Corey Lewandowski. Let's
get that real clear. And lastly, in MAGA DEI, we have investors or donors or anybody who gives
that fat sack of shit money, they will get major, major favor because everything with these people
is an issue of class. And you shouldn't just take my word for it. Instead, I'm going to provide you
the word of someone at the White House right now. Now, this woman at the White House, we will call
her AA because that's where she really should be because she's hammered by noon because she drinks
Grey Goose pear on the rocks on the White House lawn. Now, AA was and is, I don't know their
current situation, was close with Kimberly Guilfoyle. She's close with the entire Trump family,
but she was particularly close with Kimberly Guilfoyle, the former girlfriend, fiance of
Donald Trump Jr. Now, when Donald Trump Jr. and Kimberly's, which they refer to as KG,
their relationship started going south and Don met Bettina. There was a storm brewing behind the
scenes in which people were trying to sabotage Bettina because, and I do feel bad for Kimberly,
she was, according to AA, very distraught over this and trying to place lots of negative media
about Bettina all over the press. They were spreading rumors that Bettina was always high
on shrooms, that she was just a gold digger, yada yada who. Now, AA was discussing Kimberly's
appointment as the ambassador to Greece and AA was a bit, uh, conflicted about Kimberly's
appointment to be this ambassador because in her own words, there were about 20 donors and
two congressmen who also wanted the position, which is a bit curious because why, why are donors
high on the priority list for political appointments? Not once in this conversation
did anybody say, there's people who would be much better ambassadors to Greece and have the
qualifications, at least more qualifications than Don Jr.'s ex-girlfriend for this position.
No, no. What they were considering is, hey, we have some favors to do for donors and this might
fuck things up. Now, when I say this entire administration is a back-scratching circle jerk,
I say this because I know this, all right, because these people like to chat and they're drunkards
who go around telling more business than they should. Even Miss House Inhabit, who pretends to
be a neutral journalist, I have text also from AA in which it is stated that the reason House
Inhabit was brought into the White House and around the Trump family was to show a softer side of the
family and really launder their image here. And quite explicitly stated was that if House Inhabit,
Jess, did not stick to this mission, she would not be allowed access to the Trump family anymore.
So really, she has no avenue for objectivity here. And the problem is these fucking cognitive
traffic cones in the White House and at Mar-a-Lago are now making such consequential decisions for
the United States and the world and they have no business being there. They're pretending
as if they are the party of meritocracy when not a damn person in that White House has the
qualifications to be there except maybe Marco Rubio, okay. And even people like J.D. Vance,
his supporters are the first ones to call me a gold digger when, first of all, I turned down an
ungodly amount of money. But guess what, J.D.? I didn't have a sugar daddy funding my entire
career like you did in Peter Thiel. You could never say no to those bucks.
It wasn't that long ago that MAGA was calling themselves Big Tent and bragging and putting the
Black and gay conservatives front and center. And then once they got enough people in and
made these people reliant on MAGA for their social circles, for their social quota and
their community, then they implemented in lockstep this environment in which you cannot criticize
Trump without being ostracized from opportunities, from jobs, from your community because the Trump
team very much tracks any criticism, anyone stepping out of line with messaging, and they
blacklist people for it. And if they do criticize Trump, they also risk having Donald Trump go on a
dementia-fueled 4 a.m. tirade about them on Truth Social, which causes immense risk to their
physical safety. And Donald Trump and his entire team know what happens and knows the security
threats associated with him attacking someone. And now, this is certainly not an excuse for
people who do not speak out against Trump and this administration. However, when people ask
why don't more people speak out, it is because, especially for these large figureheads, their
income, the roof over their head, the food they feed their family with, and their physical safety,
their community, is at risk if they speak out.