Get ready with me while I tell you about the paid agitators in MAGA politics from
Turning Point to Libs of TikTok. For those who don't know, my name is Ashley St. Clair. I was
a MAGA influencer involved in MAGA politics for almost a decade. I know. Now I want to talk about
this because within the right wing and MAGA, it is prolific that they are obsessed with George
Soros and calling Democrats paid activists and the radical left is all paid. But what there is not
enough attention on is how much of the MAGA influencer sphere is propped up on paid agitation.
I'm going to focus primarily on my experiences with companies and individuals like Libs of TikTok,
Turning Point, and my former company that Benny Johnson had co-founded. We will start
off with the company I was working out with, Benny Johnson, and my first job for this company
was to go to the DNC convention and basically be a paid agitator. I was made to hold a sign
that said, creepy Joe has got to go, talking about Joe Biden because I don't know, he did that weird
sniffing thing. But simultaneously, this is happening and I'm made to hold a creepy Joe
has got to go sign and I'm being harassed by people. At the same company at which I was
harassed and grabbed by Madison Cawthorne and they kept him as a client. Now this protest content
is money in MAGA, okay? You are either going to get buku bucks from social media from posting
this content because there's so much engagement or a company is just straight up going to pay you
to go to protest. Turning Point does this a lot, they have their contributors fly out, all expenses
paid to go and cover these protests, but really they are just agitators. Also, this is going to be
my last time using this reformulated luminous silk because I hate it. I wore it yesterday and I hate
it. It looks too cakey, it's not the same, and whoever decided this was a good idea to reformulate
it after 25 years should be fired. There is also major, major money to be made. I am talking
seven figures to be made by people who post this agitator harassment content such as
Libs of TikTok and the likes. For those who don't know, Libs of TikTok is a Libs of TikTok LLC.
It is a company, okay? You can look this up yourself. It is a company, it is a business,
and Haya, who runs Libs of TikTok, would run around and send me pictures of the new designer
she's buying and she has a stylist and is buying a home. This is very lucrative and they will
pathologize this and say, well, you know, I have to because I was getting so many death threats
and now I'm independent and I'm successful. But really, they just don't want real jobs,
that's the reality of it. Now, this company, Libs of TikTok, because of another job I had,
I ended up having to work with Haya. And I don't know, for a long time I had a soft spot for Haya.
I think because she's just so stupid. She's genuinely not impressive intellectually.
But I would be getting calls. I tried to set boundaries with this woman, okay? I was like,
babe, my kids, I have to put my son down at a certain time. You cannot be calling me about
drag queens at 9, 10 p.m. She did not respect these boundaries whatsoever. But what's also
fascinating about this is that Haya and others were also aware that I was very uncomfortable
with this trans panic and would quite often say, this is wrong, you know, we can't just
dox trans people. At one point, I had to tell her, you cannot just post photos of random minors.
Like, if you're going to post children, you need to blur their face. What are you doing?
And it was just genuinely a nightmare. But again, this was a business for her. It still
is a business for her. And her and many others suffer from, like, this agitation content brain.
They view everything as, oh, that's going to be good content. That's going to do numbers.
And they have these, like, tip inboxes where people just send them the most crazy examples
of things. And then they push this out as if it is mainstream or this is something that you are
going to encounter in normal everyday interactions. And the other large conservative
influencers and media companies recognize the value, at least the monetary value,
they don't care about the moral value of anything, of accounts like Libs of TikTok,
because there were multiple offers to buy Libs of TikTok to buy out this content harassment
apparatus that Haya had built. And I mean, very large figures who have millions and millions
of followers. At one point, she had wrongly posted that someone who decided to, I think it was a
school because that's America now, was trans. And this wasn't true at all. And it took much
convincing to have her take this down. She's like, wait, let me let me see if it's true. Let
me see. Let's wait. Let's wait. And just left this up to induce more trans panic. And again,
my hands are not clean. Okay, I have contributed to this rhetoric. Absolutely. And I am incredibly
remorseful about my role in this. At the same time, I was really one of the only ones saying,
like, hey, maybe we should slow down. Maybe we should not just dox people based on their identity.
And this was fairly common. And there were many conversations with high up figures within the
conservative movement and MAGA on how to handle me. And at one point, it was relayed to me
that they were upset about something I had posted in disagreement with Charlie,
because Charlie Kirk had gone on a stage at a religious event and said that if your daughters
are on birth control, it is like black tar. And that you should get them off. Don't let your
daughters be on birth control. All of this crazy shit. Okay. And so I publicly disagreed with him.
And there was allegedly a meeting about this, in which they came to the conclusion that they
don't want to punish me, because I could still get people to vote for Trump. I believe I had
tweeted at Charlie and said that this white male jihad is not going to work. And they were not
happy about that. When I got involved in MAGA and this right wing influencer space, I think a lot of
it was obviously this need for validation and community. And there was another part of it that
you think going into politics that oh, I'm gonna make a difference. And then there's like this
disillusionment that happens once you're in it. And you see that everyone, everything is staged,
everything is for $1. Everything is about making money and for profit. Like it was just
there was a long term disillusionment happening within me as well during my time. And I think
we're seeing some of that disillusionment happen now, in a broader sense with the MAGA base,
because everyone's like, what the fuck do you mean? We're for more wars? What the fuck do you
mean? All the people closest to you at inauguration are the tech bros and the tech oligarchs that you
know, have created these awful discovery algorithms are bastardizing our consciousness and extracting
our souls and calling it proprietary data. So I think there's more of that disillusionment
happening. But again, I encourage people to recognize what harm and what cruelty they had to
ignore to allow it to get to this point in the first place. These groups, these influencers,
these organizations, these MAGA influencers are only able to exist because of money in politics.
And if these assholes in MAGA can run on overturning Roe v. Wade, why are the Democrats
not running on overturning Citizens United, overturning Buckley v. Valeo to get the money
out of politics? And that's because something that is stronger than any allegiance to a party
is their allegiance to class, to the elite capitalist class.