Get ready with me while I tell you about my experience with Madison Cawthorn and why I think he should never be around women ever again.
For those who don't know, my name is Ashley St. Clair and I was involved in MAGA politics as a MAGA influencer for almost a decade.
I know.
Now, I want to preface by saying this situation requires a trigger warning because what's going to be discussed is difficult for me and will be difficult for other people, but let's get into it.
Now, I never really wanted to speak about this situation and I did not plan on speaking about it publicly.
If people asked me privately, I was very vocal, but it has been a difficult situation for reasons that hopefully you will understand, but there was a moment that I realized I needed to say something.
With all the accusations coming out against Swalwell and Swalwell resigning, Madison Cawthorn decided to chime in.
Madison said, Swalwell is not the only one and this set me off because Madison Cawthorn is right.
Swalwell is not the only one.
He is far from the only one.
Madison Cawthorn is one of them and I know this because he was a client at a company that I worked for for years and I was one of the women who was on the receiving end of this behavior from Madison Cawthorn.
Now, one of the reasons I have not spoken about this sooner is because after my experience with Madison, I continued to be rather friendly and cordial with him mostly because at this time he was a one of the top clients for the company I was working at and I also had this fear that I wouldn't be believed because I was friendly with him after these instances.
Nonetheless, when this happened, I did tell my boss right away.
I told people close to me right away and I still have all of those text messages.
Again, I do need to put a trigger warning because I am going to be talking about SH and SA.
So, my first uncomfortable experience with Madison was on a shoot.
I was at a production company where we were running all of the production and social media for Madison Cawthorn while he was in Congress.
On this particular shoot, I was the lead.
I was the director of the shoot and I was tasked with running the shoot for Madison and then having a meeting with him afterwards about his campaign messaging goals, etc.
The shoot itself goes fine and then after the shoot we are getting in the car.
There's a few flirty comments from Madison here and there but that's kind of par for the course in politics as a woman, whatever.
So, then we are getting in the car and remember Madison Cawthorn is in a wheelchair.
So, as we are getting into the vehicle I am sitting by the window and Madison is in the middle.
As we are about to drive, Madison leans over and whispers in my ear and says, just so you know, I have no control over my obliques.
I assume Madison was using this as a preface for what he was about to do every time the car made a turn.
So, every time the vehicle we were in made a turn, Madison proceeded to like flail and every time he flailed his hand just so happened to land on my upper upper thigh.
This was my upper thigh.
At this point I am just wildly uncomfortable because he's like five for five with his hand landing on my upper thigh on each turn and finally we make it to this lunch meeting where we're supposed to be discussing his campaign messaging and his social media.
I got blush on my shirt.
Mind you, at this time Madison is in a relationship.
He has a longtime girlfriend.
They may have been engaged at this point and as soon as we sit down for this meeting, there is no work to be discussed.
Madison starts talking about oral, you know, very disturbing stuff.
Again, I tell my boss about this right away.
I tell him that I'm uncomfortable but nonetheless I'm still being really friendly with Madison because I don't want any sort of retaliation.
I don't, I don't, I don't know and he continues making these comments.
At one point it gets so absurd that he invites me to his wedding and tells me that he can't wait to see me in a dress again as he's talking about my potential attendance at his wedding.
Because of my experience with Madison, I also told my boss that we should not be sending female staffers on shoots with Madison alone.
This is ignored and shortly after I make this recommendation, a female staffer is sent on set alone with Madison and he proceeds to take photos of her, um, of her ass that he sees zoomed in and saying, your pants look great.
And now I'm dealing with this female staffer telling me about this and I am completely unsure what to do.
Now a few months after my own experience with Madison, uh, there is a story that comes out of women discussing almost the same experience where Madison, in their words, trapped them in a car and then made advances on them.
Now when this story comes out, I end up falling into a bit of a depressive episode because I knew that, I knew that those girls, that those women were telling the truth and I watched MAGA and Republicans attack them and call them liars when I, oh, I knew that they were telling the truth and, uh, I, I didn't speak for them.
I didn't speak out for them and say what I, I knew and experienced, um, and I've carried a lot of guilt for that.
So the best I can do is speak out about it now, especially since Madison has decided to try to take the public position that he is any different from Eric Swalwell.
Now what, this is important because so many of the people in MAGA and in right-wing politics also knew about Madison, uh, either because they knew someone with a similar story to me or because I told them.
I still have the text where I told Benny Johnson that Madison was this way and mind you, Benny used to own the company that I was working at at the time that this occurred.
You also have people like Katie Miller, Stephen Miller's, the wife of Pee Wee coming out and saying, we all knew about Swalwell.
Um, okay, well we all know about a lot more.
So let's talk about everything we know.
Let's talk about everything and all of the men that the MAGA Republicans know about too, starting with Madison Cawthorn.
Maybe we'll go to Boris Epstein next.
It really disturbs me how giddy Republicans are and MAGA is to talk about Eric Swalwell and, you know, dance on his grave here and Eric Swalwell should be held accountable, but they all should because MAGA is also covering for people in their ranks who are doing the same thing as Eric Swalwell and they all know it.
People ask me a lot why it took me so long to leave and part of the reason is because it was a lot.
Not that it's an excuse, but I went through so much that has been so difficult to unpack and maybe it's insensitive to even talk about things so serious while doing my makeup, but it's the easiest way for me to do it with at least a little bit of brevity and distance for things that are so serious.