Get ready with me while I tell you the horror story of my time at one of the top Republican
MAGA production companies. Let's get into it. And for those who are unaware, my name is Ashley
Sinclair. I was involved in MAGA politics as a MAGA influencer for almost a decade. I know. But
anyways, welcome back to episode 800 of Who the Fuck Did I Marry? Now before everyone starts
asking me where the Benny Johnson receipts are, trust me, they're coming. Do not rush my art,
my cinema here, okay? We will get to that and everything I'm about to tell you is tangentially
related. We need to introduce some other characters first here, all right? So the year is 2020 and I
am recruited to work at a company called Arsenal Media Group, which was founded by a man named Jason
Cole and Benny Johnson. Now Jason and Benny were besties in Iowa, little Iowa boys who were friends
and they were recruited by other very prominent individuals within the sphere to start Arsenal
Media Group. Now Arsenal in the beginning was a production and social media company. They really
did video shoots and social media promotion for some of the biggest names in Republican
politics and as I had mentioned in a previous video, people like Madison Cawthorne, Don Jr.,
Sarah Huckabee Sanders, Benny himself, Charlie Kirk, you name it. So I start working at Arsenal
in August of 2020 and right away this is chaotic, okay? I am being put on some pretty insane
shoots with some insane clients. Within two weeks of being there I am put basically in this like
principal position as director of operations and I am told by Jason Cole and Benny Johnson that I
need to acquire a tiger, Rick Harrison from Pawn Stars, Mike Tyson and Aubrey Huff.
Oh also they wanted an Elvis impersonator because we were doing a shoot in Las Vegas
for a candidate running there who had an extensive criminal record, whatever.
So right away I am being asked to do some shady shit because they don't have the proper permits
or insurance for any of this, certainly not bringing a damn tiger on to set with our staff.
Nonetheless, I acquire all of these things right away. What becomes abundantly clear as soon as
I'm here is that Benny Johnson is a fucking psychopath, okay? He is screaming at staff,
screaming at everyone, just a really, it's very clear that this guy has a personality disorder
and there's staff crying, I'm crying and I'm here like two weeks at this point.
Now this is important and I will get into this later when I talk about Benny more in depth,
but this is important because Jason, I end up kind of trauma bonding with him in a way
almost immediately because Jason is the person who validates that how anyone feels about Benny
is right, you know, of course Benny's like that, I know, I've known him a long time,
but you're doing good work, don't worry. What's also made clear right away is that I am overworked
and underpaid. Once we go on this Las Vegas shoot, which is a disaster, again there is,
I'm given drugs, okay? I, Jason is giving me illegal substances that he acquired from Mexico
so that I can stay up and work all night long because why not? I also forgot to say that during
this Las Vegas shoot, Jason made me get on a motorized scooter with him drunk and then
ran me into a light pole. And at this point I'm 21, 22, I have no idea what the norm is
really for a job because I've only worked in right-wing politics at this point and so I'm
like, oh, like it's par for the course that this is going to be toxic. But, and I will admit my own
faults here, because of the environment, particularly created by Benny and Jason,
you know, there was this push that, you know, you need to be harder on the staff and this is
unacceptable. So I ended up taking on some of these toxic behaviors too and kind of mirroring
some of this behavior that I was seeing from Jason and Benny. Pretty early on there is also
a lot of money issues. So people are not being paid, I'm getting calls from staffers asking where
their paycheck is, yada yada who, and Jason is just a drunkard who disappears quite often to do,
you know, God knows what, doesn't pay his staff and I'm left to clean up these pieces. At one point he
starts fronting himself the money from the Facebook pages we're monetizing like Don, Donald Trump Jr.
and Charlie Kirk to make payroll. He is telling me that he's going to have to sell off his bitcoin
to make payroll. This guy is a mess. And then he starts, mind you, Jason's married at this point.
Jason starts sleeping with a friend of mine who is also married and is now at the White House.
So Jason enters this affair. Already I'm like, wow, this is a moral conundrum. What the hell am I
supposed to do here? But he doesn't stop there. He is routinely getting drunk on these staff trips
for shoots and talking about his penis, talking about sleeping with other members of staff. He did
engage in an affair with two other female staffers and they were unaware that they were both sleeping
with Jason and they were best friends. It was a mess. It was a hot mess. Jason is also expanding
the scope of what this company and subsequently what everyone at the company is supposed to do.
We are being forced to share the messaging from certain clients that is frankly just abhorrent.
We also had to work with people like the McCloskeys. Remember the St. Louis couple?
And just really, really awful people on politics. Carrie Lake was one of them.
The clients are also becoming aware that Jason is full of shit. Jason is also just, if you didn't
know from his cheating escapades, he's a big fat liar. So I get a message one day from Jason
that says, just tore Ashley a new one. Hi, I'm Ashley. No, he didn't because I was on maternity
leave. So he is just, he meant to send it to another staffer. Meanwhile, our clients are
pretty high-end clients. We're working with major packs, illegally so by the way, because nothing was
firewalled the way it's supposed to be, if you're working for the for-profit and the non-profit and
the pack arm of things, that was also a mess. By 2022, after I had been harassed by Madison
Cawthorne, inappropriately touched, having to hear about my boss's affairs, I had to drive to his
house at one point to see where he was because he disappeared for like 48 hours and he answered the
door like naked basically and I was just done. I had my baby and I was like, I want no part of this.
So I left and shortly after I leave, the other staff basically start striking. They are like,
we're not going to any of these shoots if you don't pay us and you're a mess. What is clear
through Arsenal and all of these other consulting firms that I worked with throughout my time in
MAGA politics is that not only is nothing organic, but in private these people who are your figure
heads, their messaging is so aligned with what is going to get them the most clicks and monetization
and they say this quite explicitly. There was also a lot of blacklisting going on and
very high up figures within the MAGA coalition and from some companies that you would know
that would request that staffers of ours be fired for not being Trump loyalists,
even just criticizing Trump would cause Jason to say, well, I'm not gonna pay their bills.
I'm not gonna put food on their table. So this whole time that I'm at this company,
I am scared to step out of line in messaging because I will lose the roof over my head.
So while they're simultaneously making money, an exorbitant amount of money off of, you know,
crying about cancel culture on social media, they're also taking away the livelihoods of
people who are not ideological foot soldiers for the MAGA party of family values, Trumpism,
and the people canceling them are the most degenerate white trash scum I've ever met in
my life. There is also an exorbitant amount of pressure to keep these things quiet too,
because around the time that I leave, Arsenal starts getting media attention for this awful
behavior, their shady business operations. And I am cornered at the Mar-a-Lago pool by Andrew
Colvette from turning point saying, you know, you better not be leaking to the media about Arsenal,
yada, yada, who?