Space technology in the election.
I should also say that I have all of this backed up with many people with explicit instructions should anything happen to me, okay?
All right, Emily, so we've reviewed actually and obtained some of these text messages and what Ashley Sinclair is claiming Musk claimed is true.
And I say that quite deliberately because there's a difference between Musk making a claim and Musk's claim being true.
However, what he says matters and her reference to depositions I think is telling.
But yeah, so he wrote to her, tomorrow we unleash the anomaly in the matrix, this is not something on the chessboard, so they will be quite surprised, quote lasers from space.
And then she does tell her joke referencing kind of a Marjorie Taylor Greene thing.
Finally, a focus on the Jewish vote.
And he adds, I have over 10,000 lasers in space right now.
And she does in fact then reply, I would ask more questions, but will keep myself from getting deposed.
And Musk responds wise with the laughing guy.
And then she says something like, if your space lasers seriously end up being the anomaly in the matrix that takes back America, I will be convinced that God is maximizing the simulation.
So this conversation did happen in early October while Musk was campaigning with Trump and Butler when they went back to the scene of the attempted assassination.
Back to that, Ashley Sinclair immediately thought that depositions are coming, suggests that there probably should be some, like this is something we should, these are questions that ought to be answered, I would think.
Well, Musk seemed to agree that depositions could be coming when he responded with what the laughing face emoji, wise.
Yeah, wise.
Wise, yes, don't ask any more.
I think with ASHLEY ST. CLAIR, they thought they had an NPC, turns out they didn't.
So I think we're going to continue to find out more.