Get ready with me while I talk about the lead up to Elon sliding in my DMs. For those who don't know,
my name is Ashley St. Clair. I was a MAGA influencer involved in MAGA politics for almost
a decade. I know. Now, if you haven't already watched the other videos, specifically the
Republican Company Horror Story for where we're at right now in the timeline. So at this point,
I've been canceled several times. One of which for being in a photo with very unsavory characters.
Another because there were allegations going around that I was an underage ass worker,
which I was not. But even if I was, that is just called a victim. Okay. At this point,
I feel like I have no way out of MAGA because I am a professional and personal liability.
Additionally, I had some other cancellations for stepping out of line, specifically by saying I was
on a podcast and I said that Republicans in Colorado focus not enough on education and too
much on immigration. That brought me the ire and wrath of many alt-right figures, including people
like Ann Coulter, saying that I'm a fake Republican, yada yada who. I am constantly getting in trouble
for having what I thought was normal opinions on things like immigration and reproductive rights.
So I start working at this company co-founded by Benny Johnson in 2020. I stay there until about
2022. Oh my god, again, I put too much of this on. As I had mentioned in my previous video,
this company is a shitshow. Not only is no one being paid, but the CEO of the company is
fucking staff members, not paying people. At this point, he's asking us to target disadvantaged
Black candidates who have absolutely zero chance of winning their race, but they are very popular
on social media. Because at this time, being a Black Republican or Black conservative
flies on social media. So Jason is asking us to target and acquire clients specifically based on
race and their districts that they have zero chance of winning. At this point, Jason is using
the Facebook money that we're making from running the Facebook pages for these conservative figures
to front payroll. He is literally stealing the money from the clients that we run.
Their Facebook pages and using it to front payroll. Because if you, what are my hands doing?
Because if you, because if you didn't know, no one is more responsible for buttering the biscuits
and giving capital to right-wing propagandists than Mark Zuckerberg and Facebook, okay? These
top conservative figures make five to six figures a month on Facebook video monetization.
I am also under severe emotional distress working at this company. I still have to text where I am,
I am texting my then boyfriend saying, I can't do this. I'm having a panic attack. I'm hyperventilating
because I have to deal with Benny. Like this was such a disaster and I am working such insane hours.
And again, at one point, Jason is giving me various substances from other countries so that
I can pull all-nighters, okay? This is not a good place to be. But again, I don't have anywhere else
to go really because of my Google search results. So then in 2021, I also am pregnant with my first
son. And I am becoming increasingly concerned about what is going on here. By the time I have
my son in late 2021, I'm completely over this company. And by 2022, early 2022, I am out. But
as I'm at this company, I start looking for other jobs. And I am like, I really do not want to be
on the campaign side of things. But given my Google search results, I'm going to have to stay
in at least Republican politics adjacent companies. So the two companies I start looking to get a job
at are Project Veritas with James O'Keefe and the Babylon Bee with Seth Dillon. Now I go through
several interviews with Project Veritas. And they end up telling me that because of my controversies
and these various allegations about me being an underage S worker, they were going to decline.
Okay, at this point, I am too controversial to work with James O'Keefe. But again, I have a new
baby, I need a job, preferably one that I can work from home. But honestly, I will take anything at
this point. Eventually, Seth Dillon does extend an offer to me, which I accept. So I am like,
toodaloo, Jason and Benny, I am going to work for Seth Dillon. So I work for Seth
um, technically at his parent company, but I am helping run the operations for not only the
Babylon Bee, but other entities that Seth owns at the time, such as Libs of TikTok. Honestly,
it was just so nice to be at a normal company. I know there are people who are going to disagree
with the things that the Babylon Bee and Seth Dillon put out. But in terms of being a business
owner, like Seth was a really good boss, you know, outside of hieration calling me at 9pm.
I was like, wait, like we're off at five, everyone leaves the office at five, like there's no
screaming, there's no yelling and everyone gets paid on time. This is wonderful. And I am just
happy at this point to be doing like a normal job, you know, working with our Google Ads teams and
helping put on live events and making sure you know, going through our subscriptions and
subscribers like it is the most normal job I had ever had. This job is also offering me
more legitimacy because Seth had a rather reputable name within the MAGA space. So I'm
simultaneously getting more calls from Fox News, etc. And again, this is the most normal job I had.
Until Elon Musk bought Twitter. Oh, I forgot to say while I was at the Arsenal, the company with
Jason Cole and Benny Johnson, that is when I am reached out to about the anti-trans book deal,
okay, by the company that I ended up publishing this with. And again, I have spoken about my
remorse for being involved in this, I removed my name from the book, and I do not have the ability
to take it off the shelf. However, at this time, I am at this company and I am pregnant,
like I'm doing the promotion for this book pregnant. And I am like, I don't know what to do,
I need money, I need to get out of this company. And this was obviously the wrong thing to do.
However, I also think there's like a misconception about how much money I made from this book,
it really was not a lot. I'm not exactly allowed to disclose the details of it. But
really wasn't enough to cover rent in New York City, okay. So I just want to acknowledge that
me being in a bad personal situation and needing money to pay bills was not an excuse for me doing
this book deal. I'm rather just giving context to the financial desperation I had at this point,
though I am fully aware that it is not okay, no matter the financial desperation to then use
what none of it was okay. Okay, so back to the Babylon Bee. For those who don't know,
the Babylon Bee was completely locked out of their Twitter account because they had made
a anti trans joke about the former, I believe she was the Secretary of Health Rachel Levin.
And so the bee gets locked out of their Twitter account. And they are like, we're not gonna
delete the tweet and get our account back. So then when Elon Musk buys Twitter, he basically
text Seth and is Elon text Seth and is like, would you like the bee restored? For the longest time
when Seth would say like, oh, Elon texted me asking this, you know, are we're gonna get the
bee back? I thought these people were joking because basically our entire Slack channel
was jokes. I never knew when these people were being serious. But it became abundantly clear
that wait a second. They're being dead ass right now. At this point, my only knowledge of Elon Musk
is that he does the rockets and the cars because my gay best friend used to force me to watch
this man's rocket launches. And I think like one of the only tweets I ever had about Elon before
the fire nation attacked was when he pulled out of the Twitter deal. And I had tweeted that this
is the first time Elon Musk has ever pulled out. This tweet would come back to haunt me.
Now while at the Babylon Bee and working with Libs of TikTok, I think having a normal job and
a boss who I knew wasn't gonna fire me for having the wrong opinions. I started to
divert a little bit in my political opinions publicly and privately. As I had mentioned in
my previous video, I am privately fighting with Haya about the way in which she is handling
this information and her posts about different trans individuals.
Seth is making jokes about me being a trans ally. But I'm also becoming a bit more bold publicly
here and there. Again, I still had just putting out harmful rhetoric.
But I was able to divert a little bit and say, you know, these people don't care. I don't even
consider myself a conservative. There's a video of me from I think 2023 or 2024 where I'm like,
I don't want any part of this. You guys treat women horribly. I don't like any of this rhetoric
that's going on. And basically saying that Trump and all of these other Republicans were using them
um eventually then I went the other way. But I am starting to divert a little because of my
freedom of capital here. When Elon Musk buys Twitter, he is the most popular account on
Twitter. Everyone is watching like a hawk. Everything he replies to, all of a sudden
he's starting to reply to conservative accounts all the time. And this is like a big moment
for MAGA and the right. They are like, here's our chance. Okay, you want to talk about gold diggers?
These people all saw dollar signs when Elon started posting right wing slop. Now one of the
right wing slop accounts that Elon takes a particular interest with and follows and is
replying to nonstop is yours truly. I genuinely don't think people understand like what the
pathology of MAGA was when Elon first started responding to right wing accounts either.
I remember the first time that he responded to me on Twitter. I was getting congratulation texts.
Okay, nonetheless, um simultaneously Seth is trying to schedule a interview with Elon at the
Twitter HQ. I forgot to mention but by early 2022, I am the father of my child and I are not together.
It's whatever. We're also like friends now. It's fine. But important to note because I am a single
mom by 2023 when this starts transpiring. So because I am suffering from potentially the worst
case of pygmyism ever, I am stoked about these developments. Okay, I am like, oh you guys thought
I was too controversial. Well, the most successful man in the world thinks I'm funny as shit. Okay.
Again, Seth is trying to schedule this interview with Elon with the Babylon Bee
and then Elon slides into my DMs.