Get ready with me because I am in a wee bit of trouble for discussing Erika Kirk, so we're going to discuss Erika Kirk a little bit more.
For those who don't know, my name is Ashley St. Clair.
I was a MAGA influencer involved in MAGA politics for almost a decade.
I know.
Now, I had made a TikTok about Erika Kirk being upset about the Drewski skit calling it whiteface, which whiteface isn't real, okay?
It's objectively not real, okay?
Blackface is real because of the history in this country and the blatant racism associated with it, okay?
Whiteface is not real, but I will digress.
After I posted this video, I deleted it because I thought the comments to Erika Kirk were too mean, and I don't know.
I'm a sap, and I don't agree with her on really anything, but I was like, oh, this woman's being dogpiled in my comments, and as a mother, I don't know.
It was just uncomfortable, and I thought I was being as charitable as possible to Erika, just giving her advice from my experience that I think the people giving her advice are awful.
I think she needs to log off and take some time because that's what was most helpful for me when I was going through a lot.
Nonetheless, this video has still been making the rounds on Twitter and going viral despite me not even being on that godforsaken platform because, again, they're suing me.
Also, I'm gonna go try this invaluable ProBlow again because I'm so mad about the luminous silk still.
I've made a big mistake.
I've put too much on, but we're gonna roll with it.
Now, if people want to keep me in this conversation, whatever, then I will keep talking about it, and I will tell you guys how I really feel because I also have text from Charlie that I think could help everyone in this moment.
Now, Erika Kirk goes on this long rant about dehumanization and that the epidemic plaguing this country is dehumanization, and we're not even going to go into the rhetoric of Charlie towards the end of his life because it wasn't great.
Saying that you're not going to get on a plane if there's a black pilot.
Like, dude, what the fuck?
Nonetheless, if we all remember in the aftermath of Charlie Kirk's assassination, many, many people got fired.
The right wing and MAGA went on a freaking jihad over anyone who said something, anyone who really wasn't sad that Charlie had died.
They were not understanding about this at all, and to me, I get a lot of criticism.
I have people who are still very angry at me for my contribution to the harmful rhetoric and this goddamn dictator oompa loompa in the Oval Office, okay?
And you know what I do?
I'm understanding of that because I am being introspective about my own contributions here, but they don't seem to have this introspection.
Instead, they got people fired.
People, they have not followed up with these people.
They have no idea the damage they did to people's lives because they got them fired from their jobs.
There's a professor who won't get tenure because they disagreed with her sentiments on the death of Charlie, and all of this is in the name of honoring a man who was killed, but if you want my real opinion, I don't think anything has been more dehumanizing and disrespectful to a dead man than what Turning Point, Andrew Colvette, and all of those folks have done to him after he died.
One thing about Charlie is Charlie liked results.
Charlie liked when things were viral.
Charlie liked when there was social media engagement, and I don't think he would be too happy that they have been posting from a dead man's account and keeping his show alive just for it to fucking flop, okay?
The videos on the Charlie Kirk Show YouTube channel are flops.
I could get more views doing a stupid TikTok sound than these people are getting on the Charlie Kirk Show YouTube page.
Nonetheless, okay, they do this whole video, this live stream, a special message from Erica Kirk, and something that has gone rather unnoticed because it wasn't in the live stream, but it is on the YouTube channel, is halfway through this special message from Charlie's widow, is a fucking ad read from Andrew Colvette.
He's so unhinged that he's able to teach children by day and then attempt to murder the president of the United States by night.
On TikTok, teens get over 50 built-in protections from the start, but for parents, further visibility and control of content can help create the right environment.
That's where family pairing comes in.
Who the fuck puts an ad read?
By the way, it's an ad read for TikTok, ironically enough.
Who the fuck puts an ad read on a message from the dead guy's widow on his show that you guys are insisting that you run?
Weird enough, right?
Okay, but then she goes, again, she goes on this rant about dehumanization and basically she's blaming Drewski, Candace Owens, and the left.
That is what MAGA's doing.
They are saying that these people are the ones dehumanizing people, but from my own personal experience, I had engaged in a lot of harmful rhetoric, transphobic rhetoric to the trans community.
At no point when I was engaging in this harmful rhetoric did any trans person or person or someone who supported the trans community threaten to take my children at gunpoint.
That did happen, however, after someone decided, and all of MAGA, after I was remorseful and I humanized the trans community and I said, hey, I'm actually remorseful about my dehumanizing rhetoric.
I am remorseful about the damage that I did to trans individuals.
After I posted this, the entirety of MAGA and the right wing with their trans panic dehumanized me and my children and said they want to take my child at gunpoint.
I am just absolutely sick of these people blaming the left and everyone else except themselves for the current conditions of the United States, okay?
We have an administration who is arresting Don Lemon and MAGA is cheering.
We have an administration who is arresting James Comey, okay?
And you want to sit here and talk about dehumanization?
Do you really think James Comey and Don Lemon are our biggest issues?
Why don't you speak out about that?
Why are you only speaking out when people are saying not nice things about you?
When you really think about it, you just want to speak in broad terms about dehumanization, but you don't really give any examples and there are plenty on both sides, one more than the other, and that's the side you're a part of.
And again, whether we like to admit it or not, Charlie played a big role in this towards the end of his life and I don't think that anything is going to get better unless there's a recognition about your own role in the nightmare that is currently plaguing America.
If the financial situation at turning point is so bad that you need to interrupt this special message from the widow of the founder to have Andrew Colvette's stupid fucking face pop up and do an ad read, perhaps you should adjust course instead of doubling and tripling down like you appear to be doing.
You want to talk about dehumanization, but do you know if any of the people fired in the name of your late husband had children?
Do you know if those children were able to eat?
Do you know if they were able to keep their home?
Because again, not all of them had to go fund me for security as you did.
And again, Charlie and I disagreed vehemently, politically, both publicly and behind the scenes, but when I was young, there was a time that I was going through a very public media crisis and Charlie gave me really good advice and maybe you or anyone else can take it.
I know some people will have to consider the source, but Charlie said, keep creating good content.
Don't engage with these people.
I know it's tempting and you think the world is crashing.
I understand.
Focus on new positive content.
Don't be bitter.
Smile more and keep producing.
Remember what I told you.
The more you repeat their nonsense, the more people get aware of it.
Don't hesitate to text me whenever you need it.
I have been through this, but this is happening quicker to you than it ever did to me.
You have the correct enemies.
What will drive them mad is the constant flow of creative, strong, principled content.
Don't subtweet them.
Don't let it even show that you are getting hit.
The way you navigate a chapter like this will determine the course of your entire career.
These pop up every 18 months or so.
You are leveling up the people who engage and put themselves in disputes.
Remain at those levels.
To break through to higher planes, you have to pierce through the noise.
So a broken clock is right twice a day, I guess.
And it's difficult for me because there was, my entire youth was formed by this movement and these people, but I just, I don't know.
I'm really sick of people pretending like they're not part of the problem.
And I know because I did that for a long time.
I pretended like it was just the left who was dehumanizing people and that the right was just on the strong and mighty course.
And I encourage people within MAGA to really look at what's happening in this country and what you're a part of.
And turning point, you should fire people before you do ad reads on your dead husband show.