Get ready with me while I tell you
about meeting Elon and getting swept up into
the Elon orbit, I guess you could call
it, after he took over Twitter.
For those who don't know, my name is
Ashley St. Clair.
I was a MAGA influencer involved in MAGA
politics for almost a decade.
I know.
Now, if you haven't already, I encourage you
to watch the other videos in this playlist
to catch up on the timeline.
And I do want to put a disclaimer
here that when I'm talking about these things,
I'm going to be talking about them in
the present tense of the time at times.
So while my opinions and views have shifted
significantly, I also want people to understand the
pathology and my thought pattern during these various
times.
So the year is 2023.
At this point, I'm a single mom, which
was not received well by my right-wing
MAGA compatriots.
They are calling my son awful things, calling
my son a bastard, calling me a single
mom whore, what have you.
Okay, whatever.
Simultaneously, I am now working for Seth Dillon
and running the operations for various companies of
his, including the Babylon Bee, Lives of TikTok,
yada yada who.
Now at this point, this is the first
time, I'm 23 at this point, this is
the first time I have a stable paycheck.
I had had salaried jobs at those godforsaken
companies within MAGA before, but the companies were
a disaster and I really was not given
stable income.
I never knew when my next paycheck was
coming.
So this job with Seth and the Babylon
Bee, this is the first time I'm like,
okay, I'm on the right track.
I can provide for my child, for my
family, and I finally have some stable income
after a series of cancellations and very bad
Google search results.
I, at this time, I had also gone
through rather severe postpartum depression with my first
son, so I was just not in a
great place, okay, but at least I was
like, okay, at least I'm somewhat financially stable.
I was making decent money, though it was
basically nothing in New York City, but it
was enough for me to get what we
needed, at least the bare minimum.
Now, during this time, Big Tech and the
issue of free speech and censorship is one
of the biggest policies on the right and
within MAGA.
So when Elon Musk buys Twitter, this is
a big deal that is really taking over
the entire right wing.
Everyone from the left and the right is
watching everything that Elon posts.
I mean, it is, you kind of had
to be there, okay, and when he follows
me, he immediately begins responding and liking basically
everything of mine.
He subscribes to me, he's responding to my
posts where I'm talking about my kids saying,
like almost immediately, as soon as he follows
me, he's like, you should have more kids,
and I am inundated with the people saying,
oh, look, he found his next baby mama,
and it is really hard to explain to
people who were not involved just how many
eyeballs were on Elon and everything that he
was doing.
And there was like a cohort of right
wing accounts, including myself, that Elon had a
particular fixation with.
So I believe it was like two or
three days after Elon follows me, one of
my friends within MAGA is like, do you
want to be added to this group chat
with these other accounts that Elon follows in
response to a lot?
And at this point, again, like I don't
think anything of it.
I just think I'm like involved in this
like crazy new world where Elon's like getting
involved in right wing politics.
And this is like my entire social circle
is MAGA.
Okay, so I'm like, yay, a new group
chat with new friends and other people who
understand the insanity of like Elon responding, because
it really was, it was insane.
Like immediately, you're getting death threats, you're getting
journalists reaching out, my name is in print
next to his because he's responding to my
tweets about Ted Kaczynski, like the Unabomber.
It was just insane.
So I'm added to this group chat.
And like very quickly, this becomes like all
encompassing.
Mind you, simultaneously, I am working at the
Babylon Bee where we're like scheduling this interview
to do with Elon, like our Slack channel
for this project was literally called Elon Fest.
Okay.
So nonetheless, I, Elon, as I said, he
ends up DMing me.
And he's like, Are you ever in San
Francisco?
And I'm like, actually, I'm supposed to be
there whenever you get back to Seth, my
boss about an interview.
Within like 30 seconds, Seth calls me and
he's like, Elon just get got back to
me about an interview date.
Like, we need to book our flights to
San Francisco right now.
And I'm like, okay.
Now at this point, politically, Elon is like
primarily talking about the free speech issue because
he bought Twitter and you know, he's like
dipping his toes in right wing slop.
But so we go to San Francisco, we
do this interview.
And basically the whole time, like anytime Elon
tells a joke, he's like looking to me
to see my reaction.
I also have like footage of him like
checking me out while we were there.
It was like it was insane.
Anyways, and I'm like 23.
Okay.
And after the interview, I then get a
text from Elon because at this point, you
had given me his number.
And he is like, Do you feel like
going to Providence tonight?
Like as in Rhode Island.
So I am supposed to be cleaning up
with my fellow co workers from this interview.
And I'm like, Seth, I'm gonna leave my
phone on the table.
I need you to look at it.
And I'm leaving.
Like I gotta go.
I'm gonna go.
I was like, Oh, a side quest.
Yay, an adventure.
So right away, Elon is like, Okay, well
wheels up at midnight come to this like
private airport.
And I'm like, Oh, my God, what the
fuck am I getting involved in?
Like, am I about to be like Harvey
Weinstein here?
This is probably a bad idea.
But I'm gonna do it anyways.
Okay, like, at this point, I'm like, I'm
gonna do it for the plot.
Okay.
And so I get on his jet.
The first thing I say is I'm like,
Well, this is slightly better than commercial.
And I know there's this tendency because like,
Elon has become like such a caricature.
But like, I don't know how to explain
like how surreal it is in that moment.
You're like 23.
I'm a single mom.
And all of a sudden, I'm like, on
the jet of like the richest guy in
the world.
And he's like, pouring me red wine and
telling me how nice the wine is.
He like reiterates like four times.
He's like, this is a really nice bottle
of wine.
And I was like, honestly, I can't tell
the difference between this and a box of
Franzia.
But like, I'm sure it's nice if it's
your plane.
So like, I just don't know how much
I want to say here.
But so well, I guess this is relevant,
because there's so many and we'll we will
address this later, like the baby trapping scandal,
like people saying we baby trapped.
So not exactly proud of this, but like,
I was a young Okay, I slept with
him, the on this plane, join the mile
high club.
And the first time we engage in coitus,
do you know what he says to me?
He literally says, pick a name.
This man did not know me from Adam.
Okay.
So anyways, then we land in Providence.
I'm like told nothing, basically, I'm just like,
whisked away to this other car off of
the jet.
And then like, we're going to this hotel
that doubles as a Masonic Lodge, like what
the fuck?
At this point?
I'm like, I'm like, is this like real
life?
What the fuck is happening here?
Honestly.
So anyways, then eventually I go back to
New York.
Okay.
And in that moment, the contrast of lifestyle,
like being in this environment, where there's like
all the staff and security and, and jets
and this and that.
And then I'm like, on the train in
New York, it was like, it just felt
so, so, so surreal.
And I don't know that I'll ever be
able to articulate that feeling fully, but it
was just, it was insane.
So anyways, he does not stop texting me,
interacting with me, tweeting at me, DMing me,
calling me, whatever.
Okay.
And like I said, he is tweeting at
me incessantly.
And at this time, likes are public.
So there's this account that is like publishing
every time he likes one of my posts,
which is like multiple times a day at
this point.
And it was just a lot.
I'm getting people saying, Oh, next baby mama.
Oh, look, he found his next target, whatever.
And I'm ending up in headlines with this
dude.
Like, and I like did not know how
to deal with this.
It was like, it was like, multi-faceted.
Like I'm young and I'm like, Whoa, this
is like cool.
The, the, this guy, this super successful guy
thinks I'm smart and interesting and cool.
And like, it was very validating when I
was so insecure.
And like, I don't even know why I
did this.
Cause like, I have a good relationship with
my father.
Like, I'm sorry, dad.
But I just like really needed validation for
whatever reason.
Simultaneously, like when he is posting like right
-wing slop to me, it's not right-wing
slop because I'm so heavily meshed within the
Magical that to me, I'm like, Oh, look,
who's finally on the right side of history.
So I have no idea, like the implications
that this has for the country.
I am just like, well, I am getting
so many Twitter likes right now.
Every time he responds to me, this is
awesome.
In the same breath.
This is also really validating for me because
everyone within Maga like wants the Elon reply.
And mind you again, I had been canceled
on several occasions.
I had been, you know, I had all
of these controversies with turning point and it
like ruined my search engine results so I
can never get a normal job again.
So at this point I'm like, Oh yeah,
you guys thought I was too controversial for
turning point.
Well, look at me now.
And so for me, it was really validating
in a harmful way to have this interaction
with him all the time publicly.
And again, this like, I'm not saying any
of this to excuse my behavior, but rather
just explaining and giving context to something that
has been so public and spoken about without
my input for so long.
And hopefully to help other people who maybe
are searching for similar validation within those spheres.
Yeah, again, this is not an excuse for
any of my behavior or what I promoted
or whatever, but I was a very, very
broken individual who needed people to like me
very badly.
Also, what is happening is that all of
MAGA, these gold digging, grifting maggots, are obsessed
with anybody that Elon is responding to.
So they are really, really reaching out to
people like me and someone who was associated
with me called ALX because Elon was responding
to him a lot.
And these people from the highest levels of
power within MAGA and the lower levels, everyone
is like inundating us with requests like, oh,
can we get this to Elon?
Oh, I have this documentary.
Oh, I have this project.
Like everyone wants a bite at this apple.
Okay.
And so I am inundated with these requests.
And I actually get like a little bit
protective of Elon at this point, because I'm
like, wow, like everyone just like wants something
from him.
You know, this is crazy, like all of
these people.
So like, I kind of like took on
this self appointed role of like, filtering fucking
crazy people from him.
Elon is also like very out of his
element within the right wing and politics.
So he doesn't really understand like how half
of these things work.
And he's asking me like he is coming
to me asking about certain individuals, different things
in politics.
Like at one point, I was at his
house.
And he's like, so just explain XYZ to
me.
And like he really genuinely wanted to understand
how the entire apparatus worked.
I think I accidentally armed him with a
nuclear weapon in this capacity.
But we'll get to that later.
As I had mentioned, as well, MAGA was
not stoked that I was a single mom.
But Elon gave me validation in another sense
that he never cared about that.
It was almost like he liked that I
was a mom, he was really sweet about
my older son, like anytime we would meet
up, or he would invite me somewhere, he's
like, Oh, bring your older son and was
like, really, I felt very accepted in my
identity as another that would obviously change.
But yeah, I think very often, a lot
of my really serious posts are, are, you
know, highlighted.
But I was primarily a shit poster, guys.
Okay, I was making fun of Ron DeSantis's
heels.
And I, you know, I was questioning the
moon landing.
I was shit posting.
Okay.
And so the pathology at this point is
me and like, this group of like, other
idiots are essentially like, Oh my god, we
are going to meme this into existence.
Elon's going to save MAGA and free speech,
and we're going to meme it into the
universe.
Okay, so while it is incredibly serious, none
of us thought of it that way.
We were like, Ooh, we're gonna meme this
to shit.
And even saying this, like I know people
are going to be like, Oh, she's being
flippant about it.
Um, well, I'm being honest about the thought
pattern in that moment.
Okay.
At 23, with very lackluster capabilities to think
long term, I was I was just a
fucking idiot.
Okay.
Elon responding to anybody also gives them like,
this legitimacy, further legitimacy within the MAGA sphere.
Okay, Fox News is calling incessantly.
All of a sudden, they want me to
talk about the birth rates.
And things like this.
And I don't know, I hated myself then,
which is why I did many of these
things.
And I hate myself in retrospect, just like
thinking about the things that I did.
It makes me so uncomfortable.
I hate doing this.
But I just want to get it out
of my head off of my heart.
Like I I'm also because Elon is responding
and interacting with me so frequently publicly.
I'm also getting like this new audience and
network of like tech adjacent people and people
within his companies that are networking with me
and connecting with me and starting to develop
these relationships with me.