Get ready with me while I tell you my part one about my experience with the women of Mar-a-Lago.
Let's get into it. For those who don't know, my name is Ashley St. Clair. I was a
MAGA influencer involved in MAGA politics for almost a decade. I know. Now for a little bit
of background, we need to talk about the beginnings of Mar-a-Lago and who Donald Trump was according to
the other elite circles and classes. While Donald Trump was this wealthy businessman,
he was not viewed this way among his peer circles of other wealthy business entrepreneurs and
businessmen. He was a bit of an outcast, seen as abrasive and people didn't really want him around.
Now Donny T did not like that, so he was like, you know what? Screw you guys. You're not going
invite me to your parties. I'm gonna have my own at Mar-a-Lago, which is also how he got involved
with little Jeffy, Jeffy boy. And Mar-a-Lago has been the hub for Donny T to pretend that people
like him and people want to come over to his house. It's quite literally his house. Now obviously when
Donny T ran for president, he was like, wow, perfect. Now I can invite all these people over
to my super cool house. They'll see how super duper cool I am. They'll see that I have all these
H-1B visa slaves who do whatever I want and this will go swimmingly. Now Mar-a-Lago very quickly
became a conservative hub. It was exclusive to be at Mar-a-Lago and get an invite to Mar-a-Lago
and people get their access to Mar-a-Lago through a few different avenues.
Oh, side note, I think spam callers should be put in prison for the rest of their life. Someone
needs to do something about that, but I digress. So you, there's a lot of people don't know, but
there's memberships to Mar-a-Lago and this fucking orange oompa loompa in the Oval Office sells these
memberships for a one million dollars per year. People are paying a million dollars to get access
to Mar-a-Lago. There's also events. So for example, people like Dinesh D'Souza will do a movie premiere
or Turning Point will do a gala there and people get invites and access through that avenue. And
then there is the last avenue for access to Mar-a-Lago which is the social climbing grifting
class of primarily women who just orbit around anybody who has access to Mar-a-Lago,
a lot of members of the Trump administration, etc. Now my first experiences at Mar-a-Lago were from
these invites to various events and whatever, it was fine. And then I also had friends who were
within this social climbing real white housewives of Mar-a-Lago type bullshit. And they were very
obsessed with every event at Mar-a-Lago, always going to Mar-a-Lago, let's see who can get us
into Mar-a-Lago. And I was just like, I was in the peripherals, like I worked in Jupiter for a while.
The office of one of my companies was in Jupiter so I was down there and then these girlfriends
would be like, do you want to come to Mar-a-Lago with us? I was like, sure, what else am I going to
do, go to the hotel bar and grab a bite? Sure, I'll go. Now one of these girls that I was friends with,
she's really not a girl, she's getting up there in age, we'll call her Ozempie,
since that's about her only personality trait. She was very involved in this Palm Beach Mar-a-Lago
socialite circle. And what became abundantly clear is that these girls are all backstabbing
bitches. The amount of tea and garbage and gossip that this woman spread about the Trump family,
which valid, and other people within this, the women of Mar-a-Lago was disgusting.
I mean there were, there's affairs, there's drugs, there's this, there's that.
And these people are at the White House, they are at the State Department now. Not only are
they at the State Department, but they're getting their friends who have absolutely zero background
in anything that they're getting jobs for, they're getting them jobs at the State Department now.
And they very much wheel, oh my god my cats, they very much wheel and deal in this relational
sabotage and rumor mill. So if there is, if these girls don't like someone, they are going to start
a rumor, they are going to call someone from the admin. It is just messy, messy, messy behavior.
At one point, Ozempty was going around telling everybody who would listen that
Alina Haba was sleeping with one or two of the Trumps.
Not my mouth, and Alina Haba, sorry if you're upset that I even say this, but you know exactly
who was spreading that, so please don't be mad at me, because this is what these people do.
Now anytime I would go to Mar-a-Lago with these girls, I was ready to just show up as I was,
and then they inducted me into this like Mar-a-Lago ritual basically, where they're
setting me up with their spray tan girl, and the makeup artist who is very nice, but,
and then telling me where to get clothes, what I should do, and then setting me up with their,
this is what they call her, not me, their China lady, because they have a China lady who gets
them all whatever designer they want, except fake, so that they can continue to play this game,
class signaling and wealth signaling to pretend that they're someone that they are not.
And their entire lives revolve around these political events and Mar-a-Lago events.
I mean it was an all-day affair. They were doing nothing else
except getting ready for these Mar-a-Lago events and drinking and
mind you they're also broke, so they would go to Mar-a-Lago and then when they would get these
drinks, they would just put them on random, under random members names, like Mar-a-Lago members.
Uh, also mind you, these women are married and then they treat Mar-a-Lago like a hunting ground
for their next victim, okay? They are constantly seeing if any of these men can put them in a
bitter position than they're currently in, um, which pretty funny since you guys all had that
criticism about me. Seems like projection. And mind you, in between these Mar-a-Lago events,
these people are rolling their tits off at Burning Man, which who cares? I think Burning Man's a
good time. However, you are working for an administration now which says that the peak
of degeneracy is trans people and gay people, while you're just rolling your ass off in the
uh, climb your way up into the White House, of which some of these people successfully did
by being a drunk hoe at Mar-a-Lago. And there were some good events and causes at Mar-a-Lago,
such as Laura Trump's charity, which is for St. Jude's, which I donated to and supported.
But then even at that event, we go to the St. Jude's charity event and then a couple of people from
this group, including one person at the White House, was like, that was nice. I guess we need
a palate cleanser for kids with cancer. Let's go to the strip club. Yeah, agreed. The kids with
cancer was heavy. Let's go, let's go forget about that with some titties. Really? And like whatever,
everyone likes to have a good time, but the issue is that these people pretend like they don't.
I've had my fair share of fun and degeneracy, but these people are championing and supporting an
administration that is taking the moral high ground while they are the most degenerate white
trash I've ever met. And I know this because I did all the white trash stuff with them.
And our country, our administration, our government is not a game for you to play and place your
little friends who have no business being in the government at positions at the State Department.
It's just absurd. And people can say whatever they want about me,
but I'm not making consequential decisions for the country and the world.