Get ready with me while I tell you why my ex's fuck-ass racist robot company is suing me.
We all know why, but I'll tell you why they say they are.
For those who don't know, my name is Ashley St. Clair. I used to be
a MAGA influencer involved in MAGA politics for almost a decade. I know.
So, starting out the 2026 New Year, I was woken up to a surprise. And that surprise was Grok,
the chatbot for XAI. Grok was undressing photos of me, including of me as a child. Now,
I was the wrong person to do that to, I'll tell you what.
So, after a series of begging this robot to stop and begging the company to stop having its robot
undress me, I filed suit with my very badass attorney, Kerry Goldberg, in New York. And really,
the crux of our lawsuit is a product liability issue that XAI released an unsafe product onto
the public, in which millions of women and children have been undressed and violated.
These images and videos that Grok produced of me were so horrific and traumatic to look at.
I was stripped down. They look hyper-realistic. And there were still real things from my life
in the background, like my older son's backpack was in the background of these photos of me
undressed. And it was a lot. And it wasn't just the images of me that were disturbing.
I also saw images of girls that looked about four years old who were stripped down, undressed,
and then covered in white sticky donut glaze. So, when I talk about how graphic and crass
and disgusting these images are, I would be banned for even sharing them. I'm scared that
I'm going to get stopped for having these images on my phone. Now, because within our lawsuit,
we are also requesting a TRL, or a temporary restraining order, against Grok so that Grok
stops this behavior immediately, right away, it is required that my attorney give notice to the
legal team at XAI, which she did. Now, these fuck-ass attorneys decide to take this notice
and use it as a basis for their own lawsuit, which they proceed to file right away in Texas.
Now, they are suing me for a minimum of $75,000 and claiming that
the basis of their lawsuit is that by me even filing a lawsuit after being undressed and
violated by their own product, that I have violated the XAI terms of service.
That's what they're going off of. So, to my knowledge, I am the only private citizen
ever sued for a terms of service violation that is not data scraping or fraud. They are suing me
simply because they are demanding that due to their terms of service, I am obligated to file
my suit in this rinky-dink court in Bumblefuck, Texas, where the only judge owns Tesla stocks.
Now, of course, I don't have the cheddar to be just fighting XAI in every jurisdiction imaginable.
So, I am in this Texas case pro se, which means I am representing myself no problemo. But yeah,
so now I have to fight and respond to these people by, I believe it's April 30th,
and file my own motion to dismiss this ridiculous lawsuit that was filed with
the utmost prejudice against me because they're not doing this to anybody else.
So, when we ask, why is XAI following this suit against me? The short answer is, we all know why
they're filing it against me. But the long answer is, they are claiming that I am, if I want any
sort of justice for being violated by their racist robot, that I need to adhere to their terms of
service, which claims I need to file in Texas. And I'm telling you this because I'm not going to
because most people don't really know what is within these terms of service and what the
implications are if something goes south, which on that platform is very, very likely.
And I am thankful and privileged enough that I have at least access to information and resources that
I can manage to handle this on my own. But this is awful for most standard victims in a
case like this, that you are undressed and violated by technology like this. And then
when you try to get remedy, you're countersued by a multi, multi, multi-billion dollar company.
And I'm not dumb enough to disclose everything that has been,
that I am aware of, but you would be very surprised what those overworked
and underpaid engineers tell and send to a pretty girl. Not to mention, the games that
these attorneys play are just so dirty. At one point when they were trying to
claim that they served me and served me with this ridiculous, ridiculous lawsuit,
they were stating that if I did not accept service, they were going to go ahead and dox my
address with my children. They said this quite explicitly, that they would have to file this
and it had my address. And they made no attempt at this, that juncture to redact or request that
that information be left out. And I have been made aware that Grok is still being trained,
not only to undress real women, but undress them better. This is what they're training
this sick ass, racist ass robot to do. So yeah, now I am pro se in the Northern District of Texas
matter. Our New York case is still going through though. And I am rather hopeful that the judge
does the right thing in that matter. But we, we shall see. In the meantime,
uh, these attorneys will be dealing with me pro se in Texas. And shout out to Kerry Goldberg.
If you are a woman on the internet who has experienced, uh, the wrath of these perverts,
reach out to Kerry. And the thing about this entire Grok scandal is that it did not have to
be released on the public this way. And it is my opinion that this was entirely intentional.
Because amidst this scandal, XAI raised billions of dollars. And again, my opinion is that the issue
Grok was facing at this time was that, and still, is that nobody wanted to play with Grok.
Everyone else was beating Grok. More people were using chat GPT and Gemini and the others,
and nobody wanted to play with Grok. So what that means, if nobody wants to play with your product,
then you have an issue of usage for numbers when you are going to investors or anyone who
you are trying to siphon more cash from. And suddenly their usage is up 500 million,
bagillion percent. Very curious. And so what that means, in my opinion, and what do I know, is
that women and children were used as collateral to up the usage numbers for this racist mecha robot.
And this entire situation has caused global outrage from France and the EU and multiple
other countries trying to take action against XAI for this behavior. But of course, the party of
family values is swooping in to make sure that nothing happens to their best buddy's racist
robot. And I'm sure XAI's attorneys will find some reason to complain about this video itself
for $2,000 an hour. But, uh...