I think it's time for a lawsuit update.
At least on one of them.
Hi, my name is Ashley St. Clair,
and for those unfamiliar, I am currently suing XAI
because of the actions of its chatbot, Grok.
If you weren't paying attention to the news
a couple months ago, Grok was released onto the public
with a new image generation and manipulation feature
in which it was allowed to undress women and children
without any parameters,
and then distribute this publicly on the X platform.
I was the wrong person to do that to, I will tell you what.
So I went ahead and got an attorney,
and we decided to sue XAI for this behavior
because it was egregious.
So we sued XAI in New York
because they released an unsafe product onto the public.
This is a public nuisance.
It's a product liability issue,
among many, many other things.
Now, XAI is countersuing me
for terms of service violation in Texas
because they claim, under the terms of service of XAI
and now X, that I need to, if I'm to take any action,
I'm supposed to sue them in one rinky-dink court
in Bumblefuck, Texas, where the only judge
is the judge who owns test stocks.
If you haven't been in a lawsuit
or any legal conundrum before,
the process is really laborious,
and it's not really accessible to most people
who need help because of how tedious it is.
Though we filed this lawsuit in January,
we're still fighting over venue
and whether or not I am bound by the terms of service
after this chatbot decided to abuse me.
Why am I updating you on this, right?
Everyone wants the big updates.
We won, we took down XAI, we took down Grok.
I'm updating you because of the arguments
that they're using.
XAI has claimed that I am bound
by XAI's terms of service
and that I have to bring this lawsuit in Texas
or that I'm released of different claims, yada yada who,
but they are also claiming this for X.
They are claiming that since I have an X account,
even though I haven't used it
since beginning this litigation,
they are claiming that I am bound
by the X terms of service,
which they say states that any claims
against any of X's affiliates,
which at this point could be SpaceX, Tesla,
XAI, Elon Musk himself, who knows?
These undefined affiliates.
You must also take this to this rinky-dink court
in Bumblefuck, Texas,
where the only judge owns Tesla stocks.
And I say all of this to tell you guys
that having an X account at all
can damage your future potential
of bringing accountability to this company
if you are also harmed by its products,
by its actions, so on and so forth.
Terms of service are really the only place in the world
where you can have these one-click legal agreements
where there's no negotiation,
there's no revisions of the contract.
You are just bound to this long list of demands
that mostly benefit the company.
As I said, I have not used X since this litigation began.
I can't log in because then they'll claim
that I am bound by this terms of service,
which whatever, I've been kicked out
of better places before, Janika.
You really, really need to be careful
about these accounts and these platforms that you use
because it could impact your ability
for justice or accountability later on.