Doing My Makeup Like My MAGA Haters, Part 1.
Now this cognitive traffic cone was very offended that I said MAGA is stupid, like really fucking
stupid, and that they all do tricks on Dear Daddy Oompa Loompa's dick for a couple Facebook
dollars.
This seemingly offended this aesthetic nightmare so much that she made a video calling me Elon
Musk's crazy baby mama and accusing me of being paid with Harry Sisson to work for the
Democrats.
Newsflash, I hate you for free.
Now I am not one to make fun of the terminally ill, but this woman seems to be suffering
from a fatal case of Mar-a-Lago phase.
But even worse is it doesn't seem like she even goes to Mar-a-Lago.
Instead, she does MAGA Patriot meetups at whatever rinky-dink bar she can find in the
middle of nowhere Florida, because of course she lives in Florida.
And then she runs a podcast with her co-host, who is the worst case of millennial cringe
I've ever seen, in which they start out each episode saying hold on to your buttcheeks
patriots.
Hold on to your buttcheeks people.
Oh my god I'm so excited.
Y'all are not ready.
You're not ready.
I'm not even ready.
Oh ermagerd.
This week.
Fuck.
I put way too much fucking wasabi on that.
Now finding this woman's real face was no easy task, because she uses more filters than
a fucking HVAC company.
She also uses so many AI renditions of herself that I would not be surprised if Governor Ron
DeSantis calls that there's a water shortage in Florida because of this woman.
Anyways, we will be using both her real face and these filtered photos as inspiration for
today's look.
For our base, we are going to be using a foundation that is about 18 shades too dark and bordering
on blackface, because that is the first step to Republican makeup.
Now typically as a civilized person, I would blend this down my neck, but today we are MAGA.
Perfect.
We also want our concealer to be offensively white, just like our country.
Now I always say my eyebrows are sisters, not twins, because you can't get it right
100% of the time.
However, this woman's eyebrows are very, very distant cousins.
Wow, perfect.
That looks about right.
I need more sushi.
This is exhausting.
Now here is where we lose absolutely all civility and go absolutely apeshit on our bronzer.
And I mean completely fucking apeshit.
Oh my god, how fucking far down does she do this?
Perfect.
Now it's really hard to tell if she does contour over her lips or if that is just the shadow
from the worst case of filler migration I've ever seen in my life.
If it is the latter, I would call an attorney because I think you have one of the best medical
malpractice cases against an esthetician I've ever seen in my life.
Now for the eyes, which I love what she does with her eyes, because when I see these images,
I'm reminded of when my toddler first had to draw and paint and then he would just mix
all the colors together until they looked something and resembled something like shit.
It brought back really good memories.
It looks like she was attempting to do a cut crease but then had a medical emergency halfway
through, so I hope she's okay.
And it wouldn't be a true MAGA Patriot Republican eye look without an offensive amount of glitter
on this attempted cut crease.
Now that's not enough.
We need more.
More.
Perfect.
Now, I'm quite unsure what the fuck is going on under her eyes.
I do believe she missed the part in math class where you're supposed to do one to one side
what you do to the other.
Nonetheless, we're going to do exactly what she did.
Oops, I forgot to powder.
Perfect.
With the amount of time this woman spends on the internet, you would have thought that
she'd come across one winged eyeliner tutorial, but it doesn't look that way.
We do a hard swoop, very thick, and don't be worried about precision here.
There are no mistakes in art.
Perfect.
It also looks like she likes to tightline her waterline.
This woman alternates between nothing on her lips and the most offensive shade of brown.
I've ever seen in my life.
Even this may be too normal, but we're gonna roll with it.
I decided to go a little more brown for accuracy.
Now last but not least for this woman's look and for any good Republican look, you need
an offensive amount of highlighter because we don't care about decorum.
We're not politically correct, and we don't even care where the fuck this goes.
Nailed it.
Now it's time to get dressed, starting with our accessories.
Luckily, I kept some of mine from my time being a demonic maggot.
Now while this woman traditionally dresses like someone who may have a GoFundMe for saying
the N-word at a children's playground, it is a costume, and I kept many of my costumes
from my time in Magga World.
Let's get dressed.
First, we're gonna need some really fucking ugly denim shorts.
Perfect.
Next, we need a graphic tee that pays homage to our dear leader.
This isn't your mama's Magga, so we're allowed to wear crop tops now.
We can actually tie our shirts up.
They allow us to do that now.
Next, we need the ugliest fucking trucker hat you can find.
And we're all in luck because I've kept my relics from the underworld.
This one isn't patriotic enough since it's just about Bitcoin, but we do have several
options, including some signed by her dear daddy leader.
Ugh, I made this a thing, and I regret every second of it.
Perfect.
Last but not least, we will be adding the bold glamour filter, and I think we will have
pulled this look off with perfect precision.
Ruh-roh, you are most crazy, baby mama.
I was coordinating with the demon rats.
Perfect.