We shouldn't trust Ashley St. Clair.
She's just scripting.
She's making this up.
What?
Okay, then don't.
Then don't trust me.
Don't believe me.
My life changes like not even a little bit if you don't believe me.
I'm putting this out there because I feel like it's the right thing to do to talk about this and I feel guilty that I did not talk about it sooner, but hopefully people can understand.
You want more?
You want more mac and cheese?
Hopefully people can understand why I didn't.
And I'm angry.
I'm really angry about the things that have been done to my family.
Like I'm angry for my children.
So, yeah, I've also seen just like some crazy stuff.
People being like, she's doing this to sabotage the midterms to make the Democrats less likely to vote in the midterms.
What?
If I'm sabotaging anyone, you really think it's the Democrats with everything I just told you guys for real?
No, I am.
I'm just telling you what was said to me.
I'm telling you what I know.
I'm telling you what I experienced.
Take it or leave it.
I understand.
Like I genuinely understand why some people are distrustful or it might take them time to trust me.
I get it, but I don't know man.
There's just some wild conspiracies.
And I'm doing this like, you really think I just sat here and I'm like, oh, I know the way to grift.
I know the best way to grift and make money.
I'm going to punch the most powerful people in the world who control the White House, the federal government, all of the people who could harm me.
I'm gonna punch them in the face just for funsies.
That's my bright idea for a grift.
What are you doing, baby?
Yeah.