This is a message for Benny Johnson. Since I came forward about my experience with that predator,
Madison Cawthorn, I had mentioned in my video that Benny Johnson, I had disclosed to him
that I had experienced this behavior with Madison Cawthorn and that Benny has continued to platform
this awful human being. However, I'm not a consumer of Benny Johnson content because I value my IQ
and I'm not one of his cerebral speed bump boomer followers. Unfortunately, I've watched his content
in the last 24 hours because it's been sent to me and before yesterday, I was unaware of the
content that Benny Johnson had been putting out about me on his show, including about my family
and my children and that I should lose my child, that I am not a sane parent, that I am a narcissist,
making up lies about my finances and my family situation. So Benny, I have been sitting on the
receipts of you for far too long. You and your sociopathic behavior and the way you operate
your businesses and your grift. So you want to go Benny? You want to talk about my children
and make this personal? Let's go because I have been sitting on this for far too long and guess
what? A lot of people have been sitting on things about you for far too long and I will remind you
that if you live in a glass house, stop throwing stones for your little Facebook dollars. TTFN,
you're next.