Space technology in the election.
I should also say that I have all of this backed up with many people with explicit instructions,
should anything happen to me, okay? All right, Emily, so we've reviewed actually and obtained
some of these text messages, and what Ashley Sinclair is claiming Musk claimed is true,
and I say that quite deliberately because there's a difference between Musk making a claim and Musk
claim being true. However, what he says matters, and her reference to depositions I think is
telling. But yeah, so he wrote to her, tomorrow we unleash the anomaly in the matrix, this is not
something on the chessboard, so they will be quite surprised, quote, lasers from space, and then she
does tell her joke referencing kind of a Marjorie Taylor Greene thing. Finally, a focus on the
10,000 layers, lasers in space right now, and she does in fact then reply, I would ask more questions
but will keep myself from getting deposed, and Musk responds, wise, with the laughing guy,
and then she says something like, you know, if your space lasers seriously end up being the
anomaly in the matrix that takes back America, I will be convinced that God is maximizing
the simulation. So this conversation did happen in early October while
Musk was campaigning with Trump and Butler when they went back to the scene of the attempted
assassination. Back to that, Ashley Sinclair immediately thought that depositions are coming,
suggests that there probably should be some, like this is something we should,
these are questions that ought to be answered, I would think. Well, Musk seemed to agree that
depositions could be coming when he responded with what the laughing face emoji, wise. Yeah, wise,
wise, yes, don't ask, don't ask anymore. I think with Ashley Sinclair they thought they had an NPC,
turns out they didn't. Yeah, so I think we're going to continue to find out more.