Get ready with me while I talk about when things started going south with Yvonne.
For those who don't know, my name is Ashley St. Clair.
I was a MAGA influencer involved in MAGA politics for almost a decade, I know.
Now before we get into the story time, I want to show you guys something because someone pointed this out in my comments.
This is the C12 serum I usually use and when I put it on, someone in the comments said, that is really dark, it's not supposed to be that dark, it means that your serum has oxidized.
And I'm like, you know what?
Let me just get another one to see if this bitch is crazy.
She's not.
Like how did I not, how did I not notice this?
Oh my god.
Anyways, PSA, make sure your vitamin C serum does not oxidize because what have I been putting on my skin?
So at this point, it's like late 2023 and my relationship with Elon feels emotionally intimate, okay?
I don't really care how he would characterize it, but I'm just gonna tell you guys my experience.
And by late 2023, it's, you know, we're speaking often, he's calling me, he's texting me, he's sending me, you know, I was just thinking about you texts, he's sending me his favorite songs, he's talking to me about the things going on in his life and with the companies, whatever.
He's telling me he doesn't really want to work at Tesla anymore but he has no one who can take it over for him.
Like he's, at least to me, this feels like intimate.
So by January 2024, this is New Years of 2024, he sends me a text and he's like, I'm going to St. Bart's for a few days, like do you want to join me?
And I am like, right away, I'm on the plane, let's go.
Also at this time, because he's interacting with me publicly so often, there are a lot of people speculating that we are seeing each other, that I'm the next baby mama, like it's becoming overwhelming at this point to the point that like everyone asks me about it, my doorman, my family, my friends, random people on the internet.
And I remember one instance in particular, we were on his chat and I was like, hey, by the way, like there's a lot of people speculating and if you don't want people to know about this, maybe cool it on the replies to me.
And he's like, oh, that makes sense, that makes sense.
And then he starts laughing hysterically a few minutes later and I'm like, what the fuck are you laughing at?
And I look down at my phone and he's responding to more of my tweets, like he thinks this is funny.
So in my head, I'm like, well, I guess he doesn't care.
So I meet up with him in St. Barts with, we're staying with Joe Gebbia and his wife, the founder of Airbnb.
And at this point in my life, because I'm involved in MAGA and the right wing, like, and I'm already a single mom, I actually, I'm going to do this first.
I believe the chances of me getting married and my, the white picket fence and the white dress, I believe that's out the window for me because I'm already stained as a single mom.
But I wanted nothing more than to just be a mom.
I wanted more kids, I would love to have a daughter one day, love my sons.
I also want a daughter.
I need someone besides TikTok to share my makeup tips with.
And so I, the prospect of being with someone who wanted me to have more kids, and I wouldn't have to worry about anything, especially like, since it's difficult being a single mom, it's difficult working and having to, you know, wonder if you're going to be able to pay the bills for your kids the next month.
And I think an economic factor is a decision when anybody has kids with anybody.
Like the, there's this notion that like, oh, everybody who has kids with each other, it's just like, because they're just so passionate and in the moment, like, no, most people who are like, have more than two brain cells when they talk about family planning and having kids, like, the economics of it is a big factor.
That's why so many people don't have kids.
That is the top reason given for abortions in this country, or, you know, choosing not to have children is the economic factors.
And so when Elon is like, you know, you should have more kids, my only limited resources time, like, of course, it is appealing to do what I've always wanted to do, be a mom, and not have to worry about the shit going on in this economy.
Like, that is just, and I don't think that's a crazy position to take.
I don't think that's crazy reasoning.
Like, never was I like, oh, I'm gonna make it big.
This is my ticket to a Birkin.
No, it's more like, my kids are always going to be taken care of.
And also, like, let's be honest, I'm a young hoe at Mar-a-Lago.
Like, if I wanted to marry for money, I could have done that a long time ago.
Because at this point, when I'm in St. Bart's, I'm ovulating.
So this is like a serious discussion for me.
And we have this conversation, and my child ends up being a consensual choice between two adults.
But as soon as I'm pregnant, this is when things start getting weird, okay?
He starts, there's just things that are not adding up, or that are different than what he had previously said to me.
For example, like, when I first got involved with him, I asked him, because I can read, okay?
So I asked him about Claire, Grimes, Siobhan, because, not because I wanted to be exclusive with this man, but because I'm a girl's and I never wanted to, like, put another woman in a situation where they thought they were monogamous with someone, and, you know, they're going around with a side hoe.
He basically tells me, he's like, no, Claire and I are good, we just co-parent, everything's hunky-dory, and me and Siobhan are just platonic, you know?
It's basically a financial agreement is what he tells me.
I also outright ask him, I am like, because again, I can read, like, everyone for the last, you know, umpteen years has talked about him having a harem and, you know, being in competition with Nick Cannon here.
So I'm like, how many, like, kids are there?
And he's like, you know, it's actually not as many as people think.
And I'm like, okay, well, like, how many?
And he tells me about the Justine, with Claire, with Siobhan, um, and then he also, I ask straight up about Amber Heard, because this is what I had heard, and he's like, no, I actually asked her because I thought they were mine, but she says that they're not, yada yada who.
So at least that's what he told me, but he also has a complicated relationship with the truth, so who knows?
However, he also tells me that there is one more with a Japanese woman, and he says that this came to fruition when these Japanese people, officials, came to speak to him.
And I actually remember when this happened, because he was with me right before he met with them, like, early 2023, and he even texted me afterwards.
I was like, how'd the Japan meeting go?
Because mind you, he was pretty under the influence when he met with these people.
And he texted me and was like, you know, it was interesting, they just want my sperm, no romance, just my sperm.
And then we didn't talk about it again until like, the next year, and he tells me that he did in fact do this.
So hearing this, I'm just like, what?
Okay, like, whatever.
This is just like, I'm not even gonna ask any more questions.
Okay, whatever.
And then when I'm like, I'm also starting to see things like he's, I'm starting to see that there were misrepresentations, at least regarding his situation with Claire Grimes.
That just made me uncomfortable because, mind you, I'm already a mother by the time I'm with Elon.
So I am viewing their interactions through the lens of a mother who does co-parent.
And like, there was one time where Claire was texting him, pleading for something like with the kids, and then he just texts back and he's like, I'm blocking you.
And he blocked her.
And like, in that moment, mind you, I'm already pregnant.
And I'm just like, oh my god, like, I can feel her despair as a mother.
Because he has your kids, and now you're blocked.
Like, this is crazy.
So I'm just seeing things that I'm like, that's a data point.
Like, I'm, I start realizing that I'm gonna have to keep my head on a swivel and protect myself.
Because anything that is too good to be true probably is.
So I'm just collecting these data points in my head.
Like, that was not great of him.
Also, maybe I'm like, I think I'm like six months pregnant.
And he tells me, oh, by the way, I should tell you, I'm technically living with Siobhan half of the time.
And I'm like, oh, well, that's certainly a development from, we're just platonic and this is a financial arrangement.
But okay.
And I'm like, does she know?
And he's like, no.
And he like, he's like, but but I haven't made any commitments to her.
I'm like, okay, man, this is just like, weird.
Like, everyone in the world thinks you have a harem.
Like, why don't you just like own this shit?
Like now why am I in this weird position?
Like, it's not even like I want some exclusivity with him.
I just don't want to be in this weird ass position.
Mind you, I am also while I'm pregnant, or I'm getting like calls and texts about other people that he's reaching out to like maybe two months after I had our son together, or a month, I'm like literally holding our like infant baby.
And I'm getting a call from Tiffany Fong, this influencer on Twitter.
And mind you, she has no idea that like, I have a child with Elon at this point.
She has no idea like our relationship, none of this.
And she calls me and she's like, dude, Elon just offered to have kids with me like in the DMs. And I'm like, what is this?
Like his DMs are like a gatling gun of sperm.
What is happening?
And she's like, I don't know what to do because I love my boyfriend so much.
But like, you know, I want to have kids.
And I'm just like, what the fuck?
So then the next time I see Elon in Texas, I bring this up to him.
And I was like, and we had a mutual friend.
So Joe his wife, Isabel, that I had met in St. Barts.
Like she was one of the only people who understood Elon that I felt like I could talk to and like confide in about certain things.
So I talked to her about this Tiffany Fong situation.
And she's like, you know, you should just talk to him.
Because I wasn't sure if I even wanted to bring it up.
So the next time I see him, I do.
And I'm like, hey, you know, I didn't really want to bring this up.
But you know, I spoke to Isabel and she said, I should just talk to you about it.
And I tell him like, Tiffany called me this and that.
He starts freaking out.
He gets so angry at me.
And he's like, why would you tell Isabel?
Like if she knows, then everybody's gonna know like he's getting like red in the face embarrassed.
And then he's like, mind you, like, actually, I don't know if I can say that.
But he so he starts furiously messaging Tiffany Fong.
I like think he blocks her unfollows her.
And it's like, don't ever like share our messages like freaking out.
And then he like, goes in his room.
He like slams the door.
He's like, if you need to talk to anybody, talk to your mother.
I'm like, what the fuck, dude?
Like what is wrong with you?
And I'm not the one.
Okay, so I straight up tell him I was like, I do not like the way you're speaking to me.
Like, this is like right after Thanksgiving.
Okay, I'm like, no, like, we're not gonna do that.
And so I left.
I was like, no, find another bitch to speak to that way, because it's not gonna be me.
I'm in this weird situation where you fucking weirdos have told me nothing like there's no like, this is weird.
And so then he texts me a little while later.
And he's like, I'm sorry, like for being short with you.
I want you to come meet my older sons.
But you know, I have to go to Mar-a-Lago to interview NASA administrators.
This is what he says to me.
Okay.
And I'm like, well, too bad.
So sad.
I'm already gone.
Simultaneously, I'm just seeing how willing he is to lie publicly and privately, but like about stupid shit.
Like, for example, when you know, Butler happened the assassination of Trump attempt on Trump.
Ilan comes out and he's like, it's this moment I have no choice but to support Donald Trump.
And I'm like, dude, what the fuck you've already been working on a pack for him.
Like, you're you were already supporting him.
Like why?
Why are you lying about like this being the catalyst for supporting Trump?
Like this is just, I don't know, it just like made me uncomfortable, especially like seeing how boldly and publicly he was just misrepresenting things.
And to me, this was kind of like shattering because I idolized him in many ways.
Like I looked up to him, I guess you could say.
And it's like one of those like, don't meet your heroes moments because I'm like, in my head, when I first got involved in this, he's like, you know, this free speech warrior who's speaking truth to power.
And like, meanwhile, like there's just all of this secrecy and these lies and these misrepresentations and this dysfunction.
And like, it's just dawning on me like what I got involved in.
And while my views now have changed on immigration on, you know, ICE enforcement.
At this time when I am like going hardcore on immigration, I'm coming from like a national security standpoint from like, you know, we want to maintain a safe country and there should be some sort of assimilation.
Okay, again, my views have shifted.
But this was my point of view.
It wasn't coming, I didn't think it was coming from a place of racism, what it promoted.
And my rhetoric helped promote people who were operating from racist standpoints.
But then like when I would talk to him, it would just, it was becoming more clear to me that he was coming more from like, a eugenic standpoint.
Also, while I'm pregnant, he's like telling me that we need to use surrogates if we want to have like a legion of children before the apocalypse or before the Civil War in America.
And I'm just not comfortable with surrogacy unless it's necessary for medical purposes.
And like, I just don't want to play rent a womb so that we can increase our output of babies here.
Like it was just weird to me.
He also told me that I should get a c-section like what because it's better for the head and the brain size.
What are you?
No, I'm not signing myself up for a c-section.
What?
No, thank you.
My portal works fine.
Like everything just got really weird, really, really fast.
And like, I swear nobody's gonna believe me, but he was so much more normal before I was pregnant.
Like he was, it was like very normal conversation.
Like his demeanor was normal.
And I know I'm gonna get roasted for this, but in private, like he was funny.
But then like it just got so weird, man.
And I genuinely, because this has been so consuming on my life, like I don't want to just talk about this forever.
Like I just want to get everything out there and then never talk about it again unless it's necessary.
But also, you know, people are like, oh, well like why do you talk about it so much?
Because I was, I was 25.
I'm 27 now.
Like this to me, this happens before I have like an established career, an established life.
Like this is the biggest thing that happens to me.
Like I am a young girl who's like now thrown into this thing.
Everything anyone knows about me is now like Elon Musk baby mama.
So yeah, I want to address it and move on.
The last time I went on CNN, they put mother of Elon Musk's children on my lower third.
I've been on TV before I met Elon.
That was never my lower third, okay?
And so I just want to get this all out there and then have my lower third be my name again.
And literally everything I do is like watched by eight attorneys, four different law firms.
Like I'm in three different courts.
Like I'm just so sick of this and like being painted as like I'm the one who's like combative and chaotic when I'm in three different courts and I have people following me all the time.
Like I just want to get this out there and like be done with it.
And yeah, when someone with so much influence and so much power puts out so many lies and smears about you, who you are as a mother, your child, it's gonna take a lot more than one post for me to correct the record.
So yeah.