Get ready with me while I talk about mental health and the stigmas I promoted around it.
Trigger warning, I will be speaking about mental health issues including anxiety, depression, self-harm, yada yada hoop.
For those who don't know, my name is Ashley St. Clair and I was a MAGA influencer involved in MAGA politics for almost a decade.
I know.
Now, I want to talk about the video I did in which I was explaining how many of these MAGA influencers are paid that they coordinate so much messaging through group chats with the White House and members of the Trump team and various other MAGA figureheads.
And I want to talk about this because I've seen my video being used a lot and one thing I don't want to contribute to, now that I'm being more aware of how my presence affects discourse and rhetoric, is I don't want to be a part of something that is...
The issues we're facing right now do not go away if Trump goes away.
What we are experiencing right now does not go away if MAGA goes away.
Rather, Trump and MAGA was able to be built off of a very, very broken system and this is systemic rot coming from capitalism at its death stage.
My god, I'm almost out of this and they discontinued this shade.
Now that that's out of the way, what I want to talk about today is mental health.
And don't worry, I have no shortage of tea, guys.
I was in that godforsaken movement for almost a decade.
I have no shortage of tea and we will be back to tea time very soon.
But I want to talk about mental health because it's been weighing on my conscience since during my time in MAGA, I really contributed to a lot of harmful and stigmatizing rhetoric around mental health, despite having my own struggles with mental health throughout my life.
And I've gone back and forth about speaking on mental health issues and my thoughts and my experience with it because it can be used against me by nefarious actors, by attorneys.
It can be quoted in any of the many litigations I am involved in.
But at the same time, I do have the ability to fight it and I think that it's important that I speak about it to help other people and undo some of the harmful things that I was speaking about while simultaneously struggling with these issues.
The right wing has a weird obsession with hating on any women who are in therapy or who are on SSRIs or getting any mental health treatment.
And I very much promoted that and now I am everything I made fun of.
I am the SSRI cat lady that I made fun of for years on Twitter.
But I want to talk about this because it's not something new and I do think some of my mental health struggles are why I fell into this cult of the right wing in MAGA in the first place.
Because since I was young, I struggled with anxiety and depression.
I had my first panic attack at 12 years old and when I went to the hospital, I was given one of the more popular numbing medications for this and I remember hating not being able to feel annoyed at my brothers.
I hated that numb feeling but I also hated having panic attacks.
Around the time that I started getting involved in MAGA, I was also the victim of an assault from a close friend in college and this really did a number on my mental health.
Which I think simultaneously, I already had these underlying issues of anxiety and depression that I was self-medicating with partying and various substances and drinking.
But after this assault, I ended up being placed on an anti-depression medication and I just didn't like the way it made me feel and I was getting really wrapped up in this right wing rhetoric and seeing like, oh they just want you on this, it makes you crazy.
And so I ditched the medications and I did not try any mental health treatment until many, many years later.
Instead, I was a public advocate against it when I had no business doing that.
I think there's this idea of self-harm that's very obvious and graphic and violent but self-harm can manifest in a variety of different ways and I think the people I surrounded myself with, the relationships I got into and the behavior I engaged in, was in retrospect a form of self-harm.
I was terribly insecure.
I was very broken.
I think I'm still broken in some ways but I'm working on putting those pieces back together and making, you know, a somewhat whole picture again.
When I had my first son, I struggled with severe postpartum depression and unfortunately the medication that they put me on at that time just exacerbated these awful, awful feelings and thoughts that I was having.
But I also engaged in therapy for the first time meaningfully and it really helped me.
It wasn't until my second pregnancy that I really got the mental health treatment that I needed and that has actually been incredibly helpful for me, including therapy and a medication that has worked for me.
I carry a lot of guilt for my past rhetoric around mental health issues and medication because I can't stop thinking about who isn't or didn't get the help that could have really done so much for their life and the way that they handle situations, who didn't get help because of the things that I said or the stigmas that I helped promote.
I also think it's fundamentally insane to look at this new world we have created where we are inundated with like infinite inputs and our brains are being having all these infinite inputs that we never had to deal with before and thinking that we are just naturally evolved as human beings to deal with this fucking cyborg transhumanist bullshit we've created.
I think that is incredibly ignorant to think that anybody naturally has the ability to deal with any of this and maybe some people do but I think a lot of us need help.
Something that really pisses me off about right-wingers is when they talk about things like say ADHD and children and they're like well these kids are in ADHD you know it didn't used to be like this.
Yeah but they weren't inundated with all of these inputs either.
Of course these kids have no idea what to focus on
neither do you when the president almost got shot again you're talking about a fucking ballroom like
nobody knows what the fuck to focus on what to look at where to focus their energy and
and also most of the people talking about ADHD isn't real are on fucking
bimans and Adderall okay all of the hill is on Adderall and while I've tried various treatments
what I suggest is you really need to find a good doctor who's willing to really closely monitor you
whenever you're doing a new treatment because the reality is especially with my first postpartum
incident my doctor probably should have tried me on a different medication and not just let me
go cold turkey and raw dog life and these people in MAGA promoted a significant portion of the
discourse to shitting on women and people who get mental health treatment or use SSRIs
but they didn't have that same rhetoric for alcohol or these parties with drugs and debauchery
and so you know a lot of the decisions that I regret I wonder if I would have made that if I
would have gotten help sooner instead of just self-medicating with the worst people on the
who also need help but what I've come to the realization about is that they need this
rhetoric that you don't need mental health treatment you don't need SSRIs and everything
is hunky-dory because if you don't recognize this you also don't recognize the drastic changes that
these uber capitalists and tech oligarchs who have made to our environment as human beings
the deep anthropological and ontological changes that they are making for the species being as a
whole and if you don't recognize how all of these inputs and that technology is evolving faster than
we can adapt to it they need you to not recognize that because throughout my time with access to
such high levels of power and people who drive rhetoric there's always a reason for everything
okay why do they want people to believe this and I think the human body has a perfect design I think
our bodies and our minds are really adept at reacting to things that are wrong or changes
or inputs within our environment and the fact that so many people are struggling and so many
people need to be medicated and have mental health issues that's an indictment on the environment that
these uber capitalists and this technocracy has created and that they are demanding that we
normalize and that we refuse to address so sorry that was a bit of a ramp but we'll be back to tea
time tomorrow