Get ready with me while I talk more shit.
For those unfamiliar, my name is Ashley Sinclair.
I used to be a MAGA influencer for almost a decade.
I know.
Let's get into it.
So the other day when I did the video on Jason Cole and Arsenal Media Group and my time at that company started by Benny Johnson and Jason, I cannot believe I forgot about the honey trap.
So not only was Jason Cole engaged in the most debaucherous debauchery ever, he was also setting honey traps.
And if you're unfamiliar, that's basically when you have a pretty girl trap a man into a compromisable position for blackmail.
And Jason quite explicitly set a honey trap for another competing consulting firm's main principal.
Now the girl who Jason used for this honey trap on this competitor is someone that a lot of people would know.
She is a moderately prominent, I don't want to give her too much credit, right wing MAGA influencer.
And Jason Cole had her recording this man drunk to use as blackmail.
According to Jason, he had her sleep with him and claimed that there was footage of such.
He also claimed to have footage on another prominent client of ours.
So when they talk about the files, right, and how things work in politics and oh, they must be blackmailed.
This is not a conspiracy.
At every level, they are doing this to each other.
They are holding footage, they are holding blackmail, they don't want to speak up because they don't want their own dirt exposed.
That is how all of this operates.
And I don't want to confuse not naming this girl with anyone thinking I'm protecting her.
I'm not naming her because she is such a bottom of the barrel.
My cats are wild.
She is such a bottom of the barrel grifter that that would be her best day ever if I named her and I just don't want to do that.
Even this, I'm like she will probably take this video and name herself.
That's how messy and trashy and tacky she is.
Anyways, today's video is more casual.
We'll get back into the tea on Monday, Tuesday, okay?
But a lot of questions about my skincare.
I use the Inua Wash Daily, and then I just use the Inua Toner.
And as always, I do my La Roche-Posay C12 and the Tatcha Dewey.
And then we throw on this illuminator.
I also want to do a video on some of the things that helped me deconstruct from MAGA and the right wing ecosystem.
Also, I'm doing this like Fenty blurring skin tint because I don't feel like doing like a lot of foundation today.
But I want to do a longer video on my deconstruction, what helped me and really unpacking how I got to where I am because my views have also shifted significantly.
But also I feel like they haven't.
There's been a very public shift, but in private, I feel like the people who know me.
Oh, hang on.
I feel like the people who know me know that there were some moments where I was going off the reservation in terms of MAGA ideology.
But I also still elements for what I did and promoted publicly.
So I'd like to do a video going more in depth into that.
Also, someone suggested that I use a cool tone contour stick.
So we're trying that today.
And all of these people, I was attacked relentlessly for a year, being called a gold digger and all these other smears.
Meanwhile, these people are ideological prostitutes.
Okay, there is nothing they won't do for a buck.
And by the time I'm done with them, I hope that that's abundantly clear to everybody else from the outside looking in.
I just think we have the worst people who have been promoted to the highest positions of influence and power.
That it is very difficult for me to say nothing.
And that's probably one of the biggest ideological shifts I've had is I am absolutely not a capitalist anymore.
Sorry.
Without a doubt.
There is something very, very broken with capitalism.
I think me seeing the levels of capitalism at the level that I did.
That shit don't work.
And I think the issue with a lot of MAGA is a lot of the issues that they identify, their diagnosis of the problem is wrong.
They have been taught to scapegoat every other community and marginalized group when the real issue is a class issue.
Also, one of the biggest turnoffs to this elite class, which I don't even know if you can classify this as that, was being at Mar-a-Lago the number of times that I was.
Because that's a whole other video in itself.
But the amount of class signaling and just tacky, tacky behavior going on at Mar-a-Lago.
Ugh.
And I know the average New York Times reader might be aware that that fucking Oompa Loompa in the Oval Office charges a million dollars a year for Mar-a-Lago memberships.
But I don't think the general public really understands how Mar-a-Lago operates from the memberships to this social climbing game.
So I think maybe I'll do a video on that on Monday.
And these people really, they should be more ashamed that they engage in this behavior, that they are a part of this social climbing Mar-a-Lago class.
Like the White House has turned into like the Real Housewives of DC.
And it's, it's just so trashy.
Also for the party who always talks about bringing back manly men and men need to be men again.
They are the biggest pussies I've ever met in my life.
Like even Benny Johnson, after I posted my video saying that I was I am going to expose him and do a long form video on what a fucking sociopath grifter he is.
He takes to Twitter.
He takes to Twitter to say that he doesn't know why people are being so upset and engaging in drama.
Because you talked about my child asshole like they they can never stand when someone punches them back.
There's such whims I can't.
What a pussy do you have to be to respond to me on Twitter when you know I'm not on there.
I cannot go on there because I am being sued by them.
Okay, you are a fucking coward.
They're also just completely incapable of taking responsibility like that drop just came out talking about how Cash Patel is just running around drunk not showing up to work.
He's an alcoholic and basically has turned the FBI into a frat house.
And then he comes out saying it's a lie.
I'm gonna sue you get your checkbooks ready.
As if we didn't all watch this man like slam back a beer bottles up to with the US hockey team.
Okay, I can't throw a beer back like that because I don't drink like that.
Only someone with alcoholic tendencies can smash a beer like that.
And I know everyone wants all the tea right away because you guys have no patience.
But you must understand some tea is better suited for when their friends are not in power.
Because a lot of this stuff is also criminal.
But above all, I am just happy to be myself and not be some fringe MAGA talking head and deconstruct the harmful ideologies that I got thrown into very young and just live the most honest articulation of myself that I can for my kids.
TTFM