Get ready with me while I tell you about how the FBI investigated me for years over January 6th.
Before I get into the story time, I just want to say as I'm watching this back, I feel like I can
sound flippant at times or I'm being a bit nonchalant about what transpired on this day
and I just want to put a disclaimer that I am not discounting or being flippant about what
transpired or my involvement. However, it was traumatic to be involved in these things and
investigated by the FBI and I know some people are going to say, well that's what you get.
However, I just want to say, sorry if I come across as flippant, here's the story.
For those who don't know, my name is Ashley St. Clair and I was a right-wing MAGA influencer for
almost a decade. I know. Now, this story takes place around the 2020 election and to really
understand the conditions, you have to understand the rhetoric that was happening around the
stop the steal and the election integrity questions. What was really taking over the
discourse at this time was the notion that our elections were not secure and that we needed to
stop the steal of the 2020 election. Now, I will say there are some points to be made about how we
run our elections in the United States and it could be better. We do have election integrity
issues and we should run our elections better. However, the extent to which this was overblown
in the 2020 election was, as we all know now, absurd. Nonetheless, I bought into a lot of this
overblown rhetoric and promoted a lot of this overblown rhetoric. In around the 2020 election,
I was invited to speak at a stop the steal event and honestly, I really was going to show up
anywhere where they gave me a little graphic and where I felt important. Where they were like,
you're so important and smart, you can speak here. So, they gave me a graphic and I was like, oh,
I'm so cool and smart. Come see me at this event. They fly me out for this stop the steal event in
Wisconsin, which I speak about and the event itself is like rather tame. It's kind of nothing. I fly
out. It's fine. However, this is relevant because I attend this event. I end up being placed in
group chats and communications with all of the organizers of the stop the steal event,
which will become relevant. Now, as these stop the steal events continue progressing and the
conversations progress in the group chat, I'm in these group chats and I'm seeing all of these
things happen. I'm chiming in every now and then, but really mostly like lurking in this group chat
where all of this organization is happening and then January 6th starts being planned.
Around the time that January 6th is being planned, a group called Women for Trump gets involved and
immediately as soon as Women for Trump get involved, I'm like, guys, I am not comfortable
with this because previously it wasn't really Trump centered. I was trying to focus the messaging
more on election integrity generally and once Women for Trump got involved, I was like,
this kind of stinks. I don't like that we're attaching Trump's name to this. This seems like
it could go south very quickly and I was very vocal about that. Simultaneously, I am working
for a company, a right-wing company that does production and there are a lot of people involved
in the day of January 6th and January 5th. There was an event on January 5th where people were
speaking that I was supposed to speak at and I ended up backing out and giving my speaking slot
to someone else because I felt so uncomfortable. Then on January 6th itself, the company I was
working at was responsible for some of the assets and videos that were played on screen while people
were speaking so I had to go to DC that day. So I am in DC on January 6th. I am at this like
VIP speaking event technically for work and then Rudy Giuliani gets on stage and this man is saying
the craziest shit I have ever heard and I just look around. I'm like, you know, I'm gonna skedaddle.
I don't really want to be here. I'm gonna skedaddle and I go see my friend who's like across
the way from the Capitol who has an office and studio there. Mind you, oh my god this is leaking.
Mind you, on my way down to DC, I got in a little scuffle with a left-wing journalist
on the train and I posted a video of it. It ended up going viral. So on January 6th itself, I am
slated to do media on a few right-wing outlets and at this point I'm stoked. I'm like, oh yay I
get to be on TV. I get to be on radio. All of a sudden, I am waiting in one of the studios to do
my hits and get my little air time and January 6th happens. Now this was not the appropriate reaction
but at first I'm pissed because I'm supposed to be on TV. I'm supposed to have my moment
and these people are storming the Capitol. How could they do this to me, you know?
And so at this point, I'm still in this group chat for Stop the Steal and they are, you know,
the organizers are like, do you think our event is still happening? I'm like, are you, do you guys see
what's happening? They're storming the Capitol. No. So I am like across the street from the Capitol
at a studio at this point and I get a call from Charlie Kirk's producer and Charlie. They want
me to go on the Charlie Kirk show and tell them what's going on. So I do. I go on Charlie Kirk's,
I think it was his radio show or his podcast and I'm like, yeah, I don't know what's going on.
There's like, I don't know if it's a flare or a gunshot. There's people scaling. There's scaffolding
being climbed. This is, um, no good, very bad bears outside guys. Again, I am here technically
for work and my hotel is in Virginia, but because these insurrectionist hooligans are storming the
Capitol, uh, and performing a violent insurrection, they shut down all of DC. So I cannot go to my
hotel in Virginia. I ended up calling one of my friends who at the time was at the White House.
He's actually at the White House now. Um, but I know he had an apartment nearby and I call him
and I'm like, please tell me you're home because this is crazy. I don't know where to go. I can't
go to my hotel. I'm stuck. They're shutting down the whole city. At this point, everyone who cares
about me is seeing what's happening on the TV and they're calling to make sure I'm alive and that
I'm not storming the Capitol. Um, and I ended up going to this friend's house and we are just
watching this happen live on the television. Obviously law enforcement and our government
had lots of questions about everyone involved, how this happened, uh, how the insurrection happened,
how they ended up storming the Capitol, um, yada yada who. And because I was in these group chats
with individuals who were planning events on that day, I ended up being investigated by the FBI
for years. I mean, they are interrogating my family. They are interrogating, you know,
exes of mine. I am showing up in like official testimony because people who were more involved
than I was were being asked who was in these group chats and I was one of these people.
And the FBI is, is questioning my family and people close to me. You know, do you,
do you know her involvement? Do you know if they're planning anything else? Um,
just really insane stuff. And obviously my rhetoric around the election integrity
contributed to, um, the conditions that created January 6th. However,
being investigated by the feds for two years over this was rather extreme.
And at this point I am watching people drop like flies over January 6th. This person's
getting arrested. This person's being dragged on the house floor for questioning. And I am like
any day now I am going to get raided by the feds. So I am going to sleep making sure my hair is
cute and I'm wearing a cute pajama set because I did not want to get Roger stoned. I was not
about to have the feds come in and we have some embarrassing footage from the feds.
Something else to understand about January 6th and that day, particularly the involvement of
influencers and figures, is that it was framed as like any other event. And this is not to
discount the impact and what transpired on that day, but we were literally given VIP badges. And
you know, in my head, you're never like, oh, I'm giving a VIP badge for an insurrection.
Wait, I have the badge. Hang on. I had to finish this up first. One moment. I've got my bag. Oh,
here it is. And here it is. So this was Stop the Steal Media, January 5th and 6th. And then,
oh, Women for America First, which was Women for Trump, basically. Save America March,
VIP January 6th. So, you know, VIP badge to the insurrection.
So yeah, anyways, I'm not proud of my involvement. However, I also think people need to understand
how much these influencers and organizations are used as pawns for really sinister political agendas.