Get ready with me while I tell you more about the women of Mar-a-Lago. For those who don't know,
my name is Ashley St. Clair. I was a MAGA influencer involved in MAGA politics
for almost a decade. I know. Now, if you haven't watched my first video on the women of Mar-a-Lago,
I suggest you do that down in this playlist. But we are going to discuss one of these Mar-a-Lago
real white housewives of Palm Beach, D.C. that I had mentioned earlier, and that is Ozempe. We are
going to continue calling her Ozempe because this woman is batshit insane. She is currently suing
one of her apartment complexes because she got stuck in the elevator for a moment, and now she's
suing them for $50,000, claiming emotional distress from this while she's gallivanting
around at parties and whatever. I also want to say and preface this by saying that I'm talking
about Ms. Ozempe for a few reasons. One of which, she holds immense power at the State Department
and around the White House and around the Trump administration. So if you want to be a public
figure and you want to make decisions for me with my tax dollars, I'm going to chit chat about it.
Secondly, I'm also just really hurt because these were people that I had considered friends,
but at the same time, I can only blame myself because this only happened to me and I was only
the victim of their cruelty because I ignored their cruelty to other people,
including incredibly marginalized groups. When I was rereading my text with her,
I was disgusted not only at the things coming out of her mouth, but me ignoring some of this blatant,
awful, awful racist behavior at times. Like I'm so disgusted with myself that this was
the company that I kept and that I helped enable these people. So I knew Ozempe through the Maga
and Turning Point events, but we really didn't start getting close until 2020.
And in retrospect, I think this was because she was fucking my boss, Jason Cole. Remember Benny
Johnson's business partner? So around this time, she starts an affair because mind you, Jason's
married and she's married. Oh, by the way, this is George. And so Ozempe starts sleeping with Jason
Cole and engaging in this affair and her and I get closer, I really think because she just wanted
more information on where Jason was and the company. But nonetheless, it did evolve into
what I thought was a genuine friendship, more of like, I saw her kind of as a big sister in a way.
And there were times that she was good to me. But this entire friendship, I was watching her
cheat on her husband and engage in affairs with I don't even know how many men and women at this
point. As I am getting closer with Ozempe, I'm also getting closer with her husband who is,
I am the last person to defend a man just based on the fact that they're a man. But this man
was so good to Ozempe and such a good husband and such a good dad. So I was also getting closer
with her family and her son and the other people within her life. Oh my god, now they're both
trying to attack the screensaver. That's George and Leno. No, no, no. I have to change the screensaver.
We had to go back to the pipes because the cats were attacking the screen. So Ozempe
is from Philadelphia. And during COVID, she convinces her husband that she needs to move
to Palm Beach. And her husband does this for her, they end up moving to Jupiter. And Ozempe starts
social climbing there. And something that may seem small to other people, but while I was going
through this, it just shows what a chameleon she is and social climber. So when she moved from
Philadelphia to Palm Beach, she gave me a bunch of her clothes that she said were to Philadelphia
and completely changed her wardrobe into this flora, Lola Dre Zimmerman-esque aesthetic.
She is always fighting with her then husband about money. She would come to New York and he
would send her, you know, $1,500. She would blow through it in a second and she would start
screaming and crying and saying that she needed more money. And again, she was also really class
signaling to be a part of this Palm Beach socialite Mar-a-Lago crew with the fake Cartier
and the fake bags. And her whole existence was this social light life. And then she starts
developing a friendship with Laura Trump. I almost forgot this, but at one point she was
crying and breaking down and begging and berating her husband for them to get a membership at Trump
Jupiter, but they didn't have the money. So they settled on a seasonal membership.
I think Ozempie saw Laura Trump as her in into legitimacy within the Real Housewives of MAGA
here, because almost immediately Ozempie starts trying to sabotage all of Laura's other friends,
saying that she doesn't think these people are becoming for Laura to be around. Starts,
you know, saying she should have PIs investigate these other friends. Starts sending around,
you know, explicit photos and explicit information about one of these women's husbands.
It was nasty. Honestly, I know this is mean, but she was just dumb. Like one of the dumb
people that are just really obsessed with woke when I was going through our texts at one point,
she had sent me like a black Santa Claus that was at Target. And she she said, geographically,
he's from the North Pole. He's not black. Well, geographically, he can't fucking traverse the
whole globe and deliver presents to little children made by made up elves. Okay, he's not
fucking real. Like what the fuck? Anyways, I digress. So she right away when she starts this
friendship with Laura, she is spilling Laura's personal affairs to anyone who listens. She
ends up telling me and others that Alina Haba is sleeping with Laura's husband, Eric, and possibly
Donald Trump senior. This is what she's telling me. And then she's posting photos at a workout
class with Laura as if she's not doing this. At this time, she's also leaking an ungodly amount
of information to the press about really anything she wants to gossip about. And while simultaneously
really coming into full transformation for this Real Housewives of MAGA, she's running around with
the women for Trump going on the campaign trail, while simultaneously tripping balls at Burning
Man and cheating on her husband. Mind you, her husband thinks everything is fine. He loves her
to pieces. And then Ozempia meets a very powerful person at the White House and someone who has been
Trump's right hand man for quite some time. And Ozempia is basically like, this is my ticket
out. So she starts an affair a while after, blindsides her husband with this information,
says that she's moving to DC, leaving her husband, leaving her kid in Florida, and she's moving to DC
with this man who she thinks can do more for her than her husband. So Ozempia starts with her ticket
out and we will call this man Jigglypuff because I don't know, I just think of Jigglypuff when I see
him. And so right away, this is toxic with Jigglypuff. She moves in with Jigglypuff in DC
and is calling me crying, saying Jigglypuff won't give her money, won't give her a card.
And so I'm sending Ozempia money at this point. Nonetheless, she's still ecstatic because she
has social climbed all the way to the top and Jigglypuff had a meeting with Donald Trump to get
her a job that is completely made up and she doesn't do. And it seems like they're just using
it to funnel money to her friend that she went to Burning Man with, but that's for another video.
Oh, Ozempia also at one point told me that for the case against Elon Musk in Philadelphia,
that it was going to go in his favor because she knew the judge's daughter and that he was going
to have favor towards Elon. And then she suggested that we get this judge a job in the administration,
to which I said that would be quid pro quo. I'm sure Ozempia is back to her old ways,
trying to place dirt on me, but I don't care. I don't care if you place dirt on me because anyone
who wants to read the dirt on me, the dirt, as if I'm not saying it myself, when I don't make any
consequential decisions for people, I'm not at the State Department. I'm not at the White House.
You don't get to have it both ways. You wanted to involve yourself in these high profile
matters and be so adjacent to power. You're not a private citizen anymore.