Get ready with me while I talk about the allegations that I baby trapped Elon Musk.
For those who don't know, my name is Ashley St. Clair and I was a MAGA influencer involved in MAGA politics for way too fucking long.
I know.
Also, I'm not original.
Somebody commented that and said I should say that in the beginning, so.
We are going to address one of the most prolific smears against me and that is the accusation that I somehow baby trapped a grown ass 50 something year old man, okay?
Now, the way in which this has been put out on the internet, you would think I was poking a hole in a condom that was never used.
We are going to address this because one of the reasons this became so prolific was because the woman who put this smear out with text from me is one of the nastiest, vilest bitches I have ever had the displeasure of meeting in my life.
Her name is Isabella Riley, or now Isabella Moody, after she married a child.
When I met Isabella, I was working at Arsenal Media Group, the company founded by Benny Johnson and run by that sick alcoholic Jason Cole, okay?
And Isabella was just putting out tweets on social media trying to be a MAGA e-girl with every fiber of her being.
I think at this point she was like a libertarian e-girl.
Nonetheless, we needed more people for this company so I recruited her to work there.
I also, because she was young, she was like my age, I felt some sort of like protection over her.
I was trying to, you know, tell her to be careful in the space, whatever.
But it turns out she was just a nasty, vile bitch, okay?
So when she worked at this company, we also had campaigns that we fundraised for and I had to keep her away from certain events because I have never heard a woman say the word labia so often.
It was just gross, like she was just a classless, dirty woman and has a lot of problems, okay?
Like her parents abandoned her at one point, like she was in foster care, like I don't know.
She has like a lot of unresolved issues that she should be in therapy but instead she's on Twitter being racist.
So Isabella, she makes this whole video when the news about my child with Elon breaks.
She makes this entire video, she posts texts from me, she makes a video saying my ex-best friend trapped Elon.
First of all, we were never best friends, like we would hang out because, you know, we worked together and we were in the space but like I never considered this girl like a close friend, okay?
She just doesn't have any friends, especially girlfriends, because she's a nasty bitch.
Nonetheless, once I leave this company, I leave it very explosively.
I am telling all the staff, I'm like, if you guys need another job and you leave, I will help you get another job because this is a disaster.
Nobody's getting paid.
And at first, people are viewing me like this chaotic force, like oh my god, I'm just blowing this company up.
And then Isabella, of all people, I leave in 2022.
In early 2023, Isabella, I get a text from her after not speaking to her for a while and she says, she apologizes.
She says, you were right about Jason and this company.
I'm sorry.
And I'm like, yeah bitch, I was right.
Ostracized for being right once again.
At this point, I'm still like sort of friendly with her but I don't really want anything to do with her because she's just insane, okay?
Online, she is posting the craziest, most racist shit ever, okay?
At one point, according to other people familiar with the matter, she had to deactivate her Twitter account because she posted a video of her baby saying the n-word, okay?
This woman is fucking batshit insane.
But let me remind you, I knew this girl before she was on this trad wife path pretending to be all good and holy.
I knew her when she worked at Arsenal and she was dating her college boyfriend named Sean.
Now, Sean was working the night shift at the Amazon warehouse so that he could pay their rent in their Brooklyn apartment.
Meanwhile, she was going spread eagle on the couch of members of the New York Republicans Club and being a hussy.
Also in early 2023, I get a call from a mutual friend of me and Isabella.
At this point, Isabella has like absconded to Texas to marry a guy who's like fucking 12.
I think he's like 18, she's like 25, I don't know.
And this mutual friend calls me and she's like, I know you hate Isabella, but I'm really concerned for her because I think she's in an abusive controlling situation with Josiah, her husband.
And I'm like, okay, like I can try to just maintain more contact with her so that she feels like she has a girlfriend.
So like I'm just sending her girlfriendy texts.
And around the same time, Elon follows me.
And again, I don't know this man, like everyone is just obsessed with Elon in the MAGA space and everyone's paying attention to who he follows.
And when he follows me, I'm getting all these texts like, oh, you're the next baby mama.
So I sent Isabella a text and I'm like, oh my god, the pressure's on to be funny.
Like Elon followed me, I need the rocket babies, I will seduce him, get in the rocket and like see what's up if the moon landing was fake, all this stuff.
She posts these texts and says that I've been plotting to get an Elon baby once I release this.
Mind you, I meet Elon in May of 2023.
I'm not pregnant until January of 2024.
Okay, like it's not adding up.
Okay.
And again, I was not concerned about this because I have the tax, I have everything.
I like, I don't care.
Nonetheless, this becomes prolific that I'm like baby trapping this man.
There's also like some random tweet that I could not find anywhere saying like, oh, like, let Elon know like I want a marriage proposal, like whatever.
Okay, even if this was I can't even find the tweet anywhere.
But even if it was real, like what there's like one tweet I made about this guy who's a celebrity in a public figure like joking about the number of kids he has like as if this is not common knowledge, like what the fuck.
So Isabella posts this and she makes an hour long video saying that I'm you know, I plotted this, she has to do this now to defend Elon because he's just this honorable moral billionaire who's now being smeared and baby trapped by me.
Like what did these people think?
Like I've just been plotting for half I had nothing better to do that I'm just like plotting to baby trap Elon Musk like what the fuck is wrong with you people?
And she's like living high off of this.
Okay, she is getting more clicks than she's ever gotten in her life.
And just so you can understand like the type of people who are my detractors in this situation, this woman at one point, she said that women with stage four cancer, nobody no man wants them because they don't have hair to pull.
She offered her daughter to a PDF file, her husband's texting me.
And he said that he wanted me to tell you that we will have our daughter ready for you as a virgin.
Okay, like these are, and these are their sources, by the way.
And so anyway, she posts these texts, which, to me, like I can tell when something's objectively bad, but I could not wrap my head around how people were reading these and being like, Oh, yeah, she was baby trapping them.
Because it reads like just girl talk just like, Oh my god, he followed me like we're getting the rocket babies.
Like what the fuck?
Mind you, at the same time, okay, it wasn't long after that, that I had my first encounter with Elon, in which we did engage in coitus and he told me to pick a name.
I still have the text from someone who's currently at the State Department, in which I talk about getting a plan B.
And I did not want to have a child at this time.
I am texting her like, dude, I cannot I cannot have a child right now.
Like I do not want to do this.
My friend is texting me abortion options.
Okay, is that the conversations of someone who is just baby trapping a billionaire?
First of all, how do you do that?
Second of all, it just runs counter to literally everything else that is available.
And I feel it's important to address this because I don't ever want my son to grow up and read this shit and think that he was some pawn in a gold digging baby trap scheme because that's just not the truth.
Whatever people think about my decisions, when I did get pregnant, that was a conscious consensual choice between two adults who we will get to that later, but had a discussion about it.
This wasn't just like, again, poking a hole in a condom the first time I met him.
There was a long standing, whatever you want to call it relationship history of interaction, many, many times that we met up before I ever got pregnant.
And there were many times that I could have.
And then this nasty bitch also brings my older son into this saying that, oh, I don't care about my older son.
She goes and she works and she's speaking at conferences in Italy.
And she says, you don't see me at conferences.
Yeah, because nobody invites you because you're a racist, nasty bitch.
Okay.
Like it doesn't make you a bad mom to work.
Anyone who knows me knows I love my kids more than anything.
Like being a mom is the most important aspect of my life.
And only one of us allegedly has had CPS investigations over what we're posting online.
Okay.
Regarding our children.
So, you know, these texts between her and I that have now become like the crux of the baby trapping proof happened in May of 2023.
We really, I don't talk to her at all.
After July of 2023, she tries meeting up with me at an event that I'm at in Texas in June of 23.
And I just ignore her.
Like I'm, I'm not meeting up with you.
I had offered to like help her and bring her gifts for her baby, whatever.
Like I was trying to be nice because someone told me that your husband's abusing you.
Okay.
And that was the extent I was being a girlfriend.
And she's also like just nasty, like rereading our texts.
She was just like, we were just being like mean girls talking shit about other it.
Girls like her just have so much unresolved trauma.
And I know because I was one of these people and they just hate themselves.
Like she hates herself.
She'll pretend like she doesn't, but she's saying that women shouldn't vote.
Meanwhile, like she has a podcast, like that's not very Christian godly woman to like be yapping all day.
Like you're a yenta.
Also, let's just clarify, because in my text to her, I'm like, Oh my God, I need to post about the dangers of AI.
I wasn't actually posting anything about this as everyone else did.
I started just getting more interested in AI, but I'm posting, Elon's liking my tweets saying that I've never seen a man use a coupon and talking about the moon landing.
Like this isn't, I wasn't having to adjust anything for him to take a liking to me.
Like also when we interviewed him, when this relationship started, he was very aware that I was just a 24 year old at any managerial position at the company.
He was doing an interview with like this.
He was fully aware of who I was like, what do people think I did?
Like I just AI posted my way into like getting a baby.
Like, honestly, what the fuck guys?
And what does that say?
If we are to stipulate that this is what happened, I just made so many tweets about the dangers of AI that this man was baby trapped.
This like purported genius was baby trapped.
Like, what the fuck does that say about this grown ass man who has like all these government contracts?
Like, do you people even hear yourselves?
Like, I'm just so smart and manipulative and like femme fatal that I did this.
What the fuck?
And I guess I haven't spoken about the truth because the truth is much more embarrassing.
In fact, I wish that this was just a story about how someone baby trapped the richest man in the world.
No, the truth is actually much more embarrassing because the truth is that I actually, I actually liked this man.
Okay.
The truth is much more embarrassing because like many people, I unfortunately believed in this man.
The truth is much more embarrassing because I took the words out of his mouth at face value.
And sure, I did start posting about
rockets and AI a bit more, but that's because being in a room alone with this man, and I call
it like the Elon effect because I've seen this happen, especially like with different
members in our government now and officials, to hear him talk about space and this higher
cause for humanity, especially as a young girl in her early twenties, it was captivating at the
time.
I'm like, wow, there's so much more to believe in and accomplish.
And at that time, it's captivating.
So no, I did not baby trap Elon Musk.
And my son was not some pawn in a gold digging scheme.
Okay.
Many of these MAGA women, including myself, when I was involved in this cult, they hate themselves.
Everything that they're saying is because they are so uncontrollably miserable that they have nothing to talk about except other people.
And they just put evil nastiness out into the world.
And I know because I used to do that.
And when I was shitting on everyone else online, that's because I hated myself.
So I hope you find some self-love though.
I doubt you will, because you are a very, very rotten individual and you can keep talking about what you think of me as a mother, but I really do not concern myself with the opinions of people who teach their infant slurs or people who offer their daughters, their infant daughters to PDF files.