I get so many questions about my skincare and the products I use.
So me and George and Blanau are going to tell you exactly what I use.
I'm going to show you guys a few of the higher end options that I have, as well as some lower cost drugstore options, things like that.
First and foremost, I have to disclose that the best thing I ever did for my skin was the tretinoin cream, a retin-a generic prescription, and I use the .025%. That helped clear up a lot of the blackheads I had down here when nothing else would.
So, disclosure.
I'm trying to avoid the green light that keeps coming on my glasses.
Right now, I'm currently trying out the entire road kit.
So I'm doing like the whole shebang, the wash, the moisturizer, the serum, the glazing milk.
I don't know why I'm doing this because my skin is great and I feel like when things are going great, I just have a compulsion to throw something new into the mix.
So that's what I'm using right now.
However, you know what?
Let's start with the washes.
I recommend.
I'm too ADHD for this.
So every day, twice a day, I use the Inua heart leaf cleaner.
I was using the oil wash as well every day, but I found that I was making my makeup kind of slide off.
It was separating a bit.
So now I use the Inua oil wash once a week for like my everything shower.
And then also about twice a week, I use the Outsat, which is actually Scarlett Johansson's company if you didn't know.
The Outsat exfoliating cleanser.
I do that like twice a week.
And then once a week I will use this PCA skin benzoyl peroxide wash, which this is a little pricier, but I have had this for so long that I feel like it's a much cheaper than drugstore once you go down to the number of uses because I've had this for a very long time and I just use a little bit once a week.
For toner, the only toner I will use is this Inua one.
I have tried so many toners and they just don't work.
Even the Inua one that's like the pads, I feel like it's not the same formulation.
Only this one.
And then I use like the little clean pads, the square cotton pads twice a day.
For serums, I alternate between these every night.
This is the Inua, I can't pronounce that.
I don't know.
The red one.
I use that and then I use the Beauty of Josan Glow Serum and I alternate those so every other night I'll do one of them.
And then every day before my makeup, I use the La Roche-Posay C12 Oil Control Serum, which love cannot recommend enough.
And then every now and then I will use these Medicube Eczema Shots, which are like supposed to be like microneedling in a bottle.
I don't know.
That's at least what they said on TikTok.
So I was sold.
But be very careful because there's two different degrees of this.
One is 2000 and one is 7500.
So the other day when I used this, I accidentally grabbed the 7500 when I hadn't used it in a while and it was like the death of a thousand suns on my face.
Now for my favorite part, the moisturizers.
I love my moisturizers.
If you are able, invest in a good moisturizer, but there's also a lot of really affordable options that I love.
Like this, is it Nivea?
Nivea Cream, but only the German formulation.
Like if you need a lot of hydration, this is great if you have dry skin, but only the German formulation because the other one is not the same.
Like it needs to be produced, manufactured in Germany.
And then this one that I love, shout out to Bella Hadid, who, you know, I was influenced.
But this is so good, so great.
If you're going to use it before makeup, just make sure you give yourself time because it can take some time to like settle in and not be too slick.
But amazing, amazing, amazing has never done me dirty.
I also love, especially for the summer when you need more SPF because I will double up on my SPF in the summer.
I do not fuck around about the sun.
And so this La Roche-Posay, the double repair with the SPF in it, amazing.
Love it.
I did love this.
I did, but I cannot in good conscience recommend it anymore after this dude was in the files.
You know which files I'm talking about.
What a shame because that was a great product.
But I think I love this one more.
This is the priciest.
Well, actually, this one and the Tatcha one are like comparable in price, but the Pharmacy Honey Halo, this is so, so good.
I love this.
I use it at night.
Amazing.
And then you guys have seen, I use the Tatcha Dewy Skin before my makeup.
Love.
Again, on the pricier side, but these two are also just as good.
Well, they're comparable.
And then, of course, the Kiehl's Ultra.
I used to take this to my Equinox and I like hope they don't ban me for saying this, but I used to take this to my Equinox and they used to have Kiehl's at Equinox.
So I would just bump it in because this is not cheap.
And I was like, if I'm paying this much for a gym, I'm going to get my Kiehl's.
I think that's why they removed Kiehl's.
I don't steal the grown alchemist.
Okay.
Congrats.
You guys put a shitty enough product in there that I don't take it.
And lastly, also, I have to say I really love Miss Haley Bieber's Barrier Butter.
I like it.
It breaks some people out, but I like it a lot.
And then lastly, the masks and other things that I do that people have a lot of questions about.
I get a lot of questions about the chin mask I use, and this is literally just some random one from Amazon.
Chin lifting mask, 24k gold and collagen.
And then for under eyes, these are rather expensive because you only, even though it's by Hero, the same company that makes the pimple patches, the Mighty Patch, but you only get three sets in a box.
So it's kind of expensive, but I highly recommend these for if you're doing makeup for an event or you're going to be photographed because it does do a fantastic job at making your under eyes look phenomenal, but do not recommend if you're using this every day, you are wasting money.
Okay.
That is, it is just too expensive.
And of course, like every other basic bitch, I love, love, love, love, love the Metacube PDRN collagen mask.
I love this.
I also have the one that's like, you squeeze it out.
Also fun.
Also great.
But I actually like this night wrapping one from Metacube more.
It's the turmeric one.
I don't know.
I just like the way it makes my skin look in the morning better.
And then lastly, this mask again from Metacube, this is the blackhead mud mask, which is phenomenal.
I have had such an issue with blackheads, like right here.
And as you can see, like, I love picking them.
Like I, if I have a pimple, I will pop it.
I can't stop.
I have tried so many times.
And then like, I just make it worse.
Cause I'm like, Oh, it's, it's bad.
It's bad.
Again, a little pricey, but amazing is this Tatcha.
This is the eye cream.
Mixsoon also has a really, really fantastic eye cream.
That's way more affordable, but I do love the Tatcha.
I feel like I'm getting duped just because the spatulas, but they seem to work.
Maybe it's a placebo.
I don't know.
And lastly, I cannot stress enough the water.
If you are not drinking an ungodly amount of water, your skin is probably going to look like shit because your skin is the largest organ in your body.
And it is the first place that your diet, if you are not eating right, if you are not hydrating enough, the largest organ in your body is going to manifest that you are not taking care of yourself.
So I cannot stress enough how important your water intake and your diet is to your skin.
If you start tracking, usually your skin will change about two weeks after you eat like shit.
I don't know.
Anyways, those are the products that I recommend that are in my rotation.
And also, if you guys want me to do a video on the products that I do not recommend, because I do have a lot of those, let me know.
And again, I am purposely not linking any of these products, of which many of them have TikTok shop links, but I need the opinion to be honest.